{
	"description": "Component to kanji quiz: Give a kanji which includes the component shown",
	"deck": [
		{ "question": "一", "answers": ["二", "三", "勺", "兀", "天", "今", "元", "夫", "仁", "互", "井", "升", "云", "尤", "帀", "弌", "卅", "弖", "正", "石", "本", "半", "司", "失", "末", "未", "令", "弁", "冊", "丙", "旦", "丼", "丕", "弍", "冉", "卉", "卮", "辷", "册", "先", "百", "会", "光", "行", "合", "西", "同", "死", "両", "列", "共", "伝", "再", "后", "至", "弐", "刑", "吏", "亙", "亘", "而", "夙", "丞", "冱", "夸", "并", "戌", "聿", "形", "体", "里", "囲", "完", "芸", "低", "冷", "均", "判", "戒", "更", "寿", "伴", "邦", "亜", "呉", "但", "扶", "弄", "芙", "伶", "吞", "佚", "佞", "刪", "妍", "尨", "沍", "沛", "阮", "芫", "巵", "删", "画", "岩", "姉", "妹", "具", "使", "事", "実", "昔", "定", "味", "命", "底", "例", "券", "妻", "制", "武", "供", "担", "拝", "並", "征", "拓", "抵", "到", "昇", "奉", "斉", "邸", "迭", "併", "奔", "抹", "岡", "玩", "妬", "其", "侠", "尭", "些", "竺", "苒", "坦", "宕", "沫", "苓", "怜", "或", "亟", "佩", "佰", "侖", "冽", "刳", "囹", "妲", "帙", "忝", "怛", "拌", "昊", "枡", "枅", "肬", "矼", "羌", "歿", "殀", "茉", "罔", "刱", "拋", "亞", "兩", "卷", "室", "首", "春", "前", "昼", "屋", "研", "拾", "送", "発", "美", "面", "型", "建", "便", "逆", "政", "律", "巻", "砂", "専", "宣", "洗", "奏", "肺", "威", "狭", "恒", "咲", "是", "耐", "柄", "冒", "冠", "峡", "契", "胆", "厘", "垣", "挟", "洪", "砕", "津", "甚", "洞", "畏", "柵", "昧", "姶", "恰", "垢", "荊", "巷", "珊", "屍", "柘", "茜", "殆", "廼", "姪", "叛", "柾", "俣", "玲", "歪", "荆", "俚", "兪", "冑", "剏", "剄", "勁", "厖", "咢", "咸", "咥", "哄", "哈", "哂", "垤", "姜", "屏", "恍", "恫", "扁", "拱", "拯", "斫", "昜", "閂", "柢", "胝", "胚", "胖", "洸", "洽", "洌", "洒", "爰", "癸", "砒", "砌", "牴", "炳", "陋", "陌", "疣", "殃", "殄", "荅", "莽", "衍", "穽", "舁", "姮", "俞", "拜", "夏", "書", "院", "真", "病", "害", "挙", "差", "残", "借", "倉", "益", "耕", "師", "破", "蚕", "従", "恵", "剣", "剤", "致", "倒", "胴", "峰", "砲", "烈", "倹", "殊", "畔", "埋", "恭", "剛", "殉", "症", "泰", "秩", "朕", "逓", "俸", "耗", "倫", "釜", "桁", "拳", "凄", "唖", "桧", "桓", "莞", "倶", "倦", "晃", "砿", "晒", "栖", "朔", "砥", "晋", "秦", "迺", "砧", "套", "桐", "涛", "峯", "哩", "浬", "狸", "砺", "俱", "倆", "冓", "哽", "哢", "恙", "拿", "挈", "旆", "耙", "耘", "桎", "蚌", "蚩", "胱", "胯", "胼", "浣", "笄", "珮", "砠", "紜", "烝", "袢", "袒", "羔", "眛", "陞", "疸", "茣", "逅", "迸", "秣", "祗", "冦", "弉", "徑", "莖", "晉", "黒", "野", "理", "悪", "宿", "転", "械", "健", "得", "副", "規", "基", "険", "術", "異", "域", "済", "陰", "惜", "措", "窒", "隆", "渓", "曹", "瓶", "偏", "庸", "惧", "梗", "羞", "寅", "捲", "袴", "袷", "砦", "匙", "淀", "梼", "祷", "捧", "逢", "婁", "渕", "偸", "冕", "剪", "剳", "匐", "匏", "寇", "崙", "崘", "彗", "惓", "悽", "惘", "戛", "掟", "耜", "麸", "蛉", "梔", "脛", "曼", "趺", "馗", "淒", "淪", "笨", "硅", "絆", "聆", "瓸", "焉", "烽", "裄", "羝", "羚", "眷", "殍", "菫", "逕", "竡", "盒", "衒", "舂", "萁", "圈", "國", "專", "晝", "雲", "絵", "場", "答", "道", "開", "寒", "期", "港", "勝", "着", "湯", "童", "筆", "陽", "街", "給", "極", "散", "焼", "満", "量", "検", "減", "証", "提", "備", "富", "貴", "勤", "就", "善", "棒", "握", "援", "圏", "殖", "替", "堤", "塔", "普", "幅", "惑", "敢", "棋", "欺", "喫", "硬", "葬", "揚", "裂", "暁", "滋", "硝", "喪", "搭", "筒", "廃", "塀", "遍", "愉", "硫", "媛", "喩", "渥", "淵", "萱", "葵", "喧", "硯", "蛤", "斯", "蛭", "棲", "揃", "湊", "巽", "硲", "溌", "弼", "斌", "裡", "葎", "棊", "厥", "喊", "喘", "堙", "孳", "寔", "寐", "幄", "愕", "惴", "愃", "戞", "掣", "揆", "揣", "揄", "朞", "蛬", "跖", "跌", "跚", "湲", "湮", "湍", "湎", "渝", "湃", "軼", "筅", "鈞", "絖", "絎", "絣", "詆", "瓠", "猯", "鄂", "痙", "粨", "甦", "萼", "畴", "皖", "耋", "賁", "觝", "翕", "厦", "堯", "惠", "貳", "殘", "殼", "畫", "黑", "感", "漢", "業", "鉄", "福", "腸", "義", "傷", "蒸", "暖", "裏", "煙", "遣", "誇", "歳", "慎", "嘆", "殿", "微", "誉", "隔", "慈", "滞", "滅", "零", "虞", "頑", "碁", "溝", "嗣", "塑", "鉢", "鈴", "僅", "塞", "煎", "羨", "填", "蜂", "溢", "碍", "跨", "幌", "嵯", "嵳", "獅", "鉦", "瑞", "碓", "椿", "碇", "逼", "蒙", "愈", "傭", "楊", "碗", "溯", "堽", "韵", "亶", "僉", "僂", "嗟", "嗄", "嗤", "嗔", "媾", "廈", "愆", "惷", "搆", "搓", "暘", "暄", "耡", "蜈", "榁", "楔", "楡", "腱", "腟", "跣", "滉", "輊", "輌", "肄", "肆", "瑜", "髢", "碚", "硼", "碌", "煬", "煖", "誄", "詬", "閙", "裲", "褄", "隘", "粳", "蓁", "貊", "逾", "衙", "祺", "豢", "輀", "榆", "觥", "痹", "碎", "會", "經", "肅", "與", "勤", "碑", "算", "鼻", "様", "関", "旗", "演", "構", "製", "銅", "領", "誤", "磁", "需", "端", "髪", "網", "綱", "魂", "遭", "碑", "墨", "僕", "遡", "綻", "蔑", "瘍", "蔭", "厭", "榎", "劃", "箕", "閤", "瑳", "爾", "榛", "槙", "碩", "銑", "漕", "暢", "肇", "鳳", "碧", "蓬", "摑", "屢", "僥", "僣", "僮", "匱", "墅", "幗", "愨", "愬", "慵", "搴", "閧", "蜷", "槎", "寨", "槊", "膈", "靤", "漾", "箚", "髦", "髣", "碪", "碣", "銜", "綣", "綸", "聢", "甄", "甅", "熏", "誡", "褊", "靼", "靺", "鞆", "瘉", "殞", "蔔", "蓿", "遘", "竰", "禊", "厮", "髥", "劄", "綦", "齊", "盡", "輕", "稱", "壽", "對", "臺", "福", "嘆", "漢", "賓", "選", "養", "輪", "確", "潔", "賛", "導", "編", "暴", "遺", "論", "輝", "儀", "賦", "噴", "黙", "緩", "衝", "穂", "潜", "鋳", "墳", "魅", "霊", "槽", "賓", "憤", "弊", "撲", "窯", "潰", "稽", "憧", "餅", "頬", "慧", "翫", "槻", "蕨", "撒", "撰", "撞", "箭", "糎", "歎", "樗", "蕩", "磐", "篇", "緬", "鋒", "聨", "澂", "僵", "匳", "嘶", "嶢", "幢", "廝", "廛", "撓", "撕", "麩", "霈", "蝠", "蝙", "蝓", "蟒", "槿", "膣", "滕", "澆", "濆", "輦", "輛", "箴", "瑾", "髫", "髯", "髴", "髱", "磑", "磋", "碾", "磅", "碼", "磊", "緘", "縅", "醋", "諚", "鬧", "獗", "瞋", "殤", "蕘", "翦", "翩", "魳", "踑", "耦", "齒", "劍", "儉", "樣", "樓", "數", "髮", "墨", "穀", "德", "徵", "整", "衛", "興", "輸", "憲", "鋼", "縦", "獣", "曇", "錯", "錠", "嬢", "壇", "縫", "憾", "衡", "儒", "壌", "磨", "諭", "融", "膳", "緻", "麺", "叡", "窺", "彊", "頸", "髭", "儘", "黛", "醍", "澱", "醗", "儔", "冀", "嘯", "嶬", "嶮", "彜", "撼", "擅", "黔", "鴟", "鴒", "鮖", "曁", "耨", "閾", "橄", "樸", "橦", "橈", "膩", "踰", "靦", "澪", "濛", "輻", "輳", "駢", "歙", "篝", "篩", "璞", "髻", "髷", "磔", "磬", "磧", "磚", "錻", "縊", "縉", "縢", "縒", "諤", "諠", "諞", "鬨", "褸", "躾", "羲", "瘻", "糒", "殫", "殪", "薨", "薑", "薇", "薤", "蕭", "覦", "遶", "窶", "臻", "鮇", "曉", "燒", "默", "衞", "險", "講", "厳", "縮", "翼", "齢", "犠", "謹", "購", "礁", "謄", "鍵", "戴", "瞳", "鍔", "徽", "磯", "橿", "嬬", "濡", "糟", "檀", "濤", "糞", "輿", "嶺", "嚊", "壑", "嬪", "嬶", "孺", "懃", "懦", "擡", "擣", "擯", "龠", "鼾", "黜", "黝", "齔", "斂", "鵄", "鴿", "鵆", "氈", "朦", "曚", "螻", "蠎", "檬", "蹉", "蹇", "臀", "臉", "馘", "颶", "濬", "濔", "轂", "歛", "篷", "簍", "磽", "磴", "鍼", "鍮", "縷", "艚", "謚", "謇", "襄", "瞰", "藉", "薹", "覯", "賽", "盪", "艱", "虧", "螾", "濱", "點", "彌", "壓", "檢", "題", "験", "難", "繕", "礎", "鎮", "糧", "癒", "顎", "藤", "穣", "藪", "檮", "嚢", "鞭", "鯉", "嚙", "彝", "攅", "黠", "斃", "魍", "魎", "闕", "蟯", "櫃", "檳", "臑", "瀁", "瀑", "騏", "麌", "簣", "鬆", "礒", "礑", "鎰", "鎹", "繧", "繖", "繞", "釐", "艟", "燼", "鞳", "瞼", "矇", "癜", "餮", "殯", "藕", "覲", "邇", "觴", "翹", "鵥", "藝", "豐", "謹", "爆", "麗", "鶏", "璽", "譜", "蹴", "麒", "蟻", "鹸", "禰", "顛", "簸", "曝", "鵡", "礪", "禱", "繡", "壜", "鵲", "蹶", "蹼", "瀟", "騙", "簽", "簫", "礙", "鏤", "艤", "艨", "譛", "襦", "鞴", "羹", "羶", "殱", "疇", "疆", "贇", "獸", "贊", "懲", "難", "議", "鐘", "譲", "籍", "醸", "騰", "鰐", "巌", "耀", "礦", "攘", "黥", "齣", "齟", "齠", "鶚", "鰔", "鰆", "鰄", "霰", "蠕", "鹹", "瀲", "瀰", "轗", "騫", "籌", "礫", "礬", "鐃", "繽", "繻", "癢", "糯", "饉", "蘯", "壥", "鰚", "鰘", "壤", "齡", "黨", "獻", "嚴", "孃", "麵", "纏", "儺", "儷", "囈", "黯", "齦", "齧", "鷁", "鰤", "曩", "蠢", "躊", "轜", "籔", "籐", "鬘", "纉", "髏", "譴", "饌", "饋", "饒", "殲", "贐", "鰧", "讃", "灘", "纒", "鑓", "囊", "儼", "儻", "攤", "龕", "齬", "齪", "罎", "霾", "蠧", "躔", "灑", "驍", "鬚", "顫", "鬻", "禳", "攢", "籡", "鑄", "聽", "穰", "覽", "鷲", "鑒", "黴", "靨", "籥", "鬟", "鑚", "顬", "巖", "驗", "鹼", "囓", "齷", "齲", "齶", "魘", "靆", "蠹", "鬢", "衢", "釀", "艷", "讓", "靉", "鬣", "鑰", "釁", "纘", "廳", "讚", "黶", "鱶", "驥", "黷", "驤", "鑽", "驪", "爨"] },
		{ "question": "乛", "answers": ["了", "予", "欠", "矛", "疋", "次", "序", "吹", "亨", "坎", "抒", "欧", "炊", "虎", "弥", "欣", "茅", "亟", "杼", "姿", "柔", "虐", "茨", "凾", "祢", "咨", "胥", "矜", "称", "恣", "虔", "虒", "野", "務", "欲", "盗", "虚", "旋", "軟", "蛋", "彪", "烹", "掀", "欸", "欷", "瓷", "袤", "處", "飲", "欺", "婿", "款", "疎", "欽", "疏", "厥", "嵌", "揉", "欹", "琥", "粢", "舒", "盜", "壻", "虜", "虛", "資", "預", "虞", "虜", "羨", "楚", "歇", "歃", "號", "歌", "疑", "嘘", "嗽", "墅", "漱", "歉", "遞", "壽", "劇", "歓", "戯", "膚", "慮", "慶", "蕨", "歎", "慾", "墟", "褫", "獗", "糅", "蔬", "歐", "凝", "諮", "橘", "儔", "蹂", "歔", "歙", "蕷", "盧", "篪", "豫", "據", "擬", "濤", "嚏", "嶷", "懋", "擣", "罅", "歟", "歛", "遽", "虧", "戲", "礎", "檮", "闕", "濾", "鞣", "霧", "禱", "廬", "鯱", "蠍", "蹶", "礙", "譎", "蘆", "疇", "癡", "鶩", "櫨", "臚", "籌", "醵", "獻", "爐", "躊", "歡", "懿", "艫", "饕", "鑄", "鷸", "轤", "鑢", "鑪", "顱", "驢", "鱸"] },
		{ "question": "亅", "answers": ["了", "予", "矛", "争", "亦", "序", "亨", "抒", "事", "茅", "亟", "杼", "爭", "柔", "浄", "凾", "矜", "野", "務", "烹", "崢", "袤", "淨", "揉", "筝", "舒", "預", "静", "墅", "箏", "諍", "鬧", "糅", "橘", "蹂", "錚", "鬨", "蕷", "豫", "靜", "懋", "鬩", "鞣", "霧", "瀞", "譎", "鶩", "鬪", "鷸", "鬮"] },
		{ "question": "九", "answers": ["丸", "仇", "尻", "旭", "伜", "究", "忰", "抛", "枠", "染", "軌", "砕", "粋", "翆", "執", "酔", "孰", "馗", "勢", "鳩", "雑", "塾", "熱", "熟", "摯", "蟄", "褻", "贄", "藝", "囈", "鷙"] },
		{ "question": "丶", "answers": ["丸", "凡", "刃", "叉", "勺", "今", "太", "尤", "玉", "冬", "主", "令", "斥", "丼", "仞", "匆", "尽", "帆", "汎", "亙", "妁", "戍", "扠", "扨", "芍", "図", "住", "卵", "忍", "汰", "杓", "灼", "尨", "国", "注", "的", "往", "述", "宝", "於", "兔", "拆", "肬", "泝", "苳", "刱", "拔", "柱", "約", "為", "柊", "籾", "剏", "厖", "怱", "柝", "疣", "紉", "者", "倉", "酌", "蚤", "啄", "豹", "冤", "冢", "鬯", "疼", "荵", "祓", "粏", "終", "術", "執", "釣", "掴", "梁", "偖", "偬", "唹", "孰", "梵", "鹵", "淤", "釵", "寃", "寒", "就", "訴", "塚", "靭", "葱", "註", "堵", "菟", "葢", "奢", "屠", "跋", "靫", "葯", "猪", "都", "渚", "琢", "著", "逸", "勢", "搔", "楮", "筺", "綛", "粱", "暑", "煮", "認", "塾", "駄", "蔑", "滷", "睹", "署", "寬", "熱", "熟", "駐", "稽", "摯", "箸", "潴", "魃", "瑩", "髮", "緖", "賭", "鮗", "閼", "赭", "麈", "覩", "諸", "曙", "薯", "黻", "闍", "螽", "蟄", "簗", "褻", "璧", "儲", "鼕", "贄", "藝", "麗", "璽", "蹴", "鹸", "藷", "鯲", "躇", "襪", "羸", "巉", "鹹", "贏", "騷", "儷", "囈", "鷙", "灑", "鷲", "纔", "韈", "鹼", "讒", "鹽", "鬱", "驪"] },
		{ "question": "亠", "answers": ["亡", "文", "六", "亢", "市", "玄", "交", "衣", "充", "亦", "亥", "伉", "対", "抗", "坑", "亨", "宍", "吭", "吝", "抃", "沛", "京", "姉", "夜", "育", "卒", "効", "享", "弦", "斉", "佼", "杭", "呟", "旻", "肺", "郊", "帝", "亭", "柿", "彦", "亮", "咬", "狡", "校", "高", "流", "航", "剤", "紋", "畜", "蚊", "畝", "冥", "倅", "勍", "悋", "旆", "旁", "紊", "眩", "痃", "虔", "效", "商", "産", "停", "率", "済", "郭", "斎", "涼", "舷", "牽", "絃", "惇", "淳", "烹", "掠", "琉", "偐", "孰", "悴", "毫", "梳", "淬", "猝", "萃", "皎", "衒", "景", "統", "就", "傍", "絞", "滋", "硫", "斑", "疏", "敦", "斐", "斌", "椋", "傚", "啻", "啼", "喨", "孳", "閔", "蛟", "椁", "渟", "蒂", "較", "蓄", "棄", "慈", "塙", "禽", "嵩", "亶", "幎", "旒", "滂", "溟", "雍", "鉉", "閙", "頏", "瘁", "蒿", "蒡", "稟", "禀", "碎", "適", "磁", "豪", "摘", "滴", "銃", "塾", "嫡", "廓", "膏", "翠", "敲", "暝", "槁", "榜", "膀", "漓", "犒", "鄙", "齊", "粹", "圖", "敵", "熟", "影", "稿", "締", "徹", "撤", "憬", "璃", "毅", "醇", "諒", "凜", "凛", "憫", "槨", "膵", "磅", "諄", "鬧", "瞑", "餃", "蔬", "醉", "壇", "擁", "諦", "諺", "縞", "蹄", "嚆", "壅", "廩", "懍", "擒", "擅", "暾", "螟", "駮", "燉", "檎", "藁", "鮫", "壕", "濠", "薩", "檀", "鵁", "氈", "謗", "顔", "離", "鎬", "甕", "謫", "雜", "顏", "鯨", "蹴", "鏑", "轍", "鶉", "醯", "羶", "韲", "贇", "黥", "鐓", "囃", "魑", "纐", "顫", "鷲", "黐", "籬"] },
		{ "question": "几", "answers": ["凡", "冗", "亢", "処", "凧", "机", "帆", "肌", "汎", "夙", "凪", "伉", "凩", "投", "役", "抗", "坑", "没", "吭", "芟", "拠", "殴", "股", "虎", "杭", "咒", "佩", "凭", "風", "段", "疫", "亮", "鳬", "航", "殺", "般", "飢", "珮", "殷", "設", "殻", "凰", "梵", "處", "嵐", "凱", "颪", "發", "殼", "殿", "搬", "微", "毀", "楓", "鳧", "頏", "穀", "廏", "鳳", "慇", "愨", "槃", "颯", "颱", "骰", "瘋", "撃", "盤", "毅", "磐", "潑", "撥", "瘢", "廢", "毆", "穀", "澱", "磬", "諷", "頽", "繋", "臀", "颶", "轂", "燬", "癈", "翳", "聲", "擊", "謦", "癜", "醫", "繫", "醱", "羸", "馨", "飄", "贏", "飆", "鑿"] },
		{ "question": "刀", "answers": ["刃", "切", "分", "辺", "召", "仞", "仭", "叨", "屶", "扨", "初", "忍", "扮", "劭", "吩", "岔", "芬", "苆", "券", "招", "沼", "拐", "忿", "枌", "氛", "邵", "刱", "昭", "盆", "契", "窃", "籾", "剏", "枴", "砌", "瓰", "茘", "迢", "竕", "紉", "粉", "留", "紛", "挈", "荵", "貧", "紹", "梁", "剪", "躮", "貿", "喫", "超", "詔", "雰", "靱", "靭", "貂", "照", "解", "頒", "楔", "綛", "粱", "認", "寡", "韶", "禊", "齊", "潔", "劉", "劈", "髫", "廨", "彜", "懈", "賴", "簗", "邂", "蟹", "蠏", "嬾", "懶", "獺", "韲", "藾", "瀨", "齠", "齧", "癩", "籟", "囓", "釁"] },
		{ "question": "丿", "answers": ["刃", "少", "欠", "介", "井", "乏", "升", "屯", "壬", "勿", "匁", "尤", "夭", "石", "史", "失", "必", "弁", "矛", "叱", "丼", "弗", "戊", "匆", "卉", "先", "血", "向", "次", "成", "任", "宅", "劣", "刑", "吏", "亦", "而", "托", "价", "刎", "并", "戍", "戌", "艸", "形", "弟", "囲", "告", "系", "戒", "更", "吹", "沈", "妙", "抄", "呈", "廷", "妊", "沙", "妖", "沃", "呂", "弄", "芥", "呑", "沌", "吻", "佚", "坎", "妍", "尨", "忱", "泛", "邨", "佛", "岩", "歩", "使", "物", "易", "制", "延", "拓", "茂", "欧", "昇", "炊", "泌", "斉", "迭", "沸", "併", "奔", "虎", "妬", "阜", "枕", "弥", "欣", "忽", "宕", "茅", "侘", "凭", "帙", "彿", "忝", "怫", "毟", "枡", "杪", "枅", "虱", "肬", "矼", "炒", "狒", "殀", "刱", "拋", "卹", "拔", "拂", "風", "界", "係", "研", "追", "秒", "面", "型", "省", "便", "逆", "砂", "姿", "洗", "奏", "威", "為", "柔", "耐", "虐", "卑", "砕", "帥", "茨", "侶", "胤", "荊", "柘", "荏", "剃", "祢", "荆", "俤", "剏", "厖", "咸", "咨", "咤", "姙", "屏", "怱", "恤", "斫", "昜", "洫", "砒", "砌", "瓲", "衽", "眇", "眈", "疣", "疥", "莽", "穽", "矜", "舁", "宮", "庭", "差", "笑", "孫", "耕", "師", "造", "破", "純", "秘", "剤", "称", "砲", "託", "秩", "耗", "恣", "捗", "浩", "砿", "紗", "朔", "砥", "悌", "耽", "挺", "砧", "砺", "俾", "冓", "剔", "哽", "哢", "娑", "恁", "耙", "耘", "蚩", "胼", "涕", "涎", "笏", "笄", "砠", "陞", "莚", "莎", "芻", "迸", "虔", "祓", "衄", "弉", "虒", "祕", "械", "務", "済", "密", "欲", "釈", "添", "盗", "虚", "斎", "粛", "渉", "軟", "瓶", "淫", "梗", "羞", "戚", "惚", "砦", "悉", "梯", "彪", "埠", "偬", "婬", "婢", "掀", "晧", "耜", "梠", "梏", "梃", "欸", "欷", "硅", "酖", "瓷", "袤", "袵", "貶", "悤", "處", "場", "番", "飲", "開", "寒", "着", "湯", "陽", "費", "営", "減", "備", "衆", "就", "奥", "鈍", "欺", "硬", "葬", "揚", "款", "硝", "塀", "硫", "嵐", "堺", "喬", "欽", "硯", "惣", "葱", "牌", "硲", "厥", "喊", "喘", "嵌", "惴", "掣", "揣", "揉", "脾", "跖", "跌", "跋", "颪", "湍", "渺", "湎", "軼", "筅", "欹", "琥", "鈔", "絣", "犂", "猯", "睇", "粢", "粤", "甦", "釉", "皓", "窖", "盜", "惱", "虜", "虛", "感", "鉄", "腸", "資", "傷", "聖", "賃", "歳", "滅", "虞", "碁", "溝", "塑", "艇", "虜", "塞", "羨", "頓", "碍", "嵯", "嵳", "裟", "獅", "瑞", "詫", "碓", "碇", "稗", "楓", "楊", "碗", "溯", "嗟", "嗤", "媾", "尠", "搆", "搓", "暘", "耡", "蜒", "蜑", "跣", "筥", "筵", "歇", "歃", "瑟", "瑙", "碚", "硼", "碌", "絽", "煬", "誄", "裼", "裨", "睥", "鄒", "痺", "粳", "飩", "飫", "蒭", "蓖", "輀", "蜓", "痹", "碎", "奧", "腦", "號", "碑", "歌", "算", "鼻", "構", "製", "磁", "需", "端", "碑", "酷", "遡", "遜", "蔑", "蜜", "瘍", "嘘", "僑", "瑳", "碩", "銑", "暢", "槌", "碧", "嗽", "愬", "慥", "搴", "蜴", "槎", "寨", "槊", "靤", "颯", "颱", "漱", "歉", "碪", "碣", "熏", "誡", "誥", "睾", "瘋", "遘", "齊", "遞", "確", "劇", "蔵", "誕", "歓", "戯", "膚", "慮", "審", "賜", "賓", "弊", "稽", "餅", "蕎", "蕨", "歎", "蕩", "播", "幡", "磐", "蕃", "緬", "慾", "聨", "澂", "墟", "嬌", "黎", "鴆", "魃", "閭", "霆", "蟒", "槭", "樒", "潘", "駛", "箴", "髴", "磑", "磋", "碾", "磅", "碼", "磊", "緘", "緲", "縅", "熈", "褫", "獗", "糅", "餉", "殤", "靠", "皺", "耦", "歐", "髮", "徵", "橋", "諮", "嬢", "憾", "儒", "壌", "磨", "麺", "橘", "錫", "噸", "篦", "彜", "懊", "撼", "鮖", "耨", "蹂", "膰", "靦", "澳", "駢", "歔", "歙", "篝", "篩", "磔", "磬", "磧", "磚", "縋", "縒", "燔", "諷", "糒", "薛", "盧", "篪", "據", "縣", "講", "矯", "購", "礁", "頻", "磯", "趨", "嬬", "濡", "簒", "嚊", "嬪", "嬶", "孺", "懋", "懦", "擯", "鼾", "黻", "罅", "蟋", "蠎", "蹉", "蹇", "颶", "歟", "歛", "磽", "磴", "鍼", "燠", "謇", "謐", "襄", "藉", "覯", "賽", "遽", "盪", "虧", "濱", "總", "營", "戲", "聰", "礎", "藩", "翻", "襖", "鵠", "穣", "雛", "鎚", "鵜", "嚢", "鞭", "麿", "彝", "旛", "鯀", "鯊", "闕", "蟠", "櫁", "檳", "蹙", "臑", "瀋", "濾", "礒", "礑", "繙", "髀", "鞣", "殯", "藕", "藜", "觴", "歸", "臓", "霧", "蹴", "瀕", "礪", "嚮", "廬", "鵯", "鯣", "鯱", "霪", "蠍", "櫚", "蹶", "轎", "礙", "譎", "襦", "襪", "鞴", "蘋", "蘆", "鶍", "蹻", "贊", "懲", "譲", "籍", "懸", "醸", "礦", "攘", "鶩", "鰔", "鰄", "蠕", "櫨", "蘖", "鹹", "臚", "飄", "轗", "騫", "礫", "礬", "繽", "繻", "醵", "糯", "蘯", "櫱", "壤", "獻", "孃", "爐", "釋", "麵", "飜", "鰤", "曩", "飆", "轜", "歡", "囊", "懿", "蠧", "驕", "艫", "饕", "禳", "攢", "糱", "聽", "竊", "穰", "鷲", "鷸", "鷭", "靨", "轤", "鑢", "韈", "顬", "蠹", "鬢", "鑪", "纛", "顰", "釀", "讓", "顱", "纘", "讚", "驢", "鱸", "驤", "鑽"] },
		{ "question": "又", "answers": ["叉", "友", "反", "支", "収", "双", "奴", "仮", "伎", "扠", "投", "坂", "返", "役", "努", "技", "岐", "没", "阪", "妓", "芟", "沒", "取", "受", "板", "服", "径", "枝", "版", "殴", "怪", "茎", "肢", "叔", "股", "亟", "呶", "孥", "帑", "弩", "歿", "度", "段", "侵", "怒", "疫", "叙", "盈", "凾", "叛", "拏", "殺", "浸", "般", "隻", "桑", "捜", "蚤", "俶", "叟", "殷", "翅", "冦", "経", "授", "設", "寂", "販", "殻", "淑", "掻", "啜", "娵", "娶", "寇", "掫", "曼", "跂", "釵", "陬", "菽", "敍", "軽", "極", "最", "飯", "報", "堅", "渡", "痩", "嫂", "椒", "馭", "赧", "鈑", "靫", "發", "搜", "殼", "鼓", "寝", "殿", "搬", "督", "毀", "腎", "畷", "搔", "楹", "溲", "粲", "亂", "穀", "漫", "慢", "廏", "頚", "竪", "綬", "綴", "蔓", "幔", "慇", "愨", "敲", "槃", "箙", "骰", "聚", "寢", "撃", "趣", "盤", "緊", "撮", "毅", "諏", "磐", "潑", "慳", "撥", "輙", "輟", "駑", "瘢", "魬", "廢", "毆", "穀", "瘦", "獲", "賢", "叡", "樫", "餐", "豎", "澱", "磬", "錣", "艘", "繋", "燦", "鍍", "燮", "壑", "臀", "轂", "駸", "縵", "燬", "癈", "翳", "聲", "擊", "騒", "穫", "叢", "鼕", "謦", "謾", "瞽", "癜", "醫", "雙", "繫", "醱", "蠖", "鏝", "辭", "護", "馨", "鏗", "矍", "饅", "騷", "鬘", "鰻", "鰹", "攫", "驟", "钁", "鑿"] },
		{ "question": "勹", "answers": ["勺", "勾", "匂", "勿", "匁", "包", "句", "匆", "旬", "刎", "匈", "妁", "芍", "均", "杓", "灼", "吻", "佝", "劬", "甸", "物", "的", "易", "抱", "拘", "泡", "狗", "忽", "庖", "咆", "苞", "苟", "約", "胞", "匍", "徇", "怱", "恟", "恂", "昜", "枹", "枸", "曷", "洶", "洵", "炮", "荀", "胸", "砲", "酌", "殉", "豹", "剔", "笏", "袍", "疱", "芻", "皰", "菊", "掲", "陶", "喝", "渇", "釣", "掬", "惚", "淘", "萄", "偈", "偬", "匐", "匏", "掏", "蚫", "萢", "場", "湯", "陽", "敬", "揚", "葛", "鈎", "絢", "惣", "葱", "葡", "筍", "椈", "鈞", "犂", "葯", "揭", "渴", "腸", "傷", "飽", "褐", "鉤", "楊", "韵", "暘", "雹", "蜀", "歇", "鉋", "煬", "煦", "詢", "裼", "鄒", "蒭", "蒟", "遏", "瘍", "暢", "鞄", "蜴", "靤", "碣", "綯", "蔔", "竭", "謁", "潟", "賜", "駒", "麹", "蕩", "黎", "蝎", "髱", "羯", "殤", "皺", "寫", "濁", "錫", "鮑", "麭", "檠", "獨", "謁", "鞠", "趨", "燭", "盪", "雛", "瀉", "鞫", "鞨", "藜", "觴", "警", "麴", "鯣", "蠍", "藹", "鶍", "齣", "躅", "蘯", "觸", "屬", "驚", "髑", "靄"] },
		{ "question": "儿", "answers": ["兀", "元", "匹", "允", "四", "兄", "先", "光", "西", "充", "兇", "売", "完", "児", "克", "禿", "兌", "冏", "吮", "阮", "芫", "罕", "況", "玩", "虎", "呪", "尭", "泗", "羌", "兒", "発", "祝", "洗", "冠", "甚", "茜", "廼", "亮", "剋", "哂", "恍", "洸", "洒", "院", "党", "悦", "莞", "晃", "晒", "栖", "迺", "涜", "凌", "倪", "胱", "浣", "冦", "虒", "祝", "深", "陸", "探", "脱", "陵", "兜", "彪", "菱", "寇", "崚", "猊", "竟", "焼", "税", "統", "暁", "廃", "溌", "喨", "堙", "湮", "筅", "琥", "絖", "皖", "逵", "堯", "続", "勢", "煙", "微", "隔", "頑", "睦", "幌", "稜", "蛻", "跣", "滉", "睨", "觥", "號", "読", "説", "境", "銃", "貌", "銑", "綾", "僥", "兢", "膈", "甄", "遞", "熱", "鋭", "輝", "閲", "翫", "嶢", "廛", "撓", "澆", "駟", "褫", "蕘", "貎", "稷", "禝", "融", "醗", "憺", "霓", "橈", "澹", "薇", "薐", "遶", "篪", "曉", "擔", "燒", "檐", "磽", "謖", "褻", "藐", "膽", "蟯", "繞", "鬩", "瞻", "翹", "藝", "鏡", "鯢", "鯱", "蟾", "麑", "簷", "贊", "競", "耀", "鐃", "譫", "贍", "獻", "纏", "囈", "饒", "躔", "驍", "饕", "鬻", "攢", "纘", "讚", "鑽"] },
		{ "question": "口", "answers": ["中", "石", "右", "兄", "古", "台", "号", "加", "史", "司", "可", "句", "召", "占", "叱", "叶", "叩", "只", "叮", "叨", "叭", "叺", "名", "回", "合", "西", "同", "向", "各", "仲", "舌", "吸", "后", "叫", "吐", "吉", "如", "吏", "吃", "吋", "吊", "吁", "扣", "足", "何", "谷", "局", "君", "告", "別", "否", "乱", "含", "吹", "沖", "克", "亜", "吟", "呉", "呈", "串", "冶", "呂", "杏", "邑", "伽", "亨", "吾", "呆", "呑", "吠", "吻", "吞", "估", "佝", "兌", "冏", "劬", "劭", "吽", "听", "吭", "吼", "吮", "吶", "吩", "吝", "呎", "狆", "岩", "京", "知", "店", "苦", "始", "使", "事", "味", "命", "和", "固", "治", "周", "河", "居", "舎", "招", "沿", "呼", "忠", "奇", "況", "沼", "拓", "拘", "拐", "享", "尚", "苛", "呪", "妬", "阿", "茄", "侃", "狗", "姑", "帖", "苫", "苔", "宕", "或", "咒", "亟", "佶", "刮", "劼", "咏", "呵", "咎", "呟", "呷", "呻", "咀", "呶", "咄", "咐", "咆", "怡", "怙", "拈", "抬", "沽", "沾", "矼", "邵", "苟", "迚", "舍", "活", "点", "客", "研", "拾", "昭", "品", "祝", "故", "保", "砂", "枯", "咲", "俗", "哀", "架", "促", "胎", "怠", "括", "砕", "亭", "洞", "咽", "侶", "胡", "廻", "姶", "珂", "迦", "咳", "恰", "凾", "垢", "哉", "柘", "茜", "殆", "廼", "俣", "洛", "亮", "卻", "剋", "呱", "呰", "哇", "咢", "咸", "咥", "咬", "哄", "哈", "咨", "咫", "哂", "咤", "徊", "恪", "恬", "恫", "挌", "拮", "斫", "枴", "柯", "枷", "枳", "枸", "洽", "洒", "珈", "砒", "砌", "炯", "狢", "茴", "荅", "茹", "茗", "迢", "迥", "高", "員", "荷", "宮", "倍", "害", "郡", "倉", "浴", "格", "個", "造", "破", "容", "党", "剣", "唐", "胴", "砲", "悦", "倹", "悟", "哲", "唆", "唇", "剖", "唄", "捉", "哺", "唖", "桔", "浩", "砿", "晒", "栖", "砥", "恕", "哨", "迺", "啄", "砧", "桐", "捌", "哩", "砺", "倚", "倨", "凅", "剞", "勍", "哥", "哦", "唏", "唔", "哽", "哮", "哭", "哢", "唳", "圄", "娟", "峪", "悁", "悒", "悋", "拿", "捐", "韋", "涓", "珞", "砠", "烙", "狷", "郢", "郤", "痂", "莟", "茣", "逅", "迴", "站", "舐", "罟", "祝", "船", "悪", "商", "部", "問", "唱", "停", "堂", "副", "寄", "険", "常", "略", "域", "捨", "欲", "紹", "脱", "郭", "啓", "粘", "陪", "喝", "患", "崎", "据", "培", "唯", "涼", "埼", "唾", "袈", "梧", "袷", "釦", "砦", "惇", "淳", "甜", "菩", "烹", "掠", "婁", "啞", "做", "剳", "匐", "唹", "啀", "售", "啜", "啅", "啖", "啗", "唸", "婀", "孰", "扈", "掎", "毫", "晤", "晧", "蛄", "梠", "梏", "跂", "趺", "趾", "涸", "淌", "笘", "笞", "笳", "硅", "絅", "紿", "牾", "舸", "烱", "袞", "猗", "菫", "逞", "逧", "盒", "區", "國", "答", "湖", "落", "喜", "給", "極", "景", "結", "営", "過", "賀", "検", "減", "税", "程", "富", "割", "貴", "勤", "敬", "就", "善", "距", "尋", "塔", "幅", "絡", "惑", "喚", "喫", "硬", "掌", "超", "渦", "硝", "詔", "喪", "搭", "筒", "裕", "硫", "椅", "喉", "貼", "喩", "筈", "喬", "喰", "喧", "硯", "蛤", "揖", "葺", "智", "喋", "敦", "硲", "椋", "啣", "喙", "喀", "喊", "喟", "啻", "啾", "喘", "喞", "啼", "喃", "喇", "喨", "堙", "堝", "堡", "嵒", "愕", "敞", "蛞", "蛔", "椁", "棠", "跏", "跖", "跌", "跚", "跛", "跋", "湮", "渟", "軻", "欹", "絮", "聒", "焙", "訶", "詁", "詒", "裙", "鄂", "痞", "辜", "萼", "萵", "葆", "覘", "皓", "貂", "貽", "舒", "翕", "窖", "窘", "谺", "跎", "裎", "單", "黑", "話", "感", "漢", "福", "路", "塩", "辞", "照", "群", "損", "絹", "聖", "煙", "鉛", "詰", "遣", "跡", "嘆", "跳", "溶", "隔", "虞", "禍", "碁", "嗣", "践", "痴", "酪", "嗅", "僅", "裾", "賂", "嘩", "碍", "塙", "鉤", "瑚", "跨", "鈷", "嵩", "碓", "碇", "塘", "逼", "蓉", "碗", "蜎", "亶", "傴", "僉", "僂", "嗚", "嗇", "嗟", "嗄", "嗜", "嗤", "嗔", "蛻", "蜈", "楫", "跟", "跣", "跪", "跫", "溏", "輅", "筥", "碚", "硼", "碌", "絽", "酩", "煦", "詬", "裔", "隕", "痾", "痼", "辟", "蒿", "蒟", "畸", "貉", "稟", "禀", "衙", "碎", "圓", "當", "號", "勤", "碑", "歌", "語", "鳴", "説", "適", "銅", "閣", "誤", "磁", "箇", "豪", "摘", "滴", "踊", "碑", "酷", "塾", "嫡", "銘", "飴", "嘉", "廓", "嘘", "僑", "膏", "閤", "嘗", "厰", "裳", "碩", "蜘", "蔀", "碧", "熔", "摑", "屢", "聟", "僖", "兢", "匱", "嘔", "嗷", "嘖", "嗾", "嗽", "嘛", "嫦", "嫗", "寤", "嶇", "幗", "慥", "敲", "槁", "榕", "膈", "跼", "跿", "踉", "韶", "颱", "滾", "滬", "箚", "碪", "碣", "銛", "綺", "犒", "酲", "甄", "誥", "褓", "鄙", "殞", "蔔", "窩", "劄", "圖", "壽", "臺", "福", "嘆", "漢", "禍", "器", "賞", "確", "敵", "遺", "熟", "鋭", "影", "稿", "踏", "噴", "舗", "閲", "嘱", "賠", "褒", "潰", "憬", "駒", "踪", "嘲", "駕", "嬉", "蕎", "糊", "噛", "醇", "廠", "噌", "噂", "歎", "磐", "僻", "慾", "諒", "噓", "凜", "凛", "劈", "匳", "噎", "嘶", "嘸", "嬌", "嬋", "憚", "閭", "蝠", "蝴", "蝸", "槿", "槨", "踝", "踟", "踞", "潯", "駛", "駘", "箴", "瑾", "髫", "磑", "磋", "碾", "磅", "碼", "磊", "緘", "緝", "諄", "頡", "瞎", "鄲", "餉", "靠", "蕁", "踑", "劍", "儉", "彈", "樞", "樓", "舖", "踐", "數", "歐", "毆", "墨", "橋", "興", "操", "糖", "獣", "避", "壁", "憩", "諮", "壇", "憾", "磨", "融", "錮", "膳", "燕", "舘", "橘", "鋸", "醐", "縞", "輯", "蹄", "鮎", "噸", "噺", "蕗", "儔", "嘴", "噫", "噤", "嘯", "噬", "噪", "嚆", "嬖", "嶮", "廩", "懆", "懍", "撼", "擅", "黔", "鴣", "鮖", "暾", "閾", "霑", "檠", "蹂", "踵", "踰", "踴", "澡", "輻", "駱", "歙", "髻", "磔", "磬", "磧", "磚", "骼", "甌", "熹", "燉", "諤", "襁", "褸", "頷", "瞠", "瘻", "殫", "薔", "薜", "窶", "墻", "螗", "戰", "默", "衞", "險", "器", "燥", "嚇", "轄", "矯", "謹", "償", "礁", "鍋", "鍔", "癌", "磯", "藁", "壕", "濠", "檀", "濤", "謌", "黏", "嚀", "嚊", "嚏", "壑", "懃", "擘", "擱", "擡", "擣", "龠", "黜", "黝", "斂", "鴿", "氈", "闊", "濶", "螳", "螻", "檣", "檗", "蹊", "蹉", "蹌", "蹇", "蹐", "蹈", "臂", "臉", "牆", "馘", "歛", "雖", "簍", "磽", "磴", "鍼", "縷", "襄", "襌", "薹", "艱", "禧", "豁", "谿", "點", "禪", "營", "檢", "襃", "験", "額", "難", "臨", "騎", "繕", "礎", "癖", "顎", "璧", "鵠", "蹟", "藪", "檮", "嚢", "麿", "鎔", "簞", "蟬", "軀", "嚙", "嚠", "嚔", "黠", "鵑", "櫃", "蹙", "蹠", "蹣", "蹤", "蹕", "麌", "簣", "礒", "礑", "鎬", "繦", "甓", "謳", "謫", "襠", "鞳", "瞼", "餬", "覲", "穡", "羂", "謹", "警", "繰", "鯨", "韻", "藻", "蹴", "鹸", "鏑", "礪", "禱", "嚥", "嚮", "鶉", "蟶", "蟷", "櫚", "蹶", "蹲", "蹼", "躇", "瀛", "轎", "簽", "礙", "鏤", "艢", "譎", "襞", "羶", "羸", "疇", "蹻", "勸", "獸", "難", "競", "鰐", "灌", "礦", "嚶", "巉", "懽", "攘", "黥", "齣", "齠", "鶚", "鰔", "闡", "蘗", "躅", "躄", "躁", "鹹", "臙", "瀲", "轗", "籌", "礫", "礬", "鐓", "譬", "譟", "襭", "饉", "贏", "壥", "躃", "鼯", "壤", "黨", "獻", "嚴", "孃", "躍", "露", "儺", "囂", "嚼", "囁", "囃", "囀", "囈", "廱", "黯", "曩", "闢", "霹", "櫺", "躋", "躊", "籔", "鐺", "纈", "髏", "譴", "饋", "鐵", "權", "歡", "驅", "驚", "灘", "纒", "轡", "鑓", "鷗", "驒", "囊", "儼", "儻", "攤", "龕", "齬", "齪", "蠧", "躓", "躑", "躔", "驕", "顫", "饕", "鬻", "羇", "禳", "籡", "鑄", "穰", "鷲", "黴", "鷸", "鱚", "躙", "籥", "纔", "讌", "癰", "鱓", "巖", "罐", "驗", "鷺", "鹼", "囓", "齶", "蠹", "讙", "讒", "釀", "囑", "觀", "讓", "靈", "鑵", "躡", "鑰", "釁", "黶", "躪", "顴", "黷", "驤", "驩", "鸛", "爨"] },
		{ "question": "丨", "answers": ["中", "引", "介", "井", "升", "弔", "半", "旧", "弁", "冊", "丼", "弗", "冉", "丗", "卉", "光", "当", "共", "仲", "再", "刑", "而", "价", "并", "形", "弟", "囲", "児", "良", "判", "戒", "沖", "寿", "伴", "邦", "亜", "肖", "串", "弄", "芥", "刪", "妍", "狆", "佛", "昔", "妻", "供", "忠", "拝", "昇", "奉", "尚", "斉", "沸", "併", "奔", "其", "尭", "苒", "侖", "彿", "怫", "拌", "枡", "枅", "狒", "羌", "迚", "刱", "兩", "拂", "界", "研", "美", "面", "型", "専", "耐", "契", "削", "洪", "甚", "柵", "荊", "巷", "珊", "矧", "剃", "叛", "荆", "俤", "剏", "哄", "姜", "屏", "恍", "扁", "拱", "胖", "洸", "疥", "莽", "穽", "舁", "拜", "消", "害", "候", "差", "借", "帯", "耕", "修", "党", "恵", "剤", "峰", "娘", "畔", "浪", "陥", "恭", "宵", "俸", "倫", "凄", "唖", "晃", "哨", "屑", "悌", "套", "涛", "峯", "狼", "倆", "冓", "叟", "哢", "峭", "恙", "悄", "挈", "蚓", "蚌", "胱", "胼", "涕", "笄", "袢", "羔", "陞", "莨", "迸", "弉", "郞", "悪", "第", "械", "堂", "基", "常", "異", "済", "惜", "措", "患", "斎", "粛", "瓶", "偏", "悠", "羞", "焔", "梢", "梯", "梼", "祷", "捧", "逢", "婁", "崙", "崘", "彗", "悽", "脩", "淒", "淪", "淌", "琅", "絆", "烽", "倏", "菫", "逍", "萁", "條", "專", "朗", "開", "寒", "期", "港", "着", "散", "焼", "費", "貴", "勤", "棒", "敢", "棋", "欺", "喫", "掌", "葬", "暁", "硝", "塀", "遍", "堺", "斯", "棲", "巽", "棊", "喘", "嫂", "惴", "揣", "敞", "朞", "蛬", "棠", "跚", "湍", "湎", "湃", "絖", "絣", "猯", "睇", "畴", "賁", "稍", "惠", "搜", "黑", "義", "遣", "殿", "隔", "棄", "滞", "碁", "溝", "嗣", "僅", "塞", "羨", "蜂", "幌", "嵯", "嵳", "蛸", "瑞", "僂", "嗟", "媾", "搆", "搓", "楔", "滉", "溲", "筱", "肆", "髢", "絛", "裲", "褄", "祺", "輀", "蜋", "觥", "筲", "痹", "當", "廊", "勤", "算", "鼻", "旗", "構", "需", "端", "稲", "髪", "箕", "瑳", "爾", "嘗", "厰", "裳", "蓬", "屢", "匱", "嫦", "搴", "閧", "槎", "寨", "榔", "膈", "踉", "靤", "漾", "滌", "瑯", "髦", "髣", "綸", "熏", "誡", "誚", "褊", "遘", "趙", "禊", "厮", "髥", "綦", "齊", "稱", "滿", "賞", "選", "養", "輪", "潔", "編", "暴", "遺", "論", "輝", "儀", "噴", "穂", "鋳", "墳", "憤", "弊", "窯", "潰", "餅", "慧", "撒", "撰", "廠", "篇", "緬", "鋒", "聨", "嘶", "廝", "撕", "霄", "蝙", "蟒", "槿", "濆", "輛", "瑾", "髫", "髯", "髴", "髱", "磋", "銷", "醋", "鬧", "翩", "踑", "樣", "樓", "數", "髮", "墨", "瘦", "憲", "錯", "嬢", "縫", "儒", "壌", "融", "麺", "髭", "鞘", "澱", "冀", "嶬", "彜", "黔", "螂", "橄", "靦", "駢", "篝", "髻", "髷", "縒", "艘", "諞", "鬨", "褸", "躾", "羲", "瞠", "瞞", "瘻", "窶", "默", "講", "厳", "翼", "犠", "謹", "購", "償", "戴", "嬬", "濡", "篠", "糞", "嚊", "嬶", "孺", "懃", "懦", "龠", "鼾", "黜", "黝", "螳", "螻", "蠎", "蹉", "蹇", "臀", "濔", "篷", "簍", "縷", "謇", "襄", "瞰", "藉", "覯", "賽", "蟎", "點", "彌", "繭", "穣", "藪", "鵜", "嚢", "彝", "懣", "黠", "鮹", "魎", "櫃", "蹣", "臑", "瀁", "瀑", "騏", "簣", "鬆", "礒", "礑", "繖", "鬩", "襠", "癜", "覲", "邇", "鵥", "豐", "謹", "爆", "璽", "麒", "蟻", "禰", "簸", "曝", "鵲", "蟷", "騙", "鏤", "艤", "襦", "羹", "議", "譲", "籍", "醸", "巌", "耀", "攘", "黥", "霰", "蠕", "瀰", "騫", "繻", "癢", "糯", "饉", "壥", "壤", "黨", "獻", "鬪", "嚴", "孃", "麵", "黯", "齧", "曩", "轜", "籔", "鬘", "鐺", "髏", "譴", "饌", "饋", "纒", "鑓", "囊", "儼", "儻", "鬚", "鬻", "禳", "穰", "黴", "靨", "籥", "鬟", "顬", "巖", "囓", "蠹", "鬢", "釀", "艷", "讓", "鬣", "鑰", "黶", "鱶", "驥", "鬮", "黷", "驤"] },
		{ "question": "大", "answers": ["天", "太", "夬", "夭", "夲", "因", "夷", "尖", "夸", "戻", "汰", "妖", "沃", "呑", "吞", "夾", "参", "奇", "突", "奔", "奈", "奄", "刳", "忝", "昊", "殀", "送", "美", "奏", "咲", "契", "姻", "臭", "咽", "俣", "俠", "奕", "奐", "奎", "姨", "洟", "癸", "茵", "莽", "笑", "恩", "蚕", "涙", "朕", "俺", "皋", "套", "莫", "烟", "倚", "剞", "唳", "奚", "奘", "捩", "胯", "浹", "陜", "陝", "莢", "茣", "畚", "粏", "峽", "挾", "狹", "寄", "惨", "添", "崎", "埼", "爽", "庵", "掩", "袴", "捺", "渕", "匏", "掎", "淹", "猗", "痍", "菴", "奥", "喫", "募", "椅", "葵", "喬", "湊", "葢", "奠", "奢", "揆", "欹", "瓠", "墓", "幕", "誇", "虞", "奨", "漠", "嗅", "跨", "摸", "寞", "蜈", "楔", "筴", "綟", "獏", "飫", "畸", "罨", "奧", "溪", "関", "誤", "暮", "模", "奪", "慕", "膜", "駄", "僚", "僑", "僊", "銕", "綺", "禊", "槔", "奬", "器", "遷", "寮", "蕎", "鄭", "遼", "冪", "嬌", "撩", "蟒", "樊", "潦", "篋", "鋏", "橋", "奮", "衡", "頰", "懊", "閹", "蟇", "蟆", "澳", "輳", "燎", "躾", "篡", "療", "矯", "瞭", "簒", "蠎", "蹊", "燠", "謨", "貘", "谿", "類", "騎", "襖", "擲", "麌", "鎹", "繚", "羃", "鯵", "攀", "轎", "羹", "蹻", "類", "纂", "驀", "礬", "鐐", "鷄", "躑", "驕", "羇", "鷯", "韆", "爨"] },
		{ "question": "乂", "answers": ["文", "父", "艾", "交", "対", "吝", "効", "斉", "佼", "斧", "旻", "郊", "咬", "狡", "校", "剤", "紋", "蚊", "釜", "悋", "紊", "虔", "效", "済", "斎", "爽", "偐", "皎", "絞", "斑", "斐", "斌", "傚", "閔", "蛟", "較", "爺", "爾", "駁", "憫", "樊", "餃", "諺", "駮", "學", "鮫", "薩", "鵁", "濔", "彌", "邇", "顏", "璽", "禰", "攀", "贇", "瀰", "礬", "覺", "纐", "攪", "鷽", "鱟", "黌"] },
		{ "question": "八", "answers": ["六", "公", "父", "分", "平", "穴", "只", "叭", "交", "共", "谷", "弟", "究", "兵", "呉", "宍", "扮", "兌", "冏", "吩", "岔", "芬", "空", "具", "松", "効", "沿", "供", "突", "其", "佼", "斧", "忿", "枌", "氛", "穹", "俗", "盆", "郊", "洪", "俊", "窃", "巷", "酋", "穿", "剃", "卻", "圀", "俤", "咬", "哄", "咫", "拱", "枳", "瓰", "瓮", "狡", "盻", "竕", "穽", "突", "校", "真", "挙", "粉", "浴", "益", "容", "浜", "紛", "翁", "恭", "唆", "釜", "冥", "倶", "窄", "峻", "悌", "俱", "倥", "峪", "悛", "蚣", "涕", "浚", "郤", "窈", "衮", "眞", "效", "船", "商", "基", "貧", "異", "窓", "欲", "控", "窒", "訟", "惧", "寅", "梯", "梭", "烱", "袞", "菘", "皎", "逧", "逡", "窕", "躮", "萁", "寒", "期", "港", "尊", "棋", "欺", "絞", "雰", "裕", "猶", "腔", "斯", "竣", "巽", "硲", "棊", "傚", "奠", "敝", "黹", "朞", "蛬", "蛟", "睇", "皴", "窖", "窘", "谺", "曾", "鉛", "較", "慎", "殿", "誉", "溶", "搾", "碁", "頒", "窟", "塞", "填", "溢", "楢", "爺", "猷", "蓉", "嗔", "幎", "蛻", "椶", "溟", "裔", "頌", "隘", "遒", "祺", "與", "旗", "演", "酸", "総", "寡", "窪", "箕", "爾", "槙", "聡", "熔", "搴", "暝", "閧", "寨", "榕", "滾", "箜", "窩", "厮", "綦", "選", "暴", "遵", "窮", "幣", "弊", "窯", "蔽", "撰", "鄭", "噂", "鋲", "慾", "嘶", "廝", "廛", "撕", "膣", "瞑", "瞋", "餃", "蕕", "踑", "興", "嬢", "壌", "叡", "窺", "橘", "樽", "澱", "冀", "彜", "鴪", "螟", "駮", "縊", "諡", "鬨", "窶", "鴥", "翼", "戴", "鮫", "駿", "竃", "糞", "瞥", "輿", "壑", "黻", "鵁", "蹇", "臀", "颶", "濬", "濔", "謚", "謇", "賽", "窿", "豁", "谿", "螾", "彌", "鎮", "穣", "鵜", "嚢", "鎔", "擲", "斃", "瀑", "騏", "鬆", "鎰", "癜", "邇", "邃", "竅", "竄", "爆", "璽", "麒", "禰", "顛", "簸", "曝", "黼", "蹲", "譎", "邊", "譲", "醸", "鰌", "瀰", "騫", "竇", "竈", "鶲", "鷁", "纐", "饌", "躑", "竊", "鱒", "鷸", "鼈", "釁", "驥"] },
		{ "question": "弓", "answers": ["引", "弔", "弖", "弘", "弗", "夷", "弛", "弟", "佛", "弦", "沸", "弥", "弩", "彿", "怫", "泓", "狒", "穹", "拂", "弧", "矧", "剃", "俤", "姨", "弭", "弯", "洟", "弱", "悌", "蚓", "涕", "躬", "強", "第", "張", "梯", "弸", "痍", "費", "弾", "湾", "粥", "弼", "睇", "發", "溺", "嫋", "搦", "蒻", "漲", "銕", "窮", "潑", "撥", "髴", "彈", "廢", "彊", "襁", "癈", "繈", "彌", "鵜", "繦", "醱", "疆", "瀰", "鰯", "鶸", "彎", "鬻", "灣"] },
		{ "question": "亽", "answers": ["今", "令", "倉"] },
		{ "question": "亼", "answers": ["今", "令", "合", "冷", "伶", "命", "苓", "怜", "侖", "囹", "拾", "姶", "恰", "玲", "哈", "洽", "荅", "俞", "倉", "剣", "倹", "倫", "拿", "険", "袷", "剳", "崙", "崘", "蛉", "淪", "聆", "羚", "盒", "答", "給", "検", "塔", "搭", "愉", "蛤", "揄", "渝", "翕", "零", "鈴", "愈", "僉", "瑜", "逾", "榆", "會", "領", "閤", "箚", "綸", "瘉", "劄", "輪", "論", "匳", "蝓", "劍", "儉", "輸", "諭", "嶮", "鴒", "踰", "澪", "歙", "覦", "險", "齢", "嶺", "龠", "斂", "鴿", "臉", "歛", "鍮", "檢", "験", "鞳", "瞼", "鹸", "簽", "瀲", "齡", "龕", "籡", "籥", "驗", "鹼", "鑰"] },
		{ "question": "人", "answers": ["今", "内", "欠", "夫", "介", "仄", "失", "令", "囚", "丙", "会", "合", "次", "全", "企", "亥", "价", "谷", "冷", "余", "吹", "扶", "芥", "坐", "芙", "伶", "佚", "坎", "夾", "巫", "実", "命", "卒", "券", "舎", "欧", "炊", "奉", "迭", "於", "侠", "欣", "庚", "苓", "怜", "侖", "囹", "帙", "昃", "肭", "泅", "來", "舍", "卷", "春", "茶", "界", "拾", "巻", "姿", "奏", "狭", "俗", "珍", "柄", "峡", "挟", "茨", "姶", "臥", "恰", "玲", "俠", "卻", "俎", "哈", "咨", "洽", "炳", "衲", "陋", "疥", "殄", "荅", "臾", "俞", "病", "倉", "浴", "容", "座", "納", "剣", "倹", "栓", "泰", "秩", "俸", "倫", "拳", "挫", "恣", "脊", "桧", "倦", "疹", "秦", "閃", "倅", "峪", "拿", "蚋", "浹", "袗", "陜", "郤", "莢", "畛", "峽", "挾", "狹", "規", "険", "捨", "欲", "盗", "渓", "軟", "捲", "袷", "捧", "萊", "剳", "唹", "崙", "崘", "惓", "悴", "掀", "麸", "蛉", "趺", "淬", "淪", "淤", "欸", "欷", "聆", "瓷", "訥", "猝", "羚", "眷", "痊", "萃", "逧", "盒", "舂", "圈", "參", "麥", "從", "絵", "答", "飲", "勝", "給", "検", "棒", "幾", "圏", "替", "塔", "欺", "款", "傘", "診", "搭", "愉", "裕", "堺", "欽", "蛤", "黍", "湊", "硲", "厥", "嵌", "揄", "跌", "渝", "軫", "軼", "筌", "欹", "粢", "萸", "趁", "舒", "翕", "谺", "盜", "漢", "鉄", "幹", "資", "嘆", "溶", "零", "鈴", "羨", "詮", "禽", "椿", "愈", "蓉", "僉", "勠", "嗇", "媼", "惷", "慍", "腴", "筮", "筴", "歇", "歃", "瑜", "瘁", "蓙", "蓁", "逾", "豢", "蜹", "榆", "碎", "會", "溫", "歌", "領", "漆", "僕", "斡", "閤", "榛", "翠", "箆", "熔", "僣", "嗽", "夐", "寥", "廖", "摎", "蜷", "榕", "膃", "漱", "滲", "箚", "歉", "銓", "綣", "綸", "誣", "鞆", "瘉", "蓼", "蔘", "覡", "劄", "粹", "慘", "嘆", "漢", "輪", "賛", "論", "歓", "舗", "潜", "撲", "膝", "頬", "槻", "蕨", "歎", "慾", "麪", "匳", "慫", "戮", "黎", "麩", "蝓", "樅", "樛", "膠", "膵", "滕", "輦", "篋", "鋏", "諛", "褞", "獗", "瘟", "賚", "齒", "劍", "儉", "舖", "歐", "醉", "機", "輸", "諮", "諭", "頰", "叡", "翰", "舘", "窺", "噬", "嶮", "憖", "擒", "鴒", "麭", "閼", "樸", "踰", "澪", "澣", "輳", "歔", "歙", "璞", "縢", "薔", "薀", "覦", "臻", "墻", "縕", "險", "齢", "謄", "磯", "檎", "嶺", "黏", "壑", "龠", "齔", "斂", "鴿", "檣", "臉", "牆", "濬", "歟", "歛", "鍮", "繆", "聳", "艱", "豁", "谿", "糝", "縱", "檢", "験", "難", "藤", "謬", "鎔", "嚙", "攅", "闕", "蹤", "瓊", "醪", "鞳", "瞼", "餮", "藜", "穡", "雜", "鶏", "鹸", "麴", "鯲", "蠍", "蹶", "蹼", "瀚", "簽", "鏐", "艢", "譏", "譛", "饂", "蘊", "難", "騰", "孅", "懺", "齣", "齟", "齠", "鰆", "瀲", "韞", "齡", "麵", "儺", "囃", "齦", "齧", "鰮", "蠢", "驂", "籐", "纉", "饑", "殲", "鰧", "歡", "讃", "鰺", "灘", "懿", "攤", "龕", "齬", "齪", "籡", "黐", "籥", "籤", "鑚", "纖", "驗", "鹼", "囓", "齷", "齲", "齶", "讖", "靈", "鑰"] },
		{ "question": "兀", "answers": ["元", "先", "光", "完", "阮", "芫", "玩", "尭", "洗", "冠", "恍", "洸", "院", "莞", "晃", "胱", "浣", "冦", "寇", "焼", "暁", "筅", "絖", "皖", "堯", "微", "頑", "幌", "跣", "滉", "觥", "銑", "僥", "輝", "翫", "嶢", "撓", "澆", "蕘", "橈", "薇", "遶", "曉", "燒", "磽", "蟯", "繞", "翹", "贊", "耀", "鐃", "饒", "驍", "攢", "纘", "讚", "鑽"] },
		{ "question": "厶", "answers": ["公", "仏", "勾", "允", "云", "広", "台", "去", "弁", "払", "弘", "会", "伝", "至", "充", "牟", "芸", "私", "却", "冶", "劫", "吮", "矣", "育", "始", "参", "治", "松", "法", "拡", "到", "怯", "苔", "怡", "抬", "泓", "室", "屋", "胎", "怠", "俊", "殆", "姪", "俟", "咥", "垤", "昿", "瓮", "流", "能", "致", "倒", "翁", "唆", "挨", "桧", "砿", "峻", "套", "埃", "悛", "耘", "桙", "桎", "蚣", "浚", "紜", "畚", "盍", "衮", "晉", "強", "転", "窓", "陰", "脚", "惨", "窒", "訟", "琉", "梳", "梭", "笞", "欸", "紿", "眸", "菘", "逡", "參", "雲", "絵", "統", "握", "硫", "渥", "鈎", "蛭", "竣", "疏", "幄", "琺", "詒", "耋", "貽", "竢", "皴", "鉱", "棄", "蓋", "禽", "旒", "榁", "腟", "溘", "輊", "肆", "髢", "頌", "亂", "酸", "総", "態", "髪", "魂", "銃", "熊", "飴", "蔭", "聡", "鉾", "颱", "滲", "漓", "髦", "髣", "蔘", "髥", "慘", "臺", "徹", "撤", "罷", "璃", "膣", "駘", "髫", "髯", "髴", "髱", "蔬", "髮", "曇", "緻", "髭", "擒", "髻", "髷", "縉", "襁", "臻", "篡", "檎", "駿", "簒", "擡", "鵄", "鴾", "薹", "繈", "糝", "離", "嚔", "擺", "闔", "鬆", "繧", "藝", "鯵", "轍", "壜", "醯", "羆", "辭", "鰘", "囈", "鶲", "魑", "驂", "鬘", "鰺", "罎", "鬚", "竊", "黐", "鬟", "齷", "靆", "鬢", "靉", "籬", "鬣"] },
		{ "question": "小", "answers": ["少", "劣", "尖", "妙", "抄", "沙", "京", "歩", "叔", "弥", "毟", "杪", "炒", "県", "秒", "省", "砂", "祢", "眇", "原", "称", "捗", "紗", "俶", "勍", "娑", "莎", "寂", "淑", "渉", "涼", "戚", "雀", "掠", "淌", "菽", "景", "就", "椋", "敞", "椒", "渺", "鈔", "源", "歳", "督", "隙", "裟", "尠", "僚", "愿", "瑣", "影", "賓", "寮", "憬", "諒", "遼", "撩", "槭", "潦", "緲", "穆", "燎", "螈", "療", "頻", "瞭", "嬪", "擯", "濱", "齋", "鎖", "鯊", "檳", "蹙", "繚", "殯", "願", "鯨", "蹴", "瀕", "蘋", "黥", "鐐", "繽", "鷲", "鷯", "鬢", "顰"] },
		{ "question": "七", "answers": ["切", "宅", "托", "苆", "虎", "侘", "虐", "窃", "咤", "砌", "託", "虔", "虒", "虚", "彪", "處", "琥", "虜", "虛", "虞", "虜", "詫", "號", "嘘", "遞", "劇", "戯", "膚", "慮", "墟", "褫", "歔", "盧", "篪", "據", "罅", "遽", "虧", "戲", "濾", "廬", "鯱", "蘆", "櫨", "臚", "醵", "獻", "爐", "艫", "饕", "轤", "鑢", "鑪", "顱", "驢", "鱸"] },
		{ "question": "冂", "answers": ["内", "冊", "丙", "冉", "册", "同", "向", "両", "再", "而", "冏", "刪", "吶", "删", "尚", "岡", "苒", "侖", "肭", "罔", "兩", "南", "耐", "柄", "冒", "洞", "柵", "珊", "冑", "恫", "扁", "炳", "炯", "衲", "陋", "迥", "高", "病", "納", "胴", "剛", "倫", "桐", "倆", "冓", "蚋", "商", "偏", "庸", "冕", "崙", "崘", "惘", "曼", "淪", "淌", "絅", "烱", "訥", "満", "奥", "筒", "遍", "喬", "喘", "喃", "惴", "揣", "敞", "跚", "湍", "猯", "隔", "献", "溝", "嗣", "塙", "禽", "嵩", "瑞", "楠", "傭", "媾", "搆", "輌", "裔", "裲", "蒿", "遖", "蜹", "輀", "亂", "奧", "構", "適", "銅", "需", "端", "摘", "滴", "網", "綱", "嫡", "厭", "僑", "膏", "爾", "厰", "箆", "夐", "慵", "敲", "槁", "膈", "漓", "綸", "犒", "褊", "鞆", "遘", "髥", "稱", "滿", "輪", "敵", "編", "論", "稿", "璃", "蕎", "廠", "篇", "嬌", "蝙", "輛", "髯", "餉", "翩", "橋", "興", "鋼", "儒", "融", "橘", "縞", "嚆", "懊", "擒", "澳", "篝", "諞", "瞞", "講", "矯", "購", "檎", "藁", "嬬", "濡", "孺", "懦", "龠", "濔", "燠", "覯", "蟎", "彌", "壓", "離", "繭", "襖", "懣", "魍", "魎", "蹣", "臑", "瓊", "鎬", "謫", "邇", "麗", "璽", "禰", "鏑", "嚮", "轎", "騙", "譎", "襦", "蹻", "辭", "蠕", "瀰", "繻", "糯", "獻", "儷", "魑", "轜", "灑", "驕", "鬻", "竊", "黐", "鷸", "靨", "籥", "顬", "魘", "籬", "鑰", "釁", "黶", "驪", "爨"] },
		{ "question": "匚", "answers": ["区", "匹", "匝", "匠", "匡", "医", "匣", "欧", "殴", "枢", "柩", "匿", "匪", "框", "躯", "偃", "區", "堰", "筐", "傴", "匯", "筺", "駆", "匱", "嘔", "嫗", "嶇", "慝", "榧", "箍", "鴎", "匳", "篋", "蝘", "樞", "歐", "毆", "甌", "翳", "軀", "櫃", "謳", "醫", "驅", "鷗", "鼴"] },
		{ "question": "㐅", "answers": ["区", "刈", "凶", "気", "兇", "匈", "図", "希", "苅", "欧", "殴", "枢", "刹", "肴", "恟", "洶", "殺", "胸", "悩", "唏", "鬯", "脳", "爽", "躯", "晞", "鹵", "淆", "欷", "稀", "弑", "惱", "禽", "椶", "瑙", "蓖", "腦", "駆", "爾", "駁", "漓", "滷", "璃", "鴎", "樊", "篦", "擒", "學", "檎", "濔", "彌", "離", "鯑", "邇", "璽", "鹸", "禰", "攀", "鹹", "瀰", "礬", "覺", "魑", "竊", "攪", "黐", "鹼", "鷽", "鱟", "黌", "籬", "鹽", "鬱"] },
		{ "question": "匸", "answers": ["区", "匹", "医", "匿", "區"] },
		{ "question": "亻", "answers": ["化", "仏", "仁", "仇", "什", "仍", "仆", "仂", "仕", "他", "代", "付", "仙", "仔", "仗", "仞", "仭", "仟", "休", "仲", "伝", "仮", "件", "任", "仰", "伐", "伏", "伎", "伊", "伍", "价", "伉", "伜", "花", "何", "作", "体", "住", "位", "低", "似", "伺", "伸", "伴", "佐", "但", "伯", "佑", "伽", "佃", "伶", "佚", "估", "佝", "佗", "佇", "佞", "囮", "佛", "夜", "使", "府", "例", "価", "供", "依", "佳", "侍", "附", "侮", "併", "侃", "侠", "佼", "岱", "佶", "侈", "侏", "侘", "佻", "佩", "佰", "侑", "佯", "凭", "咐", "坿", "拊", "苻", "係", "信", "便", "保", "侵", "俗", "促", "侯", "俊", "侶", "俄", "荏", "俣", "俠", "俔", "俟", "俘", "俛", "俑", "俚", "俐", "俤", "俥", "姙", "柎", "玳", "茯", "侮", "荷", "倍", "候", "借", "個", "修", "俵", "値", "俳", "倒", "倹", "倣", "俸", "倫", "俺", "倭", "倶", "倦", "倖", "俱", "倚", "倨", "倔", "倪", "倥", "倅", "俶", "倡", "倩", "倬", "俾", "俯", "們", "倆", "恁", "烋", "莅", "宿", "貨", "健", "側", "停", "偶", "袋", "符", "偽", "偵", "偏", "悠", "偲", "椛", "偃", "偕", "偐", "偈", "偖", "偬", "偸", "做", "脩", "訛", "袱", "袵", "倏", "假", "條", "貸", "備", "偉", "傍", "雁", "筏", "傀", "傚", "傅", "堡", "腑", "葆", "働", "傷", "賃", "傾", "僧", "催", "債", "靴", "傑", "僅", "傲", "傭", "傴", "僂", "筰", "筱", "絛", "糀", "傳", "像", "腐", "閥", "僕", "僚", "僑", "僊", "僖", "僥", "僭", "僣", "僮", "滌", "褓", "蓿", "僞", "僧", "億", "儀", "褒", "鴈", "僻", "僵", "儁", "儂", "儚", "錵", "價", "儉", "儒", "儘", "黛", "鮒", "儕", "儔", "憊", "縮", "優", "償", "篠", "儡", "鮴", "膺", "應", "儲", "鞭", "贋", "儺", "儷", "儼", "儻", "鷹", "軈"] },
		{ "question": "匕", "answers": ["化", "匂", "尼", "死", "老", "旨", "此", "牝", "花", "壱", "佗", "囮", "泥", "些", "陀", "怩", "沱", "指", "屍", "柁", "姥", "呰", "昵", "卽", "能", "脂", "柴", "鬯", "耆", "耄", "眞", "貨", "掲", "喝", "渇", "蛇", "頃", "砦", "匙", "舵", "椛", "偈", "訛", "眥", "眦", "疵", "紫", "葬", "葛", "卿", "詑", "喞", "蛯", "耋", "跎", "揭", "節", "傾", "慨", "靴", "褐", "詣", "嗜", "歇", "肄", "鉈", "糀", "蓍", "貲", "觜", "態", "疑", "雌", "熊", "厩", "廐", "廏", "嘗", "碣", "竭", "謁", "罷", "稽", "漑", "鴇", "蝎", "駝", "錵", "羯", "凝", "穎", "髭", "頴", "嘴", "鴕", "曁", "薨", "擬", "嶷", "齔", "鮨", "鮱", "擺", "斃", "鞨", "礙", "藹", "羆", "癡", "鰭", "靄", "鬱"] },
		{ "question": "厂", "answers": ["反", "厄", "仄", "圧", "仮", "灰", "危", "坂", "返", "励", "阪", "扼", "阨", "岸", "板", "版", "昃", "炭", "厚", "厘", "恢", "彦", "叛", "厖", "原", "脆", "砺", "産", "販", "涯", "崖", "蛎", "崕", "偐", "啀", "軛", "厠", "飯", "備", "雁", "厨", "厥", "鈑", "厦", "源", "跪", "詭", "詼", "睚", "歴", "暦", "厭", "厩", "厰", "愿", "甅", "竰", "厮", "鴈", "蕨", "糎", "獗", "魬", "諺", "憊", "憺", "澹", "糒", "螈", "勵", "擔", "曆", "歷", "厳", "薩", "鮠", "檐", "壓", "膽", "顔", "釐", "瞻", "顏", "願", "贋", "礪", "蟾", "蹶", "瀝", "簷", "鞴", "巌", "蠣", "櫪", "譫", "糲", "贍", "壥", "嚴", "癧", "纒", "儼", "靨", "巖", "魘", "靂", "黶"] },
		{ "question": "龴", "answers": ["予", "令", "矛", "冷", "序", "伶", "抒", "茅", "苓", "怜", "囹", "杼", "勇", "柔", "玲", "俑", "矜", "通", "涌", "野", "務", "桶", "蛉", "聆", "袤", "羚", "痛", "湧", "揉", "舒", "預", "零", "鈴", "蛹", "亂", "領", "疑", "踊", "墅", "慂", "誦", "樋", "糅", "凝", "橘", "鴒", "蹂", "踴", "澪", "蕷", "豫", "齢", "擬", "嶺", "嶷", "懋", "鯒", "鞣", "霧", "礙", "譎", "癡", "辭", "鶩", "齡", "鷸"] },
		{ "question": "二", "answers": ["夫", "仁", "井", "云", "半", "失", "丼", "弍", "会", "伝", "弐", "聿", "里", "囲", "芸", "均", "判", "伴", "扶", "芙", "佚", "佞", "券", "奉", "迭", "侠", "些", "竺", "帙", "拌", "刱", "亞", "卷", "発", "建", "律", "巻", "狭", "冒", "峡", "厘", "挟", "津", "叛", "俚", "冑", "胖", "穽", "書", "耕", "畔", "埋", "秩", "逓", "俸", "拳", "桧", "倦", "哩", "浬", "狸", "冓", "耘", "紜", "袢", "黒", "野", "理", "転", "健", "規", "陰", "渓", "庸", "捲", "捧", "冕", "惓", "麸", "曼", "趺", "絆", "眷", "圈", "晝", "雲", "絵", "寒", "勝", "童", "筆", "量", "棒", "圏", "替", "廃", "溌", "裡", "葎", "跌", "軼", "鈞", "貳", "畫", "黑", "漢", "鉄", "裏", "嘆", "溝", "塞", "傭", "韵", "媾", "搆", "腱", "肄", "肆", "豢", "構", "魂", "墨", "僕", "蔭", "厭", "劃", "肇", "僣", "僮", "墅", "慵", "搴", "蜷", "寨", "綣", "甅", "遘", "竰", "髥", "嘆", "漢", "賛", "黙", "潜", "撲", "憧", "頬", "槻", "撞", "糎", "歎", "幢", "廛", "麩", "滕", "輦", "墨", "曇", "嬢", "壌", "窺", "黛", "醗", "黔", "樸", "橦", "膩", "篝", "璞", "縢", "默", "講", "購", "謄", "鍵", "瞳", "黜", "黝", "蹇", "謇", "襄", "覯", "賽", "艱", "點", "壓", "難", "糧", "藤", "穣", "嚢", "鯉", "攅", "黠", "繧", "釐", "艟", "鵥", "藝", "鶏", "壜", "蹼", "譛", "難", "鐘", "譲", "醸", "騰", "攘", "黥", "騫", "壥", "壤", "黨", "孃", "纏", "儺", "囈", "黯", "曩", "籐", "纉", "鰧", "讃", "灘", "纒", "囊", "儻", "攤", "罎", "霾", "躔", "禳", "穰", "黴", "靨", "鑚", "魘", "靆", "釀", "讓", "靉", "黶", "黷", "驤"] },
		{ "question": "十", "answers": ["支", "什", "古", "汁", "叶", "卉", "夲", "先", "早", "迅", "伎", "戎", "辻", "伜", "技", "岐", "克", "辛", "妓", "估", "孛", "忰", "瓧", "竍", "皁", "直", "苦", "協", "固", "卒", "居", "枝", "卓", "肢", "奔", "枠", "阜", "尭", "姑", "怙", "沽", "籵", "草", "計", "南", "単", "故", "洗", "枯", "盾", "卑", "砕", "勃", "胡", "哉", "剋", "真", "個", "針", "恐", "粋", "栽", "宰", "索", "皋", "隼", "訊", "翆", "倨", "倅", "倬", "俾", "凅", "悖", "罟", "翅", "章", "率", "乾", "酔", "据", "悼", "皐", "梓", "埠", "做", "啅", "婢", "悴", "掉", "蛄", "跂", "淬", "涸", "猝", "萃", "朝", "湖", "喜", "焼", "博", "裁", "弾", "暁", "傘", "循", "喪", "戟", "筑", "牌", "喃", "彭", "蛩", "棹", "脾", "筅", "絨", "詁", "覃", "辜", "賁", "單", "辞", "戦", "幹", "準", "鼓", "載", "慎", "賊", "献", "禅", "裾", "填", "瑚", "鈷", "遁", "楯", "楠", "稗", "嗔", "跣", "跫", "煢", "裨", "睥", "痺", "痼", "瘁", "辟", "遖", "罩", "滓", "碎", "適", "徳", "障", "箇", "摘", "滴", "碑", "彰", "嫡", "辣", "斡", "嘉", "槙", "翠", "銑", "僖", "兢", "嶂", "截", "綽", "褝", "槔", "粹", "敵", "潮", "噴", "墳", "憤", "嘲", "嬉", "糊", "樟", "廚", "蝉", "箪", "廟", "僻", "鴇", "劈", "嬋", "憚", "蝨", "蝴", "踞", "膵", "澎", "潭", "濆", "璋", "鞏", "瞋", "鄲", "蕈", "彈", "醉", "德", "築", "樹", "壊", "避", "壁", "膨", "懐", "錮", "翰", "鋸", "醐", "嬖", "鴣", "澣", "縡", "熹", "瘴", "殫", "薜", "薛", "辨", "戰", "聴", "繊", "戴", "嚏", "擘", "蠎", "檗", "臂", "襌", "禧", "禪", "鎮", "癖", "韓", "璧", "簞", "蟬", "嚔", "懴", "鼕", "簟", "髀", "甓", "謫", "瞽", "餬", "騨", "鏑", "顛", "鵯", "瀚", "瀛", "譚", "襞", "羸", "殱", "贊", "辭", "闡", "蘗", "蘖", "躄", "鐔", "辮", "瓣", "譬", "贏", "櫱", "躃", "闢", "霹", "籖", "鐵", "辯", "驒", "鱆", "攢", "糱", "聽", "鱚", "鱏", "鱓", "顰", "纘", "廳", "讚", "鑽"] },
		{ "question": "尸", "answers": ["尺", "尼", "尻", "尽", "局", "沢", "尾", "択", "尿", "呎", "屁", "刷", "居", "届", "屈", "泥", "怩", "屆", "昼", "屋", "屍", "咫", "屎", "屏", "昵", "展", "屑", "倨", "倔", "屓", "訳", "掘", "釈", "尉", "据", "堀", "梶", "崛", "屛", "属", "報", "握", "遅", "塀", "渥", "犀", "屡", "屠", "孱", "幄", "赧", "殿", "窟", "裾", "辟", "駅", "層", "漏", "蔚", "屢", "慰", "嘱", "履", "僻", "劈", "踞", "潺", "熨", "層", "避", "壁", "鋸", "澱", "嬖", "薜", "擘", "檗", "臀", "臂", "癖", "璧", "甓", "癜", "襞", "蘗", "躄", "譬", "躃", "闢", "霹", "屬", "齷", "屭"] },
		{ "question": "乀", "answers": ["尺", "匁", "史", "仭", "尽", "吏", "扨", "更", "沢", "択", "呎", "使", "昼", "便", "籾", "剏", "咫", "哽", "訳", "釈", "梗", "硬", "靱", "甦", "粳", "駅", "駛", "鞭"] },
		{ "question": "丩", "answers": ["収", "叫", "收", "糾", "赳"] },
		{ "question": "刂", "answers": ["刈", "刊", "刋", "列", "刑", "刔", "刎", "別", "利", "判", "苅", "刪", "删", "刷", "例", "制", "刻", "刺", "到", "刹", "冽", "刮", "刳", "前", "型", "則", "削", "荊", "剃", "荆", "俐", "剄", "剋", "剌", "洌", "俞", "剣", "剤", "倒", "烈", "剛", "剖", "剥", "剝", "捌", "剞", "剔", "悧", "莉", "側", "副", "剰", "梨", "渕", "剪", "剳", "犁", "厠", "測", "割", "創", "裂", "愉", "痢", "揃", "剴", "喇", "廁", "惻", "掣", "揄", "溂", "渝", "剩", "煎", "愈", "剿", "剽", "蜊", "瑜", "逾", "榆", "製", "罰", "劃", "箚", "瘉", "劄", "劇", "箭", "劉", "蝓", "翦", "蝲", "劍", "輸", "諭", "踰", "薊", "覦", "劑", "鍮", "鯏", "鵥"] },
		{ "question": "凵", "answers": ["凶", "屯", "兇", "匈", "艸", "沌", "邨", "画", "函", "屆", "逆", "凾", "恟", "洶", "瓲", "胸", "純", "悩", "朔", "蚩", "鬯", "芻", "脳", "歯", "鈍", "揺", "遥", "厥", "塑", "頓", "禽", "溯", "嗤", "椶", "瑶", "鄒", "飩", "蒭", "遡", "愬", "槊", "漓", "璃", "蕨", "噛", "獗", "皺", "齒", "謡", "噸", "擒", "齢", "檎", "趨", "齔", "擊", "離", "雛", "嚙", "闕", "繫", "蹶", "齣", "齟", "齠", "櫱", "齡", "齦", "齧", "魑", "齬", "齪", "糱", "黐", "囓", "齷", "齲", "齶", "籬", "鬱"] },
		{ "question": "彑", "answers": ["互", "冱", "沍", "剝", "彙", "碌", "祿", "綠", "彜", "錄", "彝", "籙"] },
		{ "question": "幺", "answers": ["幻", "幼", "玄", "弦", "呟", "拗", "後", "幽", "胤", "茲", "畜", "奚", "眩", "痃", "窈", "率", "舷", "牽", "絃", "衒", "幾", "滋", "孳", "孶", "蓄", "慈", "鉉", "溪", "磁", "麼", "酳", "畿", "聨", "樂", "機", "磯", "聯", "黝", "蹊", "隰", "谿", "濕", "擽", "藥", "櫟", "爍", "譏", "關", "礫", "饑", "鷄", "轢", "鑠", "顯"] },
		{ "question": "子", "answers": ["孔", "仔", "孕", "字", "好", "存", "孝", "孜", "李", "吼", "孚", "孛", "学", "季", "乳", "享", "孟", "孥", "厚", "孤", "勃", "俘", "孩", "孫", "浮", "哮", "悖", "郛", "教", "猛", "郭", "惇", "淳", "孰", "悸", "桴", "殍", "菰", "敦", "孳", "孱", "椁", "孶", "蜉", "艀", "酵", "塾", "遜", "廓", "孵", "熟", "醇", "槨", "潺", "諄", "暾", "燉", "學", "孺", "鶉", "鐓"] },
		{ "question": "乚", "answers": ["孔", "屯", "尤", "扎", "礼", "札", "叱", "乱", "沈", "沌", "吼", "尨", "忱", "糺", "邨", "乳", "枕", "奄", "肬", "軋", "拋", "胤", "厖", "瓲", "眈", "疣", "純", "竜", "俺", "耽", "亀", "庵", "掩", "淹", "紮", "酖", "菴", "就", "鈍", "電", "滝", "頓", "飩", "罨", "亂", "輒", "縄", "稽", "蝿", "鴆", "穐", "噸", "篭", "閹", "竃", "蹴", "鷲"] },
		{ "question": "冖", "answers": ["冗", "写", "売", "労", "壱", "沈", "孛", "忱", "罕", "学", "受", "枕", "帚", "栄", "軍", "侵", "冠", "帝", "亭", "勃", "亮", "眈", "帰", "帯", "党", "浸", "索", "冥", "耽", "涜", "冤", "冢", "悖", "旁", "冦", "深", "停", "堂", "授", "常", "婦", "探", "掃", "殻", "蛍", "牽", "壷", "毫", "酖", "帶", "運", "覚", "営", "揮", "畳", "傍", "掌", "塚", "壺", "啻", "啼", "喨", "戞", "棠", "渾", "渟", "葷", "蒂", "勞", "壹", "殼", "愛", "続", "夢", "寝", "滞", "彙", "舜", "蒙", "塋", "壼", "幎", "暈", "暉", "滂", "溟", "煢", "蒡", "當", "読", "穀", "豪", "綬", "嘗", "裳", "嫦", "愨", "暝", "榜", "膀", "箒", "犖", "褌", "皹", "皸", "榮", "寢", "臺", "賞", "確", "輝", "締", "撹", "儚", "冪", "噎", "撈", "鴆", "瑩", "磅", "甍", "瞑", "穀", "諦", "叡", "鴬", "蹄", "螟", "濛", "諢", "瞠", "殪", "蕣", "薨", "螢", "學", "償", "曖", "壕", "濠", "嚏", "壑", "擡", "朦", "曚", "螳", "檬", "濬", "轂", "駸", "謗", "癆", "薹", "營", "瞬", "嚢", "嚔", "礑", "襠", "矇", "歸", "蟷", "艨", "鶤", "蠑", "黨", "覺", "鶴", "鶯", "鐺", "饐", "囊", "儻", "懿", "蠧", "疊", "攪", "鷽", "蠹", "鱟", "黌", "靉", "釁", "鬱", "爨"] },
		{ "question": "之", "answers": ["乏", "芝", "泛", "貶"] },
		{ "question": "廾", "answers": ["升", "弁", "卉", "刑", "并", "形", "戒", "弄", "妍", "昇", "併", "奔", "枡", "枅", "研", "型", "荊", "荆", "剏", "屏", "莽", "舁", "哢", "胼", "笄", "陞", "迸", "弉", "械", "瓶", "開", "葬", "塀", "絣", "算", "鼻", "誡", "弊", "餅", "聨", "蟒", "彜", "駢", "嚊", "嬶", "鼾", "蠎", "彝"] },
		{ "question": "㔾", "answers": ["厄", "犯", "氾", "卮", "危", "扼", "阨", "宛", "苑", "范", "卷", "怨", "倦", "脆", "盌", "捲", "婉", "惓", "軛", "笵", "圈", "腕", "椀", "碗", "跪", "詭", "僊", "蜿", "蜷", "綣", "範", "遷", "豌", "鴛", "鋺", "鮠", "韆"] },
		{ "question": "士", "answers": ["壬", "仕", "任", "吉", "壮", "声", "売", "志", "壱", "呈", "廷", "妊", "壯", "佶", "凭", "劼", "荘", "荏", "姙", "拮", "衽", "庭", "桔", "挺", "涜", "奘", "恁", "弉", "莊", "殻", "淫", "壷", "婬", "敖", "梃", "袵", "結", "装", "款", "壺", "痣", "壹", "殼", "続", "聖", "賃", "詰", "艇", "壼", "蜓", "裝", "読", "穀", "誌", "愨", "壽", "臺", "澂", "噎", "霆", "頡", "賣", "穀", "徵", "隷", "儔", "髻", "殪", "濤", "擡", "擣", "轂", "薹", "檮", "瀆", "黠", "禱", "霪", "犢", "牘", "疇", "懲", "籌", "襭", "竇", "躊", "纈", "饐", "續", "懿", "蠧", "覿", "贖", "鑄", "聽", "讀", "黷"] },
		{ "question": "尢", "answers": ["尤", "尨", "肬", "拋", "厖", "疣", "就", "稽", "蹴", "鷲"] },
		{ "question": "巾", "answers": ["帀", "市", "布", "匝", "凧", "帆", "吊", "沛", "姉", "刷", "制", "帖", "佩", "帚", "帙", "帑", "帛", "肺", "帝", "帥", "柿", "帰", "席", "帯", "師", "逓", "旆", "珮", "帳", "常", "婦", "掃", "帷", "帶", "幅", "帽", "棉", "啻", "啼", "幄", "幃", "幀", "幇", "掣", "敝", "黹", "蒂", "幕", "飾", "滞", "幌", "獅", "幎", "閙", "蓆", "製", "綿", "嫦", "幗", "幔", "箍", "箒", "締", "幣", "弊", "蔽", "幡", "冪", "幟", "幢", "霈", "鬧", "魳", "錦", "諦", "蹄", "篩", "衞", "瞥", "黻", "幫", "斃", "羃", "歸", "黼", "鰤", "鼈"] },
		{ "question": "弋", "answers": ["弌", "代", "弍", "式", "弐", "杙", "武", "岱", "拭", "玳", "袋", "貸", "斌", "弑", "貳", "試", "軾", "鳶", "賦", "黛", "膩", "錻", "鵡", "贇"] },
		{ "question": "乃", "answers": ["仍", "孕", "朶", "秀", "盈", "透", "莠", "携", "楹", "綉", "躱", "誘", "銹"] },
		{ "question": "卜", "answers": ["仆", "外", "占", "朴", "抃", "店", "卓", "虎", "卦", "帖", "苫", "咎", "拈", "沾", "点", "虐", "赴", "貞", "訃", "砧", "倬", "站", "虔", "冦", "虒", "掛", "虚", "粘", "偵", "悼", "彪", "啅", "寇", "掉", "鹵", "笘", "處", "敍", "貼", "幀", "棹", "琥", "覘", "虜", "虛", "虞", "虜", "罫", "禎", "褂", "粲", "遉", "罩", "號", "嘘", "敲", "滷", "綽", "遞", "禎", "劇", "戯", "膚", "慮", "墟", "褫", "叡", "餐", "鮎", "霑", "歔", "盧", "赬", "篪", "據", "燦", "黏", "壑", "罅", "濬", "遽", "虧", "點", "戲", "濾", "鹸", "廬", "鯱", "蘆", "櫨", "鹹", "臚", "醵", "獻", "爐", "艫", "饕", "竊", "轤", "鑢", "鹼", "鑪", "顱", "鹽", "驢", "鱸"] },
		{ "question": "力", "answers": ["仂", "加", "功", "幼", "劣", "肋", "朸", "男", "助", "努", "労", "励", "伽", "劫", "劬", "劭", "抛", "協", "効", "劾", "茄", "劼", "拗", "拋", "勇", "架", "勅", "勃", "迦", "勁", "恊", "枷", "珈", "勉", "勉", "脅", "脇", "捌", "勍", "痂", "窈", "動", "務", "勘", "袈", "勗", "笳", "勒", "勖", "勝", "賀", "筋", "勤", "募", "湧", "甥", "跏", "勞", "虜", "働", "勢", "勧", "虜", "勣", "勦", "飭", "勠", "耡", "舅", "勤", "嘉", "慟", "勲", "駕", "鋤", "撈", "踴", "勳", "勵", "嬲", "懃", "黝", "癆", "霧", "勸"] },
		{ "question": "川", "answers": ["卅", "侃", "荒", "流", "訓", "釧", "琉", "梳", "順", "慌", "硫", "疏", "滞", "馴", "旒", "蔬", "醯"] },
		{ "question": "扌", "answers": ["扎", "打", "払", "扱", "托", "扞", "扛", "扣", "扠", "扨", "投", "折", "技", "批", "抗", "抜", "択", "抑", "抄", "把", "扶", "扮", "扼", "抉", "找", "抒", "抓", "抖", "抃", "抔", "抛", "招", "拡", "担", "拝", "押", "拠", "拓", "抵", "拍", "抱", "拘", "抽", "拐", "拒", "拙", "披", "抹", "拉", "拗", "拑", "抻", "拆", "拈", "拌", "拊", "拇", "抬", "拋", "拔", "拂", "指", "持", "拾", "括", "挟", "拷", "挑", "拶", "拭", "按", "挌", "拮", "拱", "挂", "拯", "拵", "振", "捕", "哲", "逝", "捜", "挿", "挨", "挫", "捉", "捗", "挺", "捌", "挽", "捐", "捍", "捏", "捩", "浙", "挾", "採", "授", "接", "捨", "推", "探", "掘", "描", "掛", "掲", "控", "措", "掃", "排", "据", "捻", "掩", "掴", "掬", "捲", "捷", "掻", "捺", "捧", "掠", "掖", "掎", "掀", "掫", "捶", "掏", "掉", "掟", "捫", "晢", "晣", "捓", "提", "揮", "握", "援", "換", "揚", "揺", "搭", "揖", "揃", "掾", "揩", "揀", "揆", "揣", "揉", "揶", "揄", "搜", "插", "揭", "損", "搬", "携", "搾", "摂", "摸", "搔", "搆", "搦", "搶", "搓", "搗", "搏", "搨", "搖", "摘", "誓", "摺", "摑", "摶", "摧", "摎", "箍", "箝", "撮", "撤", "撲", "撹", "撒", "撰", "撞", "撚", "播", "撫", "撓", "撥", "撕", "撩", "撈", "操", "擁", "擒", "撼", "擅", "撻", "擂", "據", "擇", "擔", "擦", "擬", "擢", "擱", "擠", "擡", "擣", "擯", "擾", "擲", "擺", "擽", "攅", "擴", "籀", "攘", "籒", "攝", "攤", "攢", "籡", "攪", "攫", "攬"] },
		{ "question": "王", "answers": ["玉", "主", "全", "匡", "住", "狂", "呈", "弄", "玖", "汪", "国", "注", "往", "宝", "旺", "玩", "枉", "玫", "柱", "皇", "珍", "珂", "珊", "玲", "珈", "珀", "玻", "玳", "班", "珠", "栓", "珪", "哢", "框", "珮", "珥", "珞", "郢", "理", "球", "望", "現", "凰", "掴", "琢", "琉", "琅", "痊", "逞", "程", "琴", "斑", "瑛", "閏", "註", "琶", "琵", "琳", "徨", "惶", "筌", "筐", "琥", "琲", "琺", "隍", "裎", "琢", "聖", "詮", "瑚", "瑞", "筺", "瑟", "瑙", "瑁", "瑕", "瑜", "瑶", "煌", "遑", "瑇", "徴", "瑠", "瑳", "碧", "瑯", "瑣", "瑪", "瑰", "銓", "酲", "誑", "瑤", "潤", "駐", "璃", "澂", "蝗", "篁", "瑩", "璋", "瑾", "鬧", "璇", "璢", "麈", "璞", "鬨", "環", "鍠", "懲", "璧", "瓊", "鬩", "璽", "蟶", "鰉", "瓏", "寶", "鬪", "瓔", "鐵", "聽", "廳", "鬮"] },
		{ "question": "工", "answers": ["左", "功", "巧", "式", "江", "扛", "攻", "杢", "巫", "杠", "肛", "汞", "空", "矼", "紅", "拭", "虹", "剄", "勁", "缸", "差", "恐", "貢", "倥", "訌", "徑", "莖", "控", "脛", "逕", "項", "尋", "腔", "筑", "弑", "蛩", "痙", "試", "嵯", "嵳", "嗟", "搓", "跫", "軾", "筮", "經", "瑳", "槓", "槎", "箜", "熕", "誣", "覡", "輕", "壽", "潯", "磋", "鞏", "蕁", "築", "頸", "儔", "噬", "縒", "鴻", "濤", "擣", "蹉", "燬", "隱", "檮", "禱", "疇", "穩", "籌", "躊", "鑄", "靈"] },
		{ "question": "囗", "answers": ["四", "囚", "回", "因", "団", "図", "囲", "困", "囮", "国", "固", "囹", "泗", "泅", "面", "姻", "咽", "廻", "圀", "囿", "徊", "茴", "茵", "恩", "個", "圃", "烟", "凅", "圄", "悃", "迴", "菌", "掴", "梱", "圉", "鹵", "涸", "悤", "圈", "國", "圏", "蛔", "湎", "粤", "圍", "惱", "園", "亶", "嗇", "媼", "慍", "溷", "瑙", "痼", "蓖", "稟", "禀", "圓", "腦", "溫", "箇", "摑", "幗", "膃", "靤", "滷", "箘", "鄙", "圖", "團", "緬", "凜", "凛", "駟", "褞", "瘟", "壇", "錮", "麺", "薗", "篦", "圜", "廩", "懍", "擅", "靦", "薔", "薀", "墻", "縕", "檀", "氈", "檣", "牆", "總", "聰", "穡", "鹸", "麕", "艢", "羶", "饂", "蘊", "鹹", "韞", "麵", "鰮", "顫", "竊", "靨", "鹼", "鹽"] },
		{ "question": "止", "answers": ["正", "疋", "企", "此", "凪", "足", "址", "沚", "阯", "步", "歩", "武", "延", "征", "祉", "肯", "些", "政", "卸", "柾", "歪", "呰", "祉", "症", "捗", "柴", "涎", "莚", "渋", "渉", "砦", "徙", "趾", "焉", "眥", "眦", "疵", "歯", "証", "紫", "斌", "歳", "鉦", "堽", "蜒", "蜑", "筵", "貲", "觜", "歴", "雌", "誕", "賦", "噛", "蕋", "齒", "澁", "整", "髭", "嘴", "錻", "歷", "齢", "頻", "齔", "嚙", "歸", "瀕", "鵡", "瀝", "蘋", "贇", "齣", "齟", "齠", "櫪", "齡", "齦", "齧", "癧", "齬", "齪", "囓", "齷", "齲", "齶", "靂", "顰"] },
		{ "question": "丆", "answers": ["石", "岩", "拓", "妬", "宕", "矼", "研", "砂", "砕", "柘", "斫", "砒", "砌", "差", "破", "砲", "砿", "砥", "砧", "砺", "砠", "砦", "硅", "着", "備", "硬", "硝", "硫", "硯", "硲", "跖", "碁", "碍", "嵯", "嵳", "碓", "碇", "碗", "嗟", "搓", "碚", "硼", "碌", "碎", "碑", "磁", "碑", "瑳", "碩", "碧", "槎", "碪", "碣", "確", "磐", "磑", "磋", "碾", "磅", "碼", "磊", "磨", "鮖", "磔", "磬", "磧", "磚", "縒", "糒", "礁", "磯", "蹉", "磽", "磴", "礎", "礒", "礑", "礪", "礙", "鞴", "礦", "礫", "礬", "蠧", "蠹"] },
		{ "question": "木", "answers": ["本", "札", "末", "未", "休", "机", "朽", "朴", "凩", "朸", "朶", "村", "体", "材", "条", "困", "床", "杉", "杏", "杓", "杖", "杜", "宋", "呆", "杢", "李", "杙", "杣", "杠", "杞", "杆", "沐", "林", "妹", "板", "味", "果", "松", "枝", "述", "枚", "杯", "枢", "析", "抹", "枠", "采", "刹", "枕", "杭", "杵", "杷", "枇", "沫", "杲", "杳", "枌", "枉", "枋", "枡", "杪", "杼", "枅", "牀", "茉", "來", "茶", "相", "柱", "栄", "査", "保", "染", "枯", "柔", "柄", "架", "某", "柳", "柿", "柵", "栃", "昧", "柑", "柘", "柊", "柁", "栂", "柏", "柾", "柚", "枴", "柯", "枷", "柤", "柞", "柩", "柮", "枳", "柢", "柎", "柝", "枹", "枸", "校", "根", "案", "殺", "梅", "桜", "格", "耕", "株", "桃", "桑", "核", "栽", "桟", "栓", "耗", "桁", "桧", "桓", "桔", "桂", "柴", "栖", "栴", "桐", "栗", "悃", "耙", "耘", "栩", "栞", "桙", "框", "桎", "栲", "栫", "烋", "眛", "秣", "深", "械", "菜", "巣", "採", "術", "探", "菓", "彩", "麻", "梗", "梨", "梧", "梱", "梓", "梢", "梯", "桶", "梼", "梶", "彬", "椛", "梁", "淋", "埜", "萊", "婪", "耜", "桿", "桝", "桀", "梳", "桷", "梭", "梔", "梵", "桴", "梟", "梠", "梺", "梏", "梛", "梃", "淅", "笨", "紮", "菘", "麥", "條", "梅", "巢", "森", "集", "植", "葉", "極", "検", "棒", "棋", "棺", "閑", "棚", "棟", "媒", "椅", "椎", "渠", "湘", "椙", "棲", "喋", "焚", "棉", "椋", "琳", "椀", "棊", "堡", "寐", "廂", "弑", "揉", "晰", "椏", "椁", "棠", "椈", "椄", "棕", "椒", "椚", "棍", "棹", "棣", "渣", "渫", "葆", "晳", "棧", "楽", "新", "業", "想", "禁", "棄", "裸", "楼", "傑", "鉢", "彙", "楷", "慄", "楢", "楯", "牒", "楚", "楕", "椴", "椿", "楠", "楳", "煤", "楓", "楊", "剿", "勦", "耡", "椶", "楹", "椰", "楸", "楫", "楮", "椽", "楾", "榁", "楔", "楡", "楝", "椹", "楞", "誄", "躱", "痳", "皙", "罧", "榆", "様", "歴", "構", "雑", "模", "暦", "概", "漆", "榎", "樺", "榊", "榛", "槙", "槍", "槌", "嘛", "夥", "麼", "蜥", "槓", "槁", "槎", "榻", "寨", "槐", "榧", "榾", "榴", "榑", "榜", "槊", "榕", "榔", "槃", "榱", "滌", "綵", "裹", "褓", "靺", "槔", "槇", "榮", "横", "箱", "課", "標", "権", "魅", "槽", "褒", "摩", "膝", "槻", "樟", "樗", "蝶", "樋", "麪", "嫻", "麾", "麩", "槹", "槲", "槭", "樊", "槧", "槿", "樅", "樛", "樔", "樒", "槨", "踝", "潸", "緤", "醂", "糅", "賚", "耦", "樂", "樞", "樣", "樓", "親", "橋", "機", "築", "樹", "操", "薪", "謀", "磨", "樫", "橘", "樵", "橡", "樽", "橢", "諜", "噺", "噤", "噪", "憖", "懆", "耨", "麭", "霖", "橄", "橙", "樸", "橇", "橦", "橈", "檠", "蹂", "澡", "篥", "磔", "鮇", "橫", "燥", "霜", "檜", "橿", "檎", "藁", "篠", "檀", "襍", "懋", "鮴", "檣", "檐", "檄", "檗", "檬", "檪", "簗", "縻", "顆", "糜", "藉", "檢", "襃", "隸", "礎", "襟", "檮", "麿", "擽", "櫁", "檸", "櫃", "櫂", "檳", "鬆", "釐", "鞣", "藕", "雜", "藥", "繰", "藻", "麓", "櫛", "蘂", "櫓", "麴", "攀", "櫟", "檻", "櫚", "爍", "靡", "欄", "籍", "孀", "鰈", "蠑", "蘗", "櫨", "櫪", "蘖", "躁", "礫", "礬", "譟", "櫱", "麵", "魔", "囃", "欅", "櫺", "襯", "櫻", "權", "欄", "轢", "欒", "鑠", "欖", "鬱", "爨"] },
		{ "question": "夕", "answers": ["外", "名", "多", "死", "列", "夙", "汐", "舛", "例", "宛", "苑", "侈", "冽", "歿", "殀", "怨", "拶", "屍", "殆", "洌", "殃", "殄", "茗", "残", "烈", "殊", "殉", "盌", "移", "婉", "桝", "桀", "殍", "麥", "殖", "腕", "葬", "裂", "椀", "殘", "夢", "傑", "舜", "碗", "酩", "粲", "銘", "夥", "蜿", "殞", "舞", "儚", "殤", "豌", "隣", "鴛", "餐", "憐", "磔", "鋺", "殫", "殪", "蕣", "薨", "薤", "鄰", "燦", "燐", "瞬", "斃", "餮", "殯", "殱", "殲", "驎", "鱗", "麟"] },
		{ "question": "广", "answers": ["広", "庁", "庄", "応", "序", "床", "庇", "店", "底", "府", "拡", "庚", "庖", "度", "庠", "昿", "庫", "庭", "席", "座", "唐", "砿", "俯", "康", "符", "庶", "麻", "庸", "鹿", "庵", "渡", "廊", "粧", "廃", "廁", "廂", "腑", "鉱", "廉", "塘", "傭", "廈", "溏", "痳", "蓙", "蓆", "廊", "腐", "遮", "廓", "廐", "廏", "嘛", "麼", "廖", "慷", "慵", "蔗", "慶", "摩", "廠", "廚", "廟", "廝", "廛", "廡", "麾", "廣", "廢", "糖", "磨", "廨", "廩", "螗", "糠", "鍍", "膺", "縻", "糜", "應", "麿", "壙", "蹠", "擴", "簾", "廬", "曠", "靡", "龐", "蠊", "礦", "魔", "纏", "廱", "纊", "鷓", "鱇", "躔", "鑛", "鷹", "軈", "廳"] },
		{ "question": "夂", "answers": ["冬", "処", "各", "麦", "条", "拠", "咎", "苳", "後", "客", "変", "俊", "柊", "洛", "恪", "挌", "狢", "夏", "格", "降", "峰", "唆", "峻", "峯", "凌", "悛", "浚", "珞", "烙", "疼", "終", "務", "略", "隆", "陵", "逢", "菱", "崚", "麸", "梭", "脩", "烽", "倏", "逡", "麥", "處", "條", "落", "絡", "竣", "喀", "絳", "皴", "厦", "路", "愛", "酪", "蜂", "賂", "稜", "嗄", "廈", "椶", "輅", "絛", "貉", "酸", "閣", "榎", "蓬", "綾", "夐", "滌", "憂", "慶", "麹", "鋒", "麪", "麩", "稷", "禝", "縫", "麺", "蕗", "鮗", "麭", "駱", "骼", "薐", "優", "曖", "駿", "篠", "擱", "螽", "篷", "謖", "窿", "額", "擾", "鼕", "瓊", "霧", "麴", "麵", "露", "鷺", "靉"] },
		{ "question": "⺀", "answers": ["冬", "苳", "柊", "疼", "終", "寒", "鮗", "螽", "鼕"] },
		{ "question": "丷", "answers": ["半", "平", "光", "当", "并", "判", "伴", "肖", "券", "並", "尚", "坪", "併", "岡", "侠", "怦", "拌", "羌", "苹", "罔", "卷", "首", "前", "南", "送", "美", "逆", "巻", "狭", "咲", "峡", "削", "帝", "挟", "彦", "酋", "叛", "剏", "姜", "屏", "恍", "胖", "洸", "消", "差", "益", "従", "党", "悦", "畔", "剛", "宵", "朕", "釜", "拳", "倦", "晃", "朔", "哨", "秤", "屑", "峭", "恙", "悄", "旁", "胱", "胼", "袢", "羔", "迸", "商", "産", "堂", "常", "脱", "瓶", "羞", "曽", "捲", "梢", "渕", "偐", "剪", "惓", "惘", "馗", "淌", "絆", "眷", "萍", "逍", "圈", "道", "勝", "着", "隊", "税", "評", "善", "圏", "普", "傍", "掌", "遂", "滋", "硝", "塀", "揃", "厥", "啻", "啼", "喃", "孳", "敞", "棠", "絖", "絣", "蒂", "稍", "曾", "黑", "業", "義", "僧", "慈", "献", "禅", "塑", "煎", "羨", "溢", "幌", "嵯", "嵳", "蛸", "楠", "溯", "嗟", "搓", "滉", "滂", "隘", "蒡", "遖", "豢", "觥", "筲", "當", "様", "関", "説", "増", "適", "磁", "層", "摘", "滴", "網", "綱", "憎", "嫡", "僕", "僚", "遡", "瑳", "嘗", "厰", "裳", "嫦", "愬", "蜷", "槎", "榜", "槊", "膀", "漾", "綣", "熏", "誚", "趙", "對", "賞", "養", "敵", "導", "鋭", "輝", "儀", "閲", "墜", "締", "撲", "窯", "寮", "餅", "頬", "毅", "蕨", "廠", "箭", "蝉", "箪", "遼", "撩", "霄", "滕", "潦", "磋", "磅", "銷", "獗", "翦", "樣", "墨", "鋼", "縦", "膳", "諦", "諺", "鞘", "蹄", "嶬", "黔", "鮃", "樸", "駢", "璞", "縊", "縢", "縒", "燎", "躾", "羲", "瞠", "隧", "默", "療", "犠", "償", "謄", "瞭", "黜", "黝", "螳", "蹉", "馘", "燧", "謚", "謗", "點", "顔", "贈", "繕", "藤", "叢", "黠", "鮹", "魍", "闕", "瀁", "礒", "礑", "鎰", "鎹", "繚", "謫", "襠", "邃", "鵥", "譜", "蟻", "鏑", "蟷", "蹶", "蹼", "艤", "羹", "議", "騰", "耀", "黥", "鐐", "癢", "壥", "黨", "黯", "籐", "鐺", "鰧", "纒", "儻", "黴", "鷯", "黶", "鱶", "黷", "鑿"] },
		{ "question": "土", "answers": ["去", "圧", "圦", "寺", "地", "在", "至", "吐", "圭", "庄", "社", "走", "坂", "告", "均", "却", "坊", "坑", "劫", "坐", "杜", "牡", "坎", "圻", "址", "坏", "肚", "径", "周", "法", "舎", "到", "佳", "怪", "侍", "茎", "坪", "卦", "怯", "坤", "坦", "坩", "坡", "坿", "屆", "社", "室", "屋", "持", "待", "型", "城", "赴", "封", "垣", "娃", "垢", "姪", "哇", "咥", "垓", "垠", "垤", "奎", "峙", "恃", "挂", "時", "起", "徒", "特", "造", "座", "陛", "致", "倒", "埋", "挫", "桂", "珪", "浩", "凌", "埃", "埆", "埒", "恚", "捏", "桎", "涅", "陞", "盍", "赳", "堂", "陸", "基", "経", "域", "捨", "脚", "掛", "窒", "陵", "涯", "培", "堀", "崖", "埼", "堆", "畦", "痔", "埴", "埠", "菱", "埜", "崕", "啀", "堊", "堋", "崚", "敖", "晧", "梏", "硅", "袿", "畤", "埳", "場", "軽", "等", "街", "達", "握", "越", "堅", "堤", "塔", "超", "堪", "粧", "堕", "塚", "塀", "塁", "蛙", "渥", "堰", "堺", "蛭", "堵", "堙", "堝", "堡", "幄", "幇", "湮", "琺", "皓", "耋", "逵", "趁", "窖", "堯", "壻", "詩", "塩", "勢", "墓", "煙", "塊", "塗", "塑", "蓋", "毀", "傲", "塞", "填", "睦", "塡", "塙", "罫", "蒔", "塘", "稜", "堽", "嗇", "塋", "塒", "榁", "腟", "溘", "輊", "褂", "睚", "蓙", "境", "増", "墨", "酷", "塾", "窪", "頚", "塵", "綾", "僥", "嗷", "塹", "墅", "慥", "閨", "跿", "甄", "誥", "趙", "對", "臺", "熱", "趣", "舗", "墜", "墳", "墟", "嶢", "廛", "慳", "撓", "膣", "澆", "熬", "鞋", "靠", "蕘", "遨", "墮", "墨", "增", "壊", "壁", "墾", "壇", "壌", "緻", "樫", "壅", "撻", "橈", "瞠", "薔", "薐", "遶", "臻", "墻", "曉", "燒", "鮭", "壕", "趨", "竃", "壑", "擡", "鵄", "螳", "螯", "檣", "牆", "磽", "燵", "燬", "褻", "薹", "幫", "壓", "鵠", "壙", "闔", "蟯", "繞", "贅", "穡", "翹", "藝", "壘", "壜", "壟", "艢", "疆", "壞", "鏗", "鐃", "壥", "鰘", "壤", "竈", "纏", "囈", "闥", "饒", "韃", "纒", "躔", "驍", "鰹", "齷", "鼇"] },
		{ "question": "丂", "answers": ["号", "巧", "考", "朽", "夸", "函", "亟", "刳", "拷", "咢", "盻", "娉", "栲", "胯", "袴", "匏", "極", "愕", "瓠", "鄂", "粤", "萼", "誇", "跨", "聘", "號", "樗", "諤", "諡", "羲", "鍔", "騁", "虧", "顎", "鰐", "鶚", "饕", "齶"] },
		{ "question": "也", "answers": ["他", "池", "地", "弛", "馳", "髢"] },
		{ "question": "丁", "answers": ["打", "可", "庁", "汀", "叮", "行", "灯", "町", "何", "佇", "疔", "河", "奇", "苛", "阿", "苧", "呵", "訂", "亭", "珂", "柯", "酊", "衍", "荷", "桁", "釘", "倚", "剞", "哥", "竚", "停", "寄", "術", "頂", "崎", "埼", "婀", "掎", "紵", "舸", "裄", "猗", "衒", "街", "貯", "椅", "渟", "軻", "欹", "絎", "訶", "愆", "痾", "畸", "衙", "歌", "寧", "銜", "綺", "衝", "衛", "衡", "衞", "謌", "嚀", "鵆", "濘", "獰", "騎", "檸", "羇", "衢"] },
		{ "question": "干", "answers": ["平", "刊", "汗", "奸", "幵", "扞", "形", "肝", "旱", "杆", "罕", "岸", "坪", "怦", "枅", "苹", "南", "竿", "姸", "軒", "釜", "秤", "悍", "捍", "栞", "訐", "桿", "萍", "開", "評", "揺", "遥", "喃", "稈", "筓", "幹", "献", "楠", "瑶", "骭", "遖", "謡", "鮃", "澣", "鼾", "駻", "叢", "鑿"] },
		{ "question": "礻", "answers": ["礼", "社", "祈", "祉", "祁", "祀", "神", "祝", "祖", "祇", "祢", "祐", "祥", "祗", "祠", "祚", "祓", "祕", "視", "祷", "禄", "福", "禍", "禅", "禎", "祺", "祿", "榊", "禊", "禝", "禧", "禪", "禮", "禰", "鰰", "禳"] },
		{ "question": "夫", "answers": ["失", "扶", "芙", "佚", "迭", "帙", "秩", "規", "渓", "麸", "趺", "替", "跌", "軼", "漢", "鉄", "嘆", "僕", "僣", "嘆", "漢", "賛", "潜", "撲", "槻", "歎", "麩", "輦", "窺", "樸", "璞", "艱", "難", "攅", "鶏", "蹼", "譛", "難", "儺", "纉", "讃", "灘", "攤", "鑚"] },
		{ "question": "心", "answers": ["必", "応", "志", "忘", "忌", "忍", "芯", "沁", "念", "忠", "泌", "忽", "忿", "思", "急", "怒", "怠", "怨", "怎", "怱", "息", "恩", "秘", "恐", "恵", "恥", "恋", "恣", "恕", "恚", "恁", "恙", "荵", "祕", "悪", "窓", "密", "患", "悠", "捻", "惚", "偲", "悉", "偬", "唸", "悤", "悲", "惑", "惹", "惣", "葱", "悶", "痣", "惠", "惡", "意", "感", "想", "愛", "愚", "慈", "愁", "稔", "愈", "愆", "惷", "愍", "腮", "瑟", "綛", "総", "態", "徳", "誌", "認", "隠", "寧", "蜜", "聡", "慇", "愨", "愿", "愬", "慂", "慝", "熄", "億", "慮", "慰", "穂", "慶", "慧", "蕊", "慾", "慙", "慫", "樒", "熨", "德", "憲", "憶", "穏", "憩", "憾", "噫", "憖", "憊", "憑", "撼", "薏", "聴", "懇", "曖", "臆", "嚀", "懃", "懋", "蟋", "濘", "謐", "獰", "應", "總", "聰", "隱", "懲", "癒", "懣", "櫁", "檸", "濾", "顋", "蘂", "鯰", "穩", "懲", "懸", "鰓", "轗", "鐚", "懿", "聽", "鑢", "戀", "軈", "靉", "廳"] },
		{ "question": "寸", "answers": ["付", "寺", "守", "団", "吋", "忖", "村", "対", "寿", "肘", "府", "侍", "附", "咐", "坿", "拊", "苻", "持", "待", "専", "狩", "耐", "冠", "封", "峙", "恃", "柎", "紂", "時", "特", "射", "将", "討", "辱", "酎", "涛", "俯", "埒", "得", "符", "尉", "痔", "梼", "祷", "畤", "將", "專", "等", "博", "尊", "尋", "厨", "傅", "幇", "腑", "畴", "詩", "奨", "碍", "蒔", "蒋", "塒", "搏", "溽", "溥", "蓐", "腐", "奪", "蔚", "榑", "膊", "壽", "對", "導", "慰", "遵", "鋳", "廚", "噂", "潯", "熨", "褥", "蕁", "樹", "薄", "縛", "樽", "鮒", "儔", "耨", "縟", "謝", "爵", "醤", "濤", "擣", "賻", "幫", "闘", "檮", "簿", "禱", "蹲", "疇", "籌", "鬪", "躊", "麝", "鑄", "鱒"] },
		{ "question": "辶", "answers": ["辺", "込", "辷", "巡", "迅", "辻", "近", "返", "迎", "迂", "迄", "辿", "述", "迫", "迭", "迚", "迪", "送", "追", "逆", "退", "迷", "逃", "迦", "迢", "迥", "通", "速", "連", "造", "途", "透", "逝", "逐", "逓", "迺", "逅", "迹", "迴", "迸", "週", "進", "逮", "逸", "這", "逗", "逢", "逑", "逕", "逞", "逧", "逡", "逖", "逋", "逍", "逎", "道", "運", "遊", "達", "過", "遅", "遇", "遂", "随", "遍", "遥", "逵", "逬", "逸", "遠", "違", "遣", "遁", "逼", "蓮", "遐", "遒", "遖", "遏", "遑", "逾", "遉", "適", "遭", "遮", "遡", "遜", "腿", "槌", "蓬", "漣", "慥", "遘", "遙", "遞", "選", "導", "遺", "遵", "遷", "樋", "遼", "褪", "遯", "遨", "避", "縫", "還", "撻", "暹", "縋", "隧", "遶", "邁", "遲", "隨", "謎", "篷", "縺", "燵", "燧", "邂", "邀", "遽", "鎚", "鎹", "邇", "邃", "髄", "鏈", "邊", "闥", "譴", "韃", "鑓", "邏", "髓", "靆", "韆"] },
		{ "question": "巳", "answers": ["包", "忌", "杞", "祀", "紀", "巷", "記", "起", "港", "巽", "熈"] },
		{ "question": "己", "answers": ["包", "妃", "改", "忌", "杞", "抱", "泡", "庖", "咆", "苞", "祀", "紀", "巻", "胞", "巷", "枹", "炮", "記", "起", "配", "砲", "倦", "袍", "疱", "皰", "捲", "匏", "惓", "蚫", "萢", "圏", "巽", "飽", "雹", "鉋", "鞄", "蜷", "靤", "綣", "選", "撰", "髱", "鮑", "麭", "饌"] },
		{ "question": "日", "answers": ["旧", "旦", "早", "旨", "旬", "旭", "亘", "児", "更", "但", "旱", "汨", "明", "者", "昔", "果", "易", "担", "昇", "卓", "昆", "旺", "奄", "昂", "昏", "昌", "坦", "沓", "妲", "怛", "杲", "昊", "昃", "杳", "旻", "音", "草", "春", "星", "昼", "指", "昭", "昨", "単", "便", "厚", "映", "専", "宣", "香", "恒", "是", "冒", "胆", "垣", "昧", "徇", "恂", "昜", "昴", "昶", "昵", "昿", "曷", "洵", "衵", "荀", "姮", "者", "時", "書", "借", "恵", "脂", "宴", "陥", "殉", "挿", "竜", "俺", "冥", "桓", "晃", "晒", "晋", "莫", "倡", "倬", "剔", "哽", "悍", "捍", "捏", "晟", "晁", "晏", "涅", "袒", "疸", "耆", "晉", "章", "都", "唱", "巣", "得", "混", "著", "菓", "乾", "婚", "掲", "惜", "措", "喝", "渇", "曹", "悼", "亀", "梗", "曽", "庵", "掩", "焔", "晦", "匙", "渚", "娼", "菖", "猪", "萌", "偃", "偈", "偖", "冕", "勗", "啅", "崑", "掉", "晞", "晤", "晧", "晨", "晢", "桿", "曼", "淹", "猖", "菎", "菴", "竟", "勖", "晣", "專", "晝", "巢", "晚", "間", "場", "晴", "朝", "温", "暑", "湯", "陽", "景", "最", "量", "提", "晩", "煮", "替", "弾", "堤", "普", "帽", "硬", "湿", "晶", "募", "揚", "暁", "葛", "堰", "萱", "戟", "喧", "絢", "椙", "智", "堵", "筍", "奢", "寔", "屠", "惺", "愃", "晰", "棍", "棹", "焜", "覃", "猩", "甦", "萸", "稈", "晳", "曾", "單", "惠", "猪", "都", "渚", "著", "揭", "渴", "電", "暗", "意", "照", "戦", "腸", "幹", "墓", "署", "傷", "暖", "幕", "盟", "暇", "僧", "滝", "裸", "褐", "禅", "漠", "彙", "詣", "隙", "碍", "幌", "蒔", "椿", "摸", "楊", "韵", "亶", "剿", "勦", "嗜", "塒", "寞", "幎", "惷", "搨", "暈", "暉", "暘", "暄", "楮", "腥", "滉", "溟", "歇", "瑁", "煬", "煦", "詢", "裼", "獏", "粳", "蓍", "遏", "罨", "罩", "會", "暑", "煮", "境", "増", "障", "層", "暮", "模", "稲", "漫", "慢", "暦", "遭", "憎", "慕", "膜", "緒", "彰", "僚", "瘍", "斡", "嘗", "漕", "暢", "蔓", "僭", "僣", "夥", "嶂", "幔", "曄", "暝", "蜴", "榻", "韶", "碣", "綽", "裹", "褝", "靼", "睹", "竭", "署", "億", "課", "暴", "諸", "潮", "影", "踏", "撮", "暫", "穂", "潜", "謁", "賜", "縄", "槽", "寮", "憬", "稽", "嘲", "箸", "澗", "樟", "蝉", "箪", "潴", "蕩", "廟", "蝿", "遼", "魯", "冪", "嬋", "幟", "憚", "撩", "蝎", "樔", "踝", "潭", "潦", "璋", "緡", "醋", "諛", "褞", "羯", "瞑", "鄲", "瘟", "殤", "蕈", "蝘", "彈", "緖", "憶", "曇", "錯", "壇", "醒", "賭", "翰", "錫", "穐", "醍", "篭", "噫", "擅", "暾", "暹", "曁", "閹", "蟇", "蟆", "螟", "澣", "赭", "縉", "熾", "燎", "諠", "諳", "瘴", "殫", "覩", "薏", "曉", "戰", "諸", "謁", "曆", "療", "曖", "臆", "闇", "瞭", "曙", "薯", "竃", "糟", "檀", "氈", "鮨", "曚", "闍", "駻", "縵", "艚", "謨", "襌", "鞜", "顆", "隰", "藉", "貘", "盪", "濕", "禪", "潛", "曜", "題", "職", "織", "簡", "贈", "糧", "顕", "韓", "儲", "鞭", "簞", "蟬", "瀑", "簟", "繚", "馥", "謾", "鞨", "觴", "羃", "鏡", "識", "爆", "韻", "譜", "藷", "騨", "瀦", "曝", "櫓", "壜", "鵲", "鯣", "鯤", "曠", "蠍", "躇", "瀚", "鏝", "譚", "譛", "羶", "饂", "藹", "鶍", "響", "籍", "馨", "鰆", "鰛", "曦", "闡", "驀", "簪", "鐔", "鐐", "饅", "蘯", "鰚", "韞", "鰭", "黯", "曩", "蠢", "鬘", "艪", "譖", "鰻", "驒", "鱆", "罎", "顫", "鼴", "響", "鷯", "鱏", "鱓", "顯", "靄", "蠶"] },
		{ "question": "犭", "answers": ["犯", "犲", "状", "狂", "狄", "狆", "狃", "狙", "狗", "狛", "狎", "狒", "独", "狭", "狩", "狐", "狢", "狡", "狠", "荻", "狽", "狸", "狼", "狷", "狹", "猛", "猟", "猫", "猪", "猊", "猜", "猖", "猗", "猝", "逖", "猶", "猴", "猩", "猯", "猥", "猪", "猿", "獅", "獏", "猾", "獄", "誑", "潴", "獗", "蕕", "獲", "獪", "獨", "獰", "嶽", "獵", "獺"] },
		{ "question": "宀", "answers": ["穴", "字", "安", "守", "宇", "宅", "究", "完", "宏", "宍", "宋", "牢", "佗", "佇", "空", "実", "定", "官", "宗", "宙", "宝", "突", "宜", "宛", "陀", "苧", "宕", "侘", "沱", "穹", "室", "客", "宣", "狩", "窃", "按", "穿", "柁", "宥", "咤", "穽", "突", "家", "院", "宮", "案", "害", "容", "宴", "宰", "宵", "莞", "窄", "倥", "宦", "宸", "晏", "浣", "竚", "窈", "宿", "寄", "窓", "密", "寂", "控", "窒", "蛇", "崇", "寅", "菅", "舵", "淀", "婉", "寇", "掟", "淙", "紵", "窕", "寃", "寒", "貯", "富", "割", "腕", "棺", "萱", "寓", "腔", "喧", "詑", "椀", "喀", "寔", "寐", "愃", "棕", "皖", "窖", "窘", "跎", "寝", "溶", "嫁", "搾", "寛", "窟", "塞", "詫", "碇", "蓉", "碗", "寞", "暄", "榁", "腟", "鉈", "滓", "管", "察", "演", "寡", "寧", "綻", "蜜", "窪", "綜", "熔", "寤", "寥", "搴", "蜿", "寨", "榕", "箜", "綰", "聢", "粽", "蓿", "窩", "實", "寢", "賓", "寬", "審", "稼", "窮", "賓", "窯", "寮", "踪", "鞍", "誼", "樒", "膣", "駝", "諚", "瞎", "豌", "寫", "館", "憲", "錠", "舘", "窺", "寰", "鴕", "鴪", "鋺", "縡", "諠", "窶", "鴥", "縮", "擦", "轄", "竃", "嚀", "嬪", "擯", "鮟", "蹇", "濘", "謇", "獰", "賽", "窿", "豁", "螾", "濱", "額", "鎔", "櫁", "檸", "檳", "瀋", "瀉", "殯", "邃", "竅", "竄", "寵", "鶎", "邊", "騫", "繽", "竇", "鰚", "鰘", "寶", "竈", "竊", "鬢"] },
		{ "question": "入", "answers": ["込", "叺", "圦", "全", "吶", "肭", "兩", "兪", "衲", "納", "倆", "蚋", "陝", "偸", "訥", "愉", "喩", "揄", "渝", "愈", "鳰", "楡", "瑜", "裲", "逾", "魞", "瘉", "滿", "蝓", "輛", "輸", "諭", "踰", "瞞", "覦", "鍮", "蟎", "癒", "懣", "魎", "蹣", "糴"] },
		{ "question": "女", "answers": ["奴", "安", "好", "如", "妃", "妄", "汝", "奸", "妁", "努", "妙", "妨", "妥", "妊", "妖", "妓", "佞", "妝", "妣", "妍", "姉", "妹", "委", "始", "妻", "姓", "妬", "姑", "姐", "妾", "呶", "妲", "姆", "孥", "帑", "弩", "要", "姿", "威", "怒", "姻", "娃", "按", "姶", "姦", "姪", "姥", "姨", "姜", "姙", "姚", "拏", "茹", "姸", "姮", "案", "桜", "娘", "宴", "娯", "姫", "娠", "凄", "倭", "恕", "娩", "娥", "娟", "娑", "娜", "娉", "晏", "接", "婦", "婚", "婆", "萎", "娼", "婁", "偃", "婀", "婬", "婉", "娵", "娶", "婢", "婪", "悽", "淒", "婿", "媒", "媛", "堰", "棲", "屡", "媚", "嫂", "椄", "絮", "数", "腰", "嫁", "楼", "嫌", "嫉", "僂", "媼", "媾", "嫋", "媽", "綏", "矮", "褄", "痿", "嫡", "屢", "嫦", "嫣", "嫗", "嫩", "嫖", "鞍", "嬉", "嫺", "嫻", "嬌", "嬋", "駑", "縅", "蝘", "樓", "數", "嬢", "薮", "嬖", "霎", "褸", "瘻", "餒", "窶", "嬰", "嬬", "嬲", "嬪", "嬶", "鮟", "螻", "簍", "縷", "藪", "魏", "嬾", "瀛", "鏤", "嚶", "孅", "孀", "鰄", "孃", "巍", "籔", "瓔", "髏", "櫻", "鼴", "癭", "纓", "鸚"] },
		{ "question": "予", "answers": ["矛", "序", "抒", "茅", "杼", "柔", "矜", "野", "務", "袤", "揉", "舒", "預", "墅", "糅", "橘", "蹂", "蕷", "豫", "懋", "鞣", "霧", "譎", "鶩", "鷸"] },
		{ "question": "斤", "answers": ["斥", "匠", "近", "折", "芹", "听", "圻", "忻", "沂", "所", "祈", "析", "欣", "斧", "拆", "泝", "斫", "柝", "祈", "哲", "逝", "浙", "断", "斬", "掀", "晢", "淅", "晣", "訴", "斯", "晰", "釿", "晳", "新", "皙", "誓", "漸", "塹", "嶄", "慚", "蜥", "厮", "質", "暫", "嘶", "廝", "慙", "撕", "槧", "薪", "噺", "斷", "鏨", "躓"] },
		{ "question": "氵", "answers": ["汁", "氾", "汀", "池", "汚", "汗", "江", "汎", "汝", "汐", "汕", "汽", "決", "沢", "沖", "沈", "没", "沙", "汰", "沃", "汲", "沌", "汪", "沍", "沚", "沁", "汨", "沂", "沐", "泛", "沛", "沪", "沒", "泳", "注", "波", "油", "泣", "治", "法", "河", "沿", "況", "沼", "泊", "泌", "泥", "沸", "泡", "沫", "泓", "泗", "沽", "沮", "泝", "泄", "泅", "沱", "泪", "泯", "沾", "范", "海", "活", "洋", "浅", "染", "洗", "派", "洪", "浄", "津", "洞", "洩", "洲", "洛", "洸", "洽", "洌", "洟", "洶", "洵", "洒", "洫", "茫", "衍", "酒", "消", "流", "浴", "浸", "浜", "浮", "涙", "浪", "浦", "浩", "涛", "涜", "涌", "浬", "娑", "浣", "浙", "涕", "涓", "浹", "浚", "涅", "涎", "莎", "海", "涉", "深", "清", "液", "混", "済", "淡", "添", "婆", "涯", "渇", "渓", "渋", "淑", "渉", "涼", "淫", "淳", "渚", "淀", "淘", "梁", "淋", "渕", "淹", "淬", "淒", "涵", "涸", "淅", "淙", "淆", "淪", "淌", "淤", "笵", "萢", "菠", "萍", "淨", "淺", "淚", "温", "湖", "港", "湯", "落", "満", "減", "測", "渡", "湿", "湾", "渦", "滋", "湧", "渥", "淵", "渠", "湘", "湊", "湛", "溌", "渙", "渣", "湲", "渭", "湮", "湫", "渾", "湍", "渺", "渫", "游", "溂", "渟", "湎", "渝", "湃", "琺", "盜", "渚", "渴", "漢", "準", "源", "溶", "滑", "滞", "滝", "塗", "滅", "溝", "漠", "羨", "溺", "溢", "裟", "蒲", "溜", "溯", "匯", "愆", "滉", "溽", "滄", "溏", "溥", "溷", "滔", "滂", "溘", "溟", "溲", "粱", "滓", "溪", "溫", "漁", "演", "滴", "漫", "漂", "漏", "漆", "漸", "漬", "窪", "潅", "漕", "箔", "漣", "漉", "慂", "滾", "漲", "滬", "滸", "漱", "漾", "滲", "漓", "滷", "滌", "滿", "滯", "漢", "潔", "潮", "澄", "潤", "潜", "潟", "潰", "漑", "澗", "潴", "蕩", "潑", "㵎", "澂", "霈", "潸", "潘", "澎", "潺", "潭", "澆", "潯", "潦", "濆", "澁", "激", "濁", "濃", "薄", "澱", "霑", "澡", "澪", "澣", "澹", "澳", "濛", "薀", "澤", "濯", "鴻", "濠", "濡", "濤", "闊", "濶", "濬", "濘", "濔", "簗", "盪", "濱", "濕", "濟", "潛", "藩", "濫", "瀆", "懣", "鯊", "瀋", "濺", "瀁", "瀏", "瀉", "瀑", "濾", "瀬", "簿", "藻", "瀞", "瀦", "瀕", "霪", "瀚", "瀛", "瀝", "瀟", "瀧", "瀨", "灌", "瀾", "瀲", "瀰", "蘯", "灘", "灑", "灣"] },
		{ "question": "山", "answers": ["仙", "屶", "両", "屹", "汕", "岐", "辿", "岌", "岑", "岔", "杣", "岩", "岸", "岳", "岬", "岡", "岨", "岱", "岫", "疝", "炭", "峠", "峡", "幽", "峙", "島", "峰", "剛", "峨", "峻", "峯", "峩", "峭", "峪", "豈", "峽", "密", "崩", "崎", "崇", "崖", "崕", "崟", "崛", "崑", "崔", "崢", "崚", "崙", "崘", "閊", "満", "嵐", "凱", "剴", "喘", "嵌", "嵒", "嵎", "嵋", "惴", "揣", "湍", "猯", "微", "催", "嵯", "嵳", "嵩", "瑞", "嵬", "輌", "端", "徴", "綱", "嶋", "嶇", "嶄", "嶂", "摧", "澂", "嶢", "嶝", "樒", "磑", "皚", "徵", "鋼", "嶬", "嶮", "嶼", "薇", "癌", "徽", "嶺", "嶷", "繃", "覬", "嶽", "懲", "鎧", "豐", "懲", "巌", "巉", "巍", "巓", "巒", "黴", "巖", "艷"] },
		{ "question": "井", "answers": ["丼", "囲", "刱", "穽", "耕", "冓", "寒", "溝", "塞", "媾", "搆", "構", "搴", "寨", "遘", "嬢", "壌", "篝", "講", "購", "蹇", "謇", "襄", "覯", "賽", "穣", "嚢", "譲", "醸", "攘", "騫", "壤", "孃", "曩", "囊", "禳", "穰", "釀", "讓", "驤"] },
		{ "question": "卩", "answers": ["叩", "卯", "印", "卵", "却", "即", "服", "命", "卹", "卸", "卻", "卽", "脚", "報", "卿", "喞", "赧", "節", "箙"] },
		{ "question": "龰", "answers": ["疋", "足", "走", "定", "是", "促", "赴", "胥", "起", "徒", "従", "捉", "赳", "旋", "匙", "蛋", "淀", "徙", "掟", "跂", "趺", "趾", "從", "提", "越", "距", "堤", "婿", "超", "疎", "疏", "寔", "跏", "跖", "跌", "跚", "跛", "跋", "趁", "跎", "壻", "路", "跡", "跳", "践", "跨", "楚", "碇", "跟", "跣", "跪", "跫", "疑", "踊", "綻", "跼", "跿", "踉", "聢", "趙", "趣", "踏", "踪", "慫", "樅", "踝", "踟", "踞", "諚", "蔬", "踑", "踐", "縦", "凝", "錠", "醍", "蹄", "蕗", "蹂", "踵", "踰", "踴", "擬", "趨", "嚏", "嶷", "蹊", "蹉", "蹌", "蹇", "蹐", "蹈", "聳", "縱", "題", "礎", "蹟", "嚔", "蹙", "蹠", "蹣", "蹤", "蹕", "蹴", "蹶", "蹲", "蹼", "躇", "礙", "蹻", "癡", "躅", "躄", "躁", "躃", "躍", "露", "躋", "躊", "齪", "躓", "躑", "躔", "躙", "鷺", "躡", "躪"] },
		{ "question": "戈", "answers": ["戊", "戉", "成", "伐", "戎", "戍", "戌", "戒", "找", "茂", "或", "戔", "威", "哉", "咸", "栽", "械", "域", "戚", "戛", "國", "淺", "減", "裁", "幾", "惑", "戟", "筏", "喊", "戞", "絨", "牋", "殘", "棧", "感", "戦", "歳", "載", "賊", "滅", "戡", "盞", "閥", "箋", "蔑", "摑", "幗", "截", "綫", "誡", "蔵", "戯", "畿", "賤", "幟", "戮", "槭", "箴", "緘", "縅", "臧", "踐", "機", "憾", "撼", "閾", "熾", "錢", "戰", "繊", "戴", "磯", "馘", "鍼", "餞", "戲", "職", "織", "懴", "戳", "蹙", "濺", "藏", "識", "臓", "譏", "襪", "殱", "孅", "懺", "鰔", "鰄", "鹹", "轗", "籖", "饑", "殲", "鐵", "贓", "臟", "籤", "韈", "纖", "讖"] },
		{ "question": "不", "answers": ["丕", "否", "坏", "抔", "杯", "盃", "歪", "胚", "罘", "痞"] },
		{ "question": "丈", "answers": ["仗", "杖"] },
		{ "question": "刃", "answers": ["仞", "扨", "忍", "刱", "籾", "剏", "紉", "荵", "梁", "靭", "綛", "粱", "認", "簗"] },
		{ "question": "刄", "answers": ["仭", "扨", "籾", "剏", "靱"] },
		{ "question": "千", "answers": ["仟", "刋", "舌", "阡", "乱", "乖", "刮", "瓩", "竏", "舍", "活", "括", "粁", "恬", "挿", "舐", "甜", "筈", "蛞", "聒", "舒", "插", "話", "辞", "歃", "銛", "舖", "憩", "舘", "闊", "濶"] },
		{ "question": "勿", "answers": ["匆", "刎", "吻", "物", "易", "忽", "怱", "昜", "剔", "笏", "惚", "偬", "場", "湯", "陽", "揚", "惣", "葱", "腸", "傷", "楊", "暘", "煬", "裼", "瘍", "暢", "蜴", "賜", "蕩", "殤", "錫", "盪", "觴", "鯣", "鶍", "蘯"] },
		{ "question": "廿", "answers": ["丗", "度", "席", "帯", "庶", "渡", "棄", "滞", "僅", "蓆", "勤", "遮", "蔗", "滿", "嘆", "漢", "歎", "槿", "瑾", "燕", "瞞", "鍍", "懃", "艱", "蟎", "懣", "蹠", "蹣", "覲", "謹", "嚥", "難", "臙", "饉", "儺", "灘", "攤", "鷓", "讌"] },
		{ "question": "⺁", "answers": ["卮", "后", "巵", "派", "盾", "栃", "垢", "脈", "逓", "逅", "虒", "梔", "循", "遁", "楯", "詬", "遞", "褫", "篪"] },
		{ "question": "艹", "answers": ["艾", "芋", "芝", "芍", "芒", "花", "芸", "芳", "芯", "芥", "苅", "芹", "芭", "芙", "芫", "芟", "芬", "芦", "苆", "苦", "英", "芽", "若", "茂", "苗", "茎", "苛", "苑", "茄", "苫", "苒", "苔", "苧", "茅", "苓", "苡", "苳", "茉", "苜", "苻", "苣", "范", "苞", "苙", "苟", "苹", "茆", "苴", "苺", "草", "茶", "荒", "荘", "茨", "荊", "茸", "荏", "茜", "荆", "茴", "茯", "茱", "荀", "荅", "茲", "茹", "茵", "荐", "茗", "茘", "茫", "莽", "荷", "華", "匿", "莞", "荻", "莵", "莫", "莱", "莓", "莚", "莢", "莪", "莟", "莎", "莅", "茣", "莨", "荳", "莠", "荼", "荵", "莉", "莖", "莊", "菜", "著", "菓", "描", "菊", "菌", "猫", "萎", "菅", "菖", "萄", "菩", "萌", "萠", "椛", "菱", "萊", "剳", "菽", "萢", "菠", "菎", "菴", "菲", "萃", "萍", "菫", "菁", "菘", "萁", "葉", "落", "満", "備", "勤", "敬", "塔", "慌", "葬", "募", "搭", "葛", "瑛", "萱", "葵", "韮", "菰", "惹", "萩", "葺", "葱", "菟", "董", "葡", "葎", "葢", "萼", "葩", "葷", "萸", "萵", "葯", "葭", "葆", "蒂", "孶", "萬", "著", "漢", "墓", "夢", "蒸", "幕", "嘆", "蓄", "寛", "漠", "蓋", "葦", "蓑", "蒜", "蒔", "蒐", "蒋", "蒼", "摸", "蒲", "蒙", "蓉", "蓮", "寞", "獏", "糀", "蒭", "蒿", "蓙", "蒟", "蓖", "蒡", "蓍", "蓆", "蒹", "蓁", "蓐", "蒻", "蜹", "暮", "模", "慕", "膜", "蔑", "蔚", "蔭", "蔦", "蔓", "蔀", "蓬", "蔣", "慝", "鋩", "蓼", "蔗", "蔔", "蔡", "蔘", "蔟", "蓴", "蓿", "蔕", "寬", "蔵", "諾", "蔽", "蕎", "蕨", "蕉", "蕊", "蕋", "歎", "蕩", "蕃", "蕪", "儚", "冪", "蟒", "膵", "錵", "錺", "甍", "蔬", "蕘", "蕕", "蕁", "蕈", "蕀", "薬", "獲", "薪", "薄", "薫", "薦", "薗", "薮", "薙", "錨", "蕗", "嚆", "憊", "霙", "蟇", "蟆", "檠", "濛", "糒", "蕣", "薊", "蕷", "蕾", "薔", "薨", "薀", "薑", "薜", "薛", "薈", "薇", "薐", "薤", "蕭", "邁", "薏", "勵", "謹", "藁", "薩", "薯", "懃", "朦", "曚", "蠎", "檬", "謨", "癘", "藉", "薹", "薺", "藐", "貘", "艱", "舊", "薰", "難", "穫", "藩", "繭", "藤", "藍", "藪", "鞳", "矇", "藕", "藜", "羃", "藝", "藥", "藏", "警", "臓", "藻", "藷", "蘇", "蘂", "蘭", "礪", "蠖", "躇", "瀟", "艨", "襪", "鞴", "蘊", "藾", "蘢", "藺", "藹", "蘋", "蘆", "鰙", "蠆", "勸", "護", "灌", "蠣", "懽", "蘗", "蘖", "驀", "糲", "蘚", "蘯", "儺", "囈", "權", "歡", "驚", "灘", "攤", "蘿", "臟", "韈", "罐", "讙", "觀", "鑵", "躪", "顴", "驩", "鸛"] },
		{ "question": "气", "answers": ["気", "汽", "氛", "氣", "愾"] },
		{ "question": "白", "answers": ["百", "伯", "皁", "的", "泊", "拍", "迫", "狛", "佰", "帛", "怕", "皇", "泉", "皆", "柏", "珀", "陌", "卽", "原", "皋", "畠", "袙", "習", "宿", "舶", "凰", "皐", "兜", "粕", "偕", "瓸", "皎", "竡", "階", "卿", "弼", "棉", "喞", "徨", "惶", "揩", "隍", "粨", "葩", "皓", "皖", "楽", "節", "源", "慨", "楷", "腺", "楾", "煌", "皙", "貊", "遑", "綿", "貌", "厩", "廐", "廏", "摺", "箔", "碧", "愿", "慴", "蓿", "槔", "線", "漑", "翫", "魄", "蝗", "篁", "皚", "樂", "激", "諧", "錦", "穆", "徼", "曁", "褶", "螈", "縮", "檄", "鍠", "藐", "邀", "幫", "擽", "竅", "藥", "願", "櫟", "爍", "覈", "繳", "鰉", "礫", "轢", "鑠"] },
		{ "question": "云", "answers": ["会", "伝", "芸", "桧", "耘", "紜", "転", "陰", "雲", "絵", "魂", "蔭", "曇", "繧", "藝", "壜", "囈", "罎", "靆", "靉"] },
		{ "question": "父", "answers": ["交", "効", "佼", "斧", "郊", "咬", "狡", "校", "釜", "效", "皎", "絞", "傚", "蛟", "較", "爺", "餃", "駮", "鮫", "鵁", "纐"] },
		{ "question": "⺌", "answers": ["光", "恍", "洸", "党", "晃", "胱", "堂", "常", "掌", "棠", "絖", "幌", "滉", "觥", "當", "嘗", "裳", "嫦", "賞", "輝", "瞠", "償", "螳", "礑", "襠", "蟷", "耀", "黨", "鐺", "儻"] },
		{ "question": "耂", "answers": ["考", "老", "孝", "者", "拷", "姥", "者", "哮", "栲", "耆", "耄", "教", "都", "著", "渚", "猪", "偖", "暑", "煮", "堵", "奢", "屠", "蛯", "耋", "猪", "都", "渚", "著", "署", "嗜", "楮", "蓍", "暑", "煮", "酵", "緒", "睹", "署", "諸", "箸", "潴", "緖", "賭", "赭", "覩", "諸", "曙", "薯", "闍", "鮱", "儲", "藷", "瀦", "躇", "鰭"] },
		{ "question": "彳", "answers": ["行", "役", "彷", "径", "往", "征", "彼", "徂", "彿", "後", "待", "律", "徊", "很", "徇", "衍", "徒", "従", "徐", "桁", "徑", "得", "術", "徙", "徘", "裄", "衒", "從", "街", "復", "御", "循", "葎", "徨", "絎", "微", "徭", "愆", "衙", "徳", "徴", "銜", "衝", "徹", "履", "慫", "樅", "德", "徵", "衛", "縦", "衡", "禦", "徼", "薇", "衞", "徽", "鵆", "聳", "縱", "覆", "懲", "蹤", "懲", "黴", "衢"] },
		{ "question": "亍", "answers": ["行", "衍", "桁", "術", "裄", "衒", "街", "絎", "愆", "衙", "銜", "衝", "衛", "衡", "衞", "鵆", "衢"] },
		{ "question": "巴", "answers": ["色", "把", "邑", "芭", "巵", "肥", "杷", "爬", "悒", "耙", "笆", "扈", "梔", "琶", "葩", "滬", "廱", "癰"] },
		{ "question": "彐", "answers": ["当", "争", "事", "妻", "庚", "帚", "爭", "急", "侵", "浄", "帰", "浸", "凄", "剥", "雪", "婦", "掃", "崢", "彗", "悽", "淒", "淨", "尋", "棲", "禄", "筝", "寝", "碌", "褄", "緑", "静", "隠", "箒", "箏", "寢", "縁", "慧", "潯", "諍", "蕁", "録", "穏", "錚", "靜", "駸", "艝", "隱", "轌", "歸", "瀞", "穩", "鱈", "籙"] },
		{ "question": "毋", "answers": ["毎", "毒", "瑇", "纛"] },
		{ "question": "皿", "answers": ["血", "孟", "盂", "卹", "盆", "盈", "盃", "恤", "洫", "益", "盌", "盍", "衄", "盛", "盗", "猛", "盒", "温", "衆", "葢", "盜", "塩", "盟", "蓋", "溢", "媼", "慍", "楹", "溘", "隘", "盞", "溫", "寧", "膃", "盡", "監", "盤", "褞", "瘟", "儘", "縊", "諡", "薀", "盧", "盥", "縕", "嚀", "濘", "醢", "謚", "謐", "獰", "盪", "闔", "檸", "鎰", "燼", "廬", "醯", "饂", "蘊", "蘆", "鰛", "櫨", "臚", "蘯", "韞", "爐", "鷁", "鰮", "贐", "艫", "蠱", "轤", "鑪", "顱", "鹽", "驢", "鱸"] },
		{ "question": "冋", "answers": ["向", "尚", "炯", "迥", "高", "淌", "絅", "喬", "敞", "塙", "嵩", "蒿", "僑", "膏", "厰", "敲", "槁", "犒", "稿", "蕎", "廠", "嬌", "餉", "橋", "縞", "嚆", "矯", "藁", "鎬", "嚮", "轎", "蹻", "驕"] },
		{ "question": "歹", "answers": ["死", "列", "夙", "例", "冽", "歿", "殀", "屍", "殆", "洌", "殃", "殄", "残", "烈", "殊", "殉", "殍", "殖", "葬", "裂", "殘", "殞", "殤", "殫", "殪", "薨", "薤", "斃", "餮", "殯", "殱", "殲"] },
		{ "question": "冫", "answers": ["次", "冱", "冷", "均", "冶", "冴", "冽", "姿", "茨", "咨", "弱", "凍", "准", "恣", "凄", "凋", "凌", "凅", "盗", "瓷", "馮", "鈞", "粢", "資", "溺", "韵", "嫋", "搦", "蒻", "凜", "凛", "凝", "諮", "憑", "鰯", "鶸", "懿"] },
		{ "question": "欠", "answers": ["次", "吹", "坎", "欧", "炊", "欣", "姿", "茨", "咨", "恣", "欲", "盗", "軟", "掀", "欸", "欷", "瓷", "飲", "欺", "款", "欽", "厥", "嵌", "欹", "粢", "盜", "資", "羨", "歇", "歃", "歌", "嗽", "漱", "歉", "歓", "蕨", "歎", "慾", "獗", "歐", "諮", "歔", "歙", "歟", "歛", "闕", "蠍", "蹶", "歡", "懿"] },
		{ "question": "月", "answers": ["有", "肌", "肋", "肝", "肖", "肘", "肛", "肚", "肓", "青", "明", "育", "服", "肥", "肩", "肪", "肯", "肢", "股", "肱", "朋", "肭", "肬", "前", "胃", "肺", "背", "削", "胎", "胆", "胞", "胤", "胡", "兪", "朏", "胙", "胝", "胛", "胚", "胥", "胄", "胖", "俞", "消", "脈", "能", "胸", "骨", "朗", "脂", "胴", "脅", "宵", "朕", "脊", "脇", "朔", "哨", "脆", "屑", "倩", "娟", "峭", "悁", "悄", "捐", "胱", "胯", "胼", "涓", "狷", "清", "望", "情", "脳", "脚", "脱", "豚", "崩", "梢", "萌", "萠", "偸", "剪", "堋", "弸", "脣", "脯", "脛", "脩", "猜", "菁", "逍", "朗", "晴", "朝", "期", "湖", "勝", "散", "筋", "腕", "婿", "硝", "惰", "棚", "愉", "喩", "腔", "揃", "脹", "喟", "揄", "朞", "腋", "脾", "腓", "腆", "腑", "渭", "渝", "隋", "稍", "腁", "壻", "腸", "絹", "腹", "盟", "腰", "滑", "塑", "腫", "腎", "煎", "腺", "瑚", "蛸", "靖", "楕", "愈", "溯", "蜎", "楡", "腮", "腴", "腱", "腥", "腟", "瑜", "硼", "骭", "猾", "睛", "逾", "榆", "筲", "腦", "静", "精", "態", "膜", "熊", "遡", "厭", "膏", "腿", "愬", "蜻", "榾", "槊", "膃", "膈", "膀", "膂", "膊", "箙", "骰", "酳", "誚", "瘉", "趙", "潮", "膚", "請", "徹", "撤", "罷", "嘲", "膝", "糊", "撒", "箭", "廟", "㵎", "嫺", "霄", "蝴", "蝓", "蝟", "膣", "膠", "膵", "滕", "潸", "銷", "遯", "翦", "墮", "輸", "膨", "諭", "骸", "膳", "謂", "醐", "錆", "鞘", "橢", "膩", "踰", "膰", "骼", "燗", "覦", "龍", "隨", "靜", "謄", "臆", "膿", "朦", "臀", "臂", "膺", "膾", "臉", "鍮", "繃", "癇", "壓", "膽", "癒", "藤", "擺", "鵑", "鮹", "臑", "臍", "繖", "繝", "髀", "餬", "羂", "臓", "髄", "覇", "鯖", "瀞", "轍", "鵬", "臘", "瀛", "羸", "羆", "鶄", "騰", "朧", "霰", "臙", "臚", "贏", "霸", "鶻", "籐", "髏", "鰧", "臟", "靨", "髑", "髓", "體", "魘", "黶"] },
		{ "question": "龷", "answers": ["共", "昔", "供", "洪", "巷", "哄", "拱", "借", "恭", "異", "惜", "措", "港", "散", "巽", "蛬", "殿", "閧", "選", "暴", "撒", "撰", "醋", "錯", "澱", "冀", "鬨", "翼", "戴", "糞", "臀", "藉", "瀑", "繖", "癜", "爆", "曝", "鵲", "籍", "霰", "饌", "驥"] },
		{ "question": "卄", "answers": ["共", "昔", "供", "其", "尭", "侖", "洪", "甚", "巷", "哄", "扁", "拱", "借", "恭", "倫", "基", "異", "惜", "措", "偏", "崙", "崘", "淪", "萁", "期", "港", "散", "焼", "棋", "欺", "暁", "遍", "斯", "巽", "棊", "朞", "蛬", "賁", "殿", "碁", "嗣", "祺", "旗", "箕", "閧", "綸", "褊", "厮", "綦", "選", "輪", "編", "暴", "論", "噴", "墳", "憤", "撒", "撰", "篇", "嘶", "廝", "撕", "蝙", "濆", "醋", "翩", "踑", "錯", "澱", "冀", "諞", "鬨", "翼", "戴", "糞", "龠", "臀", "藉", "瀑", "騏", "繖", "癜", "爆", "麒", "簸", "曝", "鵲", "騙", "籍", "霰", "饌", "籥", "鑰", "驥"] },
		{ "question": "戊", "answers": ["成", "戍", "戌", "茂", "威", "咸", "戚", "減", "喊", "感", "歳", "滅", "蔑", "蔵", "槭", "箴", "緘", "縅", "憾", "撼", "鍼", "蹙", "臓", "襪", "鰔", "鰄", "鹹", "轗", "韈"] },
		{ "question": "⺈", "answers": ["争", "危", "急", "負", "浄", "陥", "脆", "魚", "亀", "焔", "啗", "埳", "陷", "焰", "筝", "跪", "麁", "詭", "魞", "静", "漁", "夐", "魯", "魴", "諍", "諂", "魳", "魸", "魬", "衡", "穐", "鮎", "鮒", "憺", "鮃", "鮓", "鮑", "鮗", "鮖", "閻", "澹", "錚", "薊", "鮇", "擔", "賴", "鮮", "鮪", "鮭", "鮫", "鮟", "鮨", "鮠", "鮴", "檐", "餡", "鮱", "膽", "鯉", "鯀", "鯊", "鯒", "鯑", "鯏", "鮹", "瓊", "瞻", "鯎", "鮸", "鯨", "鯖", "瀞", "蘇", "鯵", "鯛", "櫓", "鯣", "鯢", "鯤", "鯲", "鯡", "鯔", "鯱", "鯰", "蟾", "簷", "鰙", "鰐", "鰍", "巉", "鰓", "鰉", "鰔", "鰕", "鰌", "鰈", "鰆", "鰒", "鰊", "鰄", "鰛", "譫", "蘚", "贍", "鰚", "鰘", "鰯", "鰭", "鰮", "鰥", "鰤", "鰰", "艪", "鰧", "鱈", "鰺", "鰻", "鱆", "鱇", "鰾", "癬", "鰹", "鱒", "鱚", "纔", "鱛", "鱏", "鱓", "鱗", "鱠", "鱧", "讒", "鱟", "鱩", "鱶", "鱲", "鱸"] },
		{ "question": "中", "answers": ["仲", "沖", "串", "狆", "忠", "迚", "患", "貴", "遣", "匱", "遺", "潰", "嚢", "櫃", "簣", "譴", "饋", "鑓", "囊", "蠹"] },
		{ "question": "火", "answers": ["灯", "灰", "災", "灸", "灼", "狄", "炎", "炊", "炉", "炙", "炒", "秋", "炭", "畑", "恢", "炸", "炮", "炬", "炳", "炯", "荻", "烟", "耿", "烙", "淡", "焔", "啖", "烱", "烽", "逖", "焼", "萩", "焚", "焰", "啾", "愀", "毯", "湫", "焜", "焙", "勞", "煙", "滅", "愁", "煩", "煤", "煉", "塋", "楸", "煥", "煢", "煌", "煬", "煖", "詼", "痰", "煽", "熔", "犖", "甃", "熕", "熄", "榮", "談", "撈", "瑩", "燃", "熾", "燉", "燔", "燗", "燎", "燈", "螢", "燒", "燥", "燦", "鍬", "燭", "燐", "燮", "燵", "燧", "燠", "燬", "癆", "餤", "營", "燹", "燿", "燼", "燻", "鞦", "爆", "爍", "鰍", "蠑", "爐", "鶯", "爛", "爨"] },
		{ "question": "反", "answers": ["仮", "坂", "返", "阪", "板", "版", "叛", "販", "飯", "鈑", "魬"] },
		{ "question": "午", "answers": ["件", "忤", "杵", "許", "滸"] },
		{ "question": "冉", "answers": ["再", "苒", "冓", "溝", "媾", "搆", "構", "遘", "稱", "髯", "篝", "講", "購", "覯"] },
		{ "question": "壬", "answers": ["任", "呈", "廷", "妊", "凭", "荏", "姙", "衽", "庭", "挺", "恁", "淫", "婬", "梃", "袵", "聖", "賃", "艇", "蜓", "澂", "霆", "徵", "霪", "懲", "聽"] },
		{ "question": "于", "answers": ["宇", "芋", "吁", "迂", "盂", "紆", "竽"] },
		{ "question": "厃", "answers": ["危", "脆", "跪", "詭", "憺", "澹", "擔", "鮠", "檐", "膽", "瞻", "蟾", "簷", "譫", "贍"] },
		{ "question": "及", "answers": ["吸", "扱", "汲", "岌", "級", "笈"] },
		{ "question": "乇", "answers": ["宅", "托", "侘", "咤", "託", "詫"] },
		{ "question": "亐", "answers": ["汚", "虧"] },
		{ "question": "卬", "answers": ["仰", "迎", "抑", "昂"] },
		{ "question": "巛", "answers": ["巡", "災", "拶", "剄", "勁", "徑", "莖", "脛", "逕", "巢", "痙", "惱", "剿", "勦", "瑙", "經", "腦", "緇", "輕", "樔", "輜", "頸", "錙", "鯔", "廱", "癰"] },
		{ "question": "尺", "answers": ["尽", "沢", "択", "呎", "昼", "咫", "訳", "釈", "駅"] },
		{ "question": "忄", "answers": ["忙", "忖", "快", "忻", "忤", "忸", "忱", "忰", "性", "怖", "怪", "怯", "怜", "怡", "怙", "怩", "怛", "怕", "怫", "怦", "怏", "怺", "恒", "悔", "恨", "恢", "恰", "恪", "恟", "恊", "恍", "恃", "恤", "恂", "恬", "恫", "恆", "悩", "悦", "悟", "悌", "悁", "悍", "悃", "悚", "悄", "悛", "悖", "悒", "悧", "悋", "悔", "情", "惨", "惜", "悼", "惧", "惟", "惚", "惇", "悸", "惓", "悴", "悽", "惆", "悵", "惘", "慌", "惰", "愉", "愕", "惶", "愀", "惴", "惺", "愃", "惻", "愎", "惱", "慎", "慨", "慄", "慍", "愾", "愧", "慊", "愴", "愼", "慣", "慢", "憎", "慷", "慚", "慴", "慥", "慟", "慓", "慵", "慘", "憤", "憬", "憧", "慳", "憔", "憚", "憫", "憮", "憎", "憶", "懐", "憾", "憐", "懌", "懊", "懈", "懆", "憺", "懍", "罹", "懦", "懴", "懶", "懷", "懺", "懽", "懾", "懼"] },
		{ "question": "亡", "answers": ["忙", "妄", "芒", "忘", "肓", "盲", "氓", "罔", "荒", "虻", "茫", "望", "惘", "慌", "網", "鋩", "蝱", "魍", "瀛", "羸", "贏"] },
		{ "question": "少", "answers": ["劣", "妙", "抄", "沙", "歩", "毟", "杪", "炒", "秒", "省", "砂", "眇", "捗", "紗", "娑", "莎", "渉", "渺", "鈔", "裟", "尠", "賓", "緲", "頻", "嬪", "擯", "濱", "鯊", "檳", "殯", "瀕", "蘋", "繽", "鬢", "顰"] },
		{ "question": "开", "answers": ["刑", "并", "形", "妍", "併", "枅", "研", "型", "荊", "荆", "剏", "屏", "胼", "笄", "迸", "瓶", "開", "塀", "絣", "餅", "駢"] },
		{ "question": "凡", "answers": ["帆", "汎", "梵", "羸", "贏"] },
		{ "question": "犬", "answers": ["伏", "状", "吠", "拔", "狀", "茯", "莽", "突", "哭", "唳", "捩", "祓", "臭", "袱", "倏", "淚", "然", "跋", "献", "嗅", "猷", "綟", "獄", "厭", "黙", "魃", "髮", "獣", "憖", "默", "器", "黻", "闃", "嶽", "壓", "獸", "鶪", "獻", "飆", "靨", "魘", "黶"] },
		{ "question": "史", "answers": ["吏", "使", "駛"] },
		{ "question": "允", "answers": ["充", "吮", "統", "銃"] },
		{ "question": "卂", "answers": ["迅", "恐", "訊", "筑", "蛩", "跫", "煢", "蝨", "鞏", "築", "瀛", "羸", "贏"] },
		{ "question": "⺄", "answers": ["迅", "虱", "恐", "訊", "筑", "蛩", "跫", "煢", "蝨", "鞏", "築", "瀛", "羸", "贏"] },
		{ "question": "丬", "answers": ["壮", "荘", "将", "装", "寝", "奨", "蒋", "醤"] },
		{ "question": "支", "answers": ["伎", "技", "岐", "妓", "枝", "肢", "翅", "跂", "鼓", "鼕", "瞽"] },
		{ "question": "尹", "answers": ["伊", "君", "郡", "笋", "裙", "窘", "群"] },
		{ "question": "乞", "answers": ["吃", "屹", "迄", "訖", "乾"] },
		{ "question": "凶", "answers": ["兇", "匈", "恟", "洶", "胸", "悩", "脳", "禽", "椶", "漓", "璃", "擒", "檎", "離", "魑", "黐", "籬"] },
		{ "question": "五", "answers": ["伍", "吾", "悟", "唔", "圄", "梧", "晤", "牾", "衙", "語", "寤", "鼯", "齬"] },
		{ "question": "旦", "answers": ["亘", "但", "担", "坦", "妲", "怛", "昼", "宣", "恒", "胆", "垣", "昜", "姮", "桓", "袒", "疸", "得", "晝", "場", "湯", "陽", "量", "揚", "萱", "喧", "愃", "腸", "傷", "碍", "楊", "亶", "暘", "暄", "煬", "瘍", "暢", "靼", "蕩", "殤", "壇", "擅", "曁", "諠", "檀", "氈", "盪", "糧", "觴", "羶", "蘯", "鰚", "顫"] },
		{ "question": "氶", "answers": ["丞", "拯", "烝", "蒸"] },
		{ "question": "牛", "answers": ["牝", "牟", "牡", "牢", "吽", "物", "牧", "牲", "牴", "特", "造", "浩", "桙", "牽", "晧", "梏", "牾", "犁", "眸", "犀", "惣", "犂", "犇", "皓", "窖", "解", "酷", "鉾", "犒", "犖", "誥", "靠", "廨", "懈", "犠", "鴾", "邂", "鵠", "蟹", "蠏", "犢", "犧"] },
		{ "question": "介", "answers": ["价", "芥", "界", "疥", "堺"] },
		{ "question": "亢", "answers": ["伉", "抗", "坑", "吭", "杭", "航", "頏"] },
		{ "question": "卆", "answers": ["伜", "忰", "枠", "砕", "粋", "翆", "酔"] },
		{ "question": "互", "answers": ["冱", "沍"] },
		{ "question": "夬", "answers": ["刔", "決", "快", "抉", "袂", "缺", "訣", "鴃", "鴂"] },
		{ "question": "亏", "answers": ["夸", "刳", "咢", "胯", "袴", "匏", "愕", "瓠", "鄂", "萼", "誇", "跨", "樗", "諤", "鍔", "虧", "顎", "鰐", "鶚", "齶"] },
		{ "question": "勺", "answers": ["妁", "芍", "杓", "灼", "的", "約", "酌", "豹", "釣", "葯"] },
		{ "question": "叉", "answers": ["扠", "蚤", "釵", "靫", "搔", "騷"] },
		{ "question": "肀", "answers": ["聿", "建", "律", "津", "書", "唐", "健", "粛", "庸", "晝", "筆", "葎", "畫", "塘", "傭", "腱", "溏", "肄", "肆", "肅", "劃", "肇", "慵", "盡", "糖", "儘", "嘯", "蕭", "螗", "鍵", "燼", "繡", "瀟", "簫", "贐"] },
		{ "question": "才", "answers": ["犲", "材", "財", "豺", "閉"] },
		{ "question": "阝", "answers": ["阡", "防", "邦", "那", "阪", "阮", "阯", "阨", "邨", "邪", "阻", "邸", "附", "阿", "祁", "陀", "陂", "邯", "邵", "邱", "限", "郎", "郊", "郁", "耶", "陋", "陌", "院", "郡", "降", "除", "陛", "陣", "陥", "陜", "陝", "陟", "陞", "郛", "郢", "郤", "郞", "都", "部", "陸", "険", "郷", "郵", "陰", "郭", "陳", "陶", "陪", "隆", "陵", "婀", "陬", "陲", "捓", "陷", "階", "陽", "隊", "随", "隅", "堕", "隈", "揶", "隋", "隍", "鄂", "都", "隔", "隙", "爺", "椰", "隗", "隕", "隘", "鄒", "痾", "廊", "際", "障", "隠", "蔭", "廓", "蔀", "榔", "瑯", "鄙", "墜", "鄭", "槨", "鄲", "墮", "隣", "橢", "螂", "隧", "隨", "鄰", "險", "薩", "隰", "窿", "隱", "擲", "隴", "騭", "躑"] },
		{ "question": "屮", "answers": ["艸", "逆", "朔", "蚩", "芻", "厥", "塑", "溯", "嗤", "鄒", "蒭", "遡", "愬", "槊", "蕨", "獗", "皺", "趨", "雛", "闕", "蹶", "櫱", "糱"] },
		{ "question": "攵", "answers": ["收", "改", "条", "攻", "孜", "放", "牧", "枚", "玫", "故", "政", "畋", "修", "致", "敏", "倣", "效", "教", "救", "敗", "啓", "赦", "悠", "做", "敖", "脩", "倏", "敕", "敏", "散", "敬", "敢", "敦", "傚", "敞", "敝", "数", "微", "傲", "愍", "筱", "絛", "徴", "厰", "肇", "嗷", "嫩", "綮", "敵", "敷", "徹", "撤", "幣", "弊", "蔽", "撒", "廠", "澂", "熬", "遨", "數", "徵", "整", "激", "繁", "緻", "薮", "徼", "暾", "橄", "檠", "燉", "薇", "厳", "徽", "瞥", "斂", "螯", "螫", "檄", "瞰", "邀", "繁", "懲", "藪", "斃", "瓊", "繖", "釐", "贅", "竅", "警", "轍", "覈", "繳", "懲", "巌", "鶩", "霰", "瀲", "鐓", "嚴", "籔", "驚", "儼", "黴", "巖", "變", "鼇", "鼈"] },
		{ "question": "化", "answers": ["花", "囮", "貨", "椛", "訛", "靴", "糀", "錵"] },
		{ "question": "田", "answers": ["男", "町", "佃", "甸", "画", "苗", "思", "界", "畑", "胃", "勇", "卑", "畏", "毘", "毗", "畋", "留", "畜", "畔", "畝", "畠", "俾", "畛", "畚", "魚", "細", "副", "略", "異", "描", "猫", "累", "曽", "畦", "偲", "匐", "婢", "畤", "番", "富", "畳", "幅", "塁", "湧", "堺", "甥", "牌", "喟", "脾", "渭", "畭", "畴", "畬", "畫", "福", "僧", "蓄", "雷", "虜", "畷", "稗", "逼", "腮", "鈿", "裨", "睥", "痺", "畸", "舅", "魞", "痹", "當", "鼻", "漁", "増", "層", "憎", "碑", "劃", "緇", "蔔", "福", "膚", "慮", "審", "畿", "播", "幡", "蕃", "魯", "僵", "魴", "蝠", "蝟", "潘", "輜", "稷", "禝", "魳", "魸", "魬", "奮", "獣", "衡", "謂", "彊", "鴫", "鮎", "錨", "鮒", "璢", "冀", "擂", "鮃", "鮓", "鮑", "鮗", "鮖", "踴", "膰", "輻", "錙", "燔", "瘰", "薊", "蕾", "薑", "盧", "鮇", "鮮", "翼", "戴", "鮪", "鮭", "橿", "鮫", "糞", "螺", "儡", "嚊", "嚏", "嬲", "嬶", "鼾", "鮟", "鮨", "鮠", "鮴", "縲", "謖", "鮱", "贈", "藩", "翻", "鯉", "嚔", "旛", "鯀", "鯊", "鯒", "鯑", "鯏", "鮹", "霤", "蟠", "瀋", "濾", "礑", "繙", "髀", "襠", "顋", "鯎", "鮸", "壘", "鯨", "鯖", "蘇", "鯵", "鯛", "櫓", "廬", "鵯", "鯣", "鯢", "鯤", "鯲", "鯡", "鯔", "鯱", "鯰", "蟷", "蘆", "疇", "疆", "鰙", "獸", "鰐", "鰍", "鰓", "鰉", "鰔", "鰕", "鰌", "鰈", "鰆", "鰒", "鰊", "鰄", "鰛", "櫨", "臚", "蘚", "鰚", "鰘", "爐", "鰯", "鰭", "飜", "鰮", "鰥", "鰤", "鰰", "罍", "騾", "鐺", "艪", "籒", "鰧", "鱈", "鰺", "鰻", "鱆", "鱇", "鰾", "艫", "癬", "疊", "鰹", "鱒", "鷭", "鱚", "轤", "鑢", "鱛", "鱏", "鱓", "鱗", "鱠", "鱧", "鑪", "顰", "鱟", "鱩", "顱", "鱶", "驥", "驢", "鱲", "鱸"] },
		{ "question": "可", "answers": ["何", "河", "奇", "苛", "阿", "呵", "珂", "柯", "荷", "倚", "剞", "哥", "寄", "崎", "埼", "婀", "掎", "舸", "猗", "椅", "軻", "欹", "訶", "痾", "畸", "歌", "綺", "謌", "騎", "羇"] },
		{ "question": "幵", "answers": ["形", "枅", "姸", "栞", "開", "筓"] },
		{ "question": "彡", "answers": ["形", "杉", "尨", "参", "衫", "珍", "彦", "厖", "殄", "修", "疹", "袗", "畛", "彩", "惨", "彫", "彪", "彬", "偐", "參", "診", "須", "彭", "軫", "趁", "勠", "髢", "髪", "彰", "寥", "廖", "摎", "滲", "髦", "髣", "蓼", "蔘", "髥", "慘", "影", "戮", "樛", "膠", "澎", "髫", "髯", "髴", "髱", "髮", "膨", "諺", "髭", "穆", "髻", "髷", "簓", "繆", "糝", "顔", "謬", "鬆", "醪", "餮", "顏", "鯵", "鏐", "驂", "鬘", "鰺", "鬚", "鬟", "鬢", "鬣", "鬱"] },
		{ "question": "乍", "answers": ["作", "昨", "怎", "柞", "胙", "炸", "窄", "祚", "詐", "酢", "搾", "筰", "鮓"] },
		{ "question": "本", "answers": ["体", "笨", "鉢"] },
		{ "question": "弚", "answers": ["弟", "剃", "俤", "悌", "涕", "梯", "睇", "鵜"] },
		{ "question": "弔", "answers": ["弟", "剃", "俤", "悌", "涕", "第", "梯", "睇", "鵜"] },
		{ "question": "龶", "answers": ["麦", "青", "表", "毒", "害", "素", "倩", "清", "情", "責", "麸", "猜", "菁", "晴", "割", "債", "靖", "勣", "睛", "瑇", "静", "精", "漬", "嘖", "蜻", "請", "麹", "瞎", "積", "憲", "麺", "錆", "磧", "靜", "績", "轄", "簀", "豁", "蹟", "鯖", "瀞", "鶄", "癪", "纛"] },
		{ "question": "甲", "answers": ["里", "匣", "押", "岬", "呷", "狎", "厘", "俚", "胛", "埋", "哩", "浬", "狸", "黒", "野", "理", "童", "量", "裡", "裏", "閘", "墨", "僮", "墅", "甅", "竰", "黙", "憧", "撞", "糎", "幢", "廛", "鴨", "黛", "橦", "瞳", "糧", "鯉", "釐", "艟", "鐘", "纏", "霾", "躔"] },
		{ "question": "矢", "answers": ["医", "矣", "知", "侯", "矧", "俟", "候", "疾", "挨", "矩", "埃", "族", "欸", "短", "智", "竢", "痴", "嫉", "肄", "雉", "矮", "疑", "蜘", "聟", "踟", "凝", "薙", "擬", "矯", "嶷", "翳", "醫", "礙", "癡"] },
		{ "question": "穴", "answers": ["究", "空", "突", "穹", "窃", "穿", "穽", "突", "窄", "倥", "窈", "窓", "控", "窒", "窕", "腔", "窖", "窘", "搾", "窟", "窪", "箜", "窩", "窮", "窯", "膣", "窺", "鴪", "窶", "鴥", "竃", "窿", "邃", "竅", "竄", "邊", "竇", "竈", "竊"] },
		{ "question": "主", "answers": ["住", "注", "往", "柱", "註", "駐", "麈"] },
		{ "question": "且", "answers": ["助", "阻", "宜", "狙", "姐", "岨", "咀", "徂", "沮", "苴", "査", "祖", "俎", "柤", "租", "砠", "疽", "祖", "組", "粗", "勗", "蛆", "畳", "渣", "詛", "耡", "雎", "誼", "鋤", "鎺", "齟", "疊"] },
		{ "question": "文", "answers": ["対", "吝", "斉", "旻", "剤", "紋", "蚊", "悋", "紊", "虔", "済", "斎", "偐", "斑", "斐", "斌", "閔", "憫", "諺", "薩", "顏", "贇"] },
		{ "question": "殳", "answers": ["投", "役", "没", "芟", "殴", "股", "段", "疫", "殺", "般", "殷", "設", "殻", "發", "殼", "殿", "搬", "毀", "穀", "廏", "慇", "愨", "槃", "骰", "撃", "盤", "毅", "磐", "潑", "撥", "瘢", "廢", "毆", "穀", "澱", "磬", "繋", "臀", "轂", "燬", "癈", "翳", "聲", "擊", "謦", "癜", "醫", "繫", "醱", "馨", "鑿"] },
		{ "question": "立", "answers": ["位", "辛", "竍", "泣", "拉", "妾", "苙", "竏", "音", "竓", "竕", "倍", "宰", "剖", "竜", "莅", "竚", "站", "竝", "章", "部", "接", "翌", "粒", "陪", "培", "梓", "菩", "笠", "竟", "竡", "翊", "童", "竣", "椄", "焙", "辜", "竢", "竦", "新", "暗", "意", "辞", "滝", "靖", "韵", "碚", "辟", "蒟", "滓", "境", "障", "端", "彰", "辣", "竪", "蔀", "僮", "嶂", "韶", "颯", "竭", "竰", "億", "賠", "憧", "撞", "樟", "僻", "劈", "幟", "幢", "璋", "親", "憶", "薪", "避", "壁", "噺", "篭", "噫", "嬖", "霎", "橦", "縡", "熾", "諳", "瘴", "薜", "薛", "薏", "龍", "辨", "臆", "瞳", "闇", "擘", "檗", "臂", "職", "織", "癖", "璧", "甓", "艟", "鏡", "識", "韻", "襞", "辭", "競", "響", "鐘", "蘗", "蘖", "躄", "辮", "瓣", "譬", "櫱", "躃", "黯", "闢", "霹", "襯", "辯", "鱆", "糱", "響"] },
		{ "question": "元", "answers": ["完", "阮", "芫", "玩", "冠", "院", "莞", "浣", "冦", "寇", "皖", "頑", "翫"] },
		{ "question": "布", "answers": ["希", "怖", "唏", "晞", "欷", "稀", "鯑"] },
		{ "question": "⺧", "answers": ["告", "造", "浩", "晧", "梏", "皓", "窖", "酷", "慥", "誥", "靠", "鵠"] },
		{ "question": "旧", "answers": ["児", "陥", "焔", "稲"] },
		{ "question": "衤", "answers": ["初", "衫", "衿", "衵", "袂", "衲", "衽", "被", "袖", "袗", "袙", "袢", "袒", "袍", "袴", "袷", "袿", "裃", "裄", "袱", "袵", "補", "裕", "裡", "裙", "裎", "裸", "褐", "裾", "褂", "裼", "裲", "裨", "褄", "複", "褌", "褊", "褓", "褝", "褞", "褥", "褫", "褪", "襁", "褸", "褶", "襍", "襌", "襟", "襖", "襠", "襦", "襪", "襭", "襤", "襯", "襴", "襷"] },
		{ "question": "氐", "answers": ["低", "底", "抵", "邸", "柢", "胝", "牴", "砥", "祗", "羝", "詆", "觝", "鴟"] },
		{ "question": "氏", "answers": ["低", "底", "抵", "邸", "昏", "祇", "柢", "胝", "牴", "紙", "砥", "舐", "祗", "婚", "羝", "詆", "觝", "鴟"] },
		{ "question": "奴", "answers": ["努", "呶", "孥", "帑", "弩", "怒", "拏", "駑"] },
		{ "question": "丘", "answers": ["兵", "岳", "邱", "浜", "蚯", "駈", "鋲"] },
		{ "question": "禾", "answers": ["利", "私", "秀", "禿", "委", "和", "季", "科", "秋", "秒", "香", "俐", "秕", "秘", "称", "透", "租", "秩", "倭", "秤", "秦", "悧", "莠", "莉", "秣", "秬", "秧", "乘", "移", "菌", "萎", "梨", "悸", "犁", "税", "程", "痢", "稀", "萩", "黍", "啾", "愀", "湫", "犂", "酥", "稈", "稍", "剩", "稚", "愁", "稔", "稗", "稜", "蜊", "楸", "綉", "矮", "痿", "蓁", "稟", "稠", "種", "穀", "稲", "誘", "榛", "箘", "甃", "稱", "稿", "穂", "稼", "稽", "凜", "黎", "蝌", "銹", "稷", "稻", "穀", "積", "穏", "穎", "穐", "穆", "廩", "懍", "頽", "薐", "臻", "麇", "曆", "歷", "鍬", "黏", "穗", "穫", "穣", "鯏", "魏", "馥", "鞦", "藜", "穢", "穡", "蘇", "瀝", "麕", "穩", "馨", "鰍", "櫪", "龝", "巍", "癧", "癪", "穰", "黐", "靂"] },
		{ "question": "艮", "answers": ["良", "限", "退", "恨", "垠", "很", "狠", "根", "娘", "浪", "狼", "莨", "郞", "眼", "痕", "琅", "朗", "跟", "蜋", "廊", "銀", "腿", "榔", "踉", "瑯", "褪", "墾", "螂", "懇", "艱", "齦"] },
		{ "question": "令", "answers": ["冷", "伶", "苓", "怜", "囹", "玲", "蛉", "聆", "羚", "零", "鈴", "領", "鴒", "澪", "齢", "嶺", "齡"] },
		{ "question": "⺍", "answers": ["労", "学", "栄", "単", "挙", "桜", "悩", "巣", "脳", "蛍", "覚", "営", "弾", "戦", "誉", "禅", "褝", "撹", "蝉", "箪", "獣", "鴬", "厳", "騨", "巌"] },
		{ "question": "匀", "answers": ["均", "鈞", "韵"] },
		{ "question": "勻", "answers": ["均", "鈞", "韵"] },
		{ "question": "以", "answers": ["似", "苡"] },
		{ "question": "半", "answers": ["判", "伴", "拌", "叛", "胖", "畔", "袢", "絆", "鵥"] },
		{ "question": "方", "answers": ["防", "坊", "芳", "妨", "彷", "放", "肪", "房", "於", "枋", "施", "圀", "旅", "倣", "紡", "旃", "旆", "旁", "旄", "舫", "族", "訪", "旋", "唹", "旌", "敖", "淤", "傍", "傲", "旒", "楞", "滂", "蒡", "旗", "嗷", "榜", "膀", "髣", "敷", "魴", "磅", "錺", "熬", "遨", "激", "徼", "閼", "螯", "檄", "謗", "邀", "旛", "贅", "竅", "鯲", "覈", "繳", "邊", "鼇"] },
		{ "question": "糸", "answers": ["系", "糺", "級", "係", "紀", "約", "紅", "糾", "紆", "紂", "紉", "紙", "孫", "素", "純", "納", "紋", "紛", "索", "紡", "紘", "紗", "紐", "紊", "紕", "紜", "細", "組", "終", "経", "紹", "紺", "紳", "累", "絃", "紬", "絅", "紿", "絆", "紵", "紮", "紲", "絵", "給", "結", "絶", "統", "紫", "絡", "絞", "絢", "絳", "絖", "絎", "絣", "絨", "絏", "絮", "葯", "絲", "続", "絹", "継", "綏", "絽", "綉", "絛", "綛", "綟", "經", "緑", "練", "総", "綿", "維", "網", "綱", "緒", "遜", "綻", "綬", "綜", "綴", "緋", "綾", "綺", "綵", "緇", "綽", "綢", "綣", "綸", "綯", "綮", "綰", "綫", "綦", "綠", "線", "潔", "編", "縁", "緩", "緊", "締", "縄", "緬", "緤", "緞", "緘", "緲", "縅", "緝", "緡", "練", "緖", "緣", "縦", "緯", "繁", "縛", "縫", "緻", "縞", "縡", "縟", "縊", "縉", "縋", "縢", "縒", "瘰", "縕", "縣", "績", "縮", "繊", "徽", "繋", "繍", "螺", "縻", "繆", "縹", "縵", "縺", "繃", "縲", "縷", "繈", "總", "縱", "繁", "織", "繕", "繭", "彝", "鯀", "繧", "繚", "繖", "繝", "繦", "繙", "繞", "羂", "繰", "羅", "繡", "繫", "繹", "蘊", "繳", "繪", "繩", "懸", "纂", "繽", "纃", "辮", "繻", "繼", "纏", "騾", "纈", "纐", "纉", "纊", "續", "纒", "轡", "巒", "彎", "蘿", "攣", "欒", "纔", "纓", "邏", "戀", "纖", "變", "纛", "臠", "纘", "蠻", "灣", "鑼", "鑾", "纜", "癴", "鸞"] },
		{ "question": "比", "answers": ["批", "庇", "妣", "屁", "昆", "枇", "皆", "毘", "毗", "砒", "秕", "陛", "紕", "粃", "混", "鹿", "偕", "崑", "菎", "階", "琵", "揩", "棍", "焜", "楷", "蓖", "箆", "諧", "篦", "鯤", "巉", "纔", "讒"] },
		{ "question": "舌", "answers": ["乱", "刮", "舍", "活", "括", "恬", "舐", "甜", "筈", "蛞", "聒", "舒", "話", "辞", "銛", "舖", "憩", "舘", "闊", "濶"] },
		{ "question": "今", "answers": ["含", "吟", "岑", "念", "衿", "矜", "衾", "莟", "陰", "貪", "捻", "唸", "琴", "稔", "蔭", "黔", "頷", "鯰"] },
		{ "question": "去", "answers": ["却", "劫", "法", "怯", "盍", "脚", "琺", "蓋", "溘", "闔"] },
		{ "question": "司", "answers": ["伺", "祠", "笥", "詞", "覗", "飼", "嗣"] },
		{ "question": "冘", "answers": ["沈", "忱", "枕", "眈", "耽", "酖", "鴆"] },
		{ "question": "友", "answers": ["抜", "拔", "爰", "祓", "援", "媛", "跋", "湲", "暖", "煖", "髪", "緩", "魃", "髮", "黻"] },
		{ "question": "毛", "answers": ["尾", "毟", "瓱", "竓", "耗", "粍", "旄", "耄", "梶", "毬", "毫", "毯", "毳", "髦", "麾", "橇", "氈"] },
		{ "question": "古", "answers": ["克", "估", "苦", "固", "居", "姑", "怙", "沽", "故", "枯", "胡", "剋", "個", "倨", "凅", "罟", "据", "做", "蛄", "涸", "湖", "詁", "辜", "裾", "瑚", "鈷", "痼", "適", "箇", "摘", "滴", "嫡", "兢", "敵", "糊", "蝴", "踞", "錮", "鋸", "醐", "鴣", "謫", "餬", "鏑"] },
		{ "question": "兄", "answers": ["克", "兌", "況", "呪", "祝", "党", "悦", "祝", "脱", "税", "蛻", "説", "鋭", "閲", "競"] },
		{ "question": "丰", "answers": ["寿", "邦", "契", "害", "峰", "涛", "峯", "挈", "蚌", "梼", "祷", "逢", "彗", "烽", "喫", "畴", "蜂", "楔", "蓬", "禊", "潔", "鋳", "慧", "鋒", "憲", "縫", "篷", "豐", "齧", "囓", "艷"] },
		{ "question": "三", "answers": ["寿", "邦", "実", "奉", "春", "奏", "契", "害", "峰", "泰", "俸", "秦", "涛", "峯", "挈", "蚌", "梼", "祷", "捧", "逢", "彗", "烽", "菫", "舂", "棒", "喫", "湊", "畴", "僅", "蜂", "椿", "惷", "楔", "蓁", "勤", "榛", "蓬", "禊", "潔", "鋳", "慧", "鋒", "槿", "瑾", "憲", "縫", "輳", "臻", "謹", "懃", "篷", "覲", "豐", "謹", "鰆", "饉", "齧", "蠢", "囓", "艷"] },
		{ "question": "申", "answers": ["伸", "坤", "呻", "抻", "神", "捜", "神", "紳", "痩", "榊", "暢", "鰰"] },
		{ "question": "水", "answers": ["尿", "汞", "沓", "泉", "腺", "楾", "線", "踏", "漿", "盥", "鞜"] },
		{ "question": "厉", "answers": ["励", "砺", "蛎"] },
		{ "question": "万", "answers": ["励", "栃", "砺", "蛎"] },
		{ "question": "左", "answers": ["佐", "惰", "隋", "楕", "墮", "橢", "隨", "髓"] },
		{ "question": "爫", "answers": ["妥", "孚", "受", "乳", "采", "爭", "俘", "爰", "将", "浮", "埒", "奚", "郛", "菜", "採", "授", "彩", "渓", "淫", "婬", "崢", "桴", "殍", "覓", "淨", "援", "揺", "媛", "遥", "湲", "爲", "愛", "暖", "奨", "舜", "蒋", "徭", "蜉", "滔", "瑶", "綏", "艀", "煖", "亂", "搖", "溪", "隠", "稲", "綬", "孵", "箏", "綵", "瑤", "遙", "稱", "緩", "諍", "稻", "謡", "穏", "錚", "餒", "蕣", "靜", "爵", "曖", "醤", "蹊", "蹈", "谿", "謠", "隱", "瞬", "鶏", "瀞", "霪", "穩", "辭", "韜", "鷂", "鷄", "靉"] },
		{ "question": "廴", "answers": ["廷", "延", "廸", "建", "廻", "廼", "庭", "挺", "涎", "莚", "健", "梃", "艇", "蜒", "蜑", "腱", "筵", "蜓", "誕", "霆", "鍵"] },
		{ "question": "戸", "answers": ["戻", "芦", "沪", "所", "肩", "房", "炉", "扁", "扇", "涙", "唳", "捩", "啓", "扈", "雇", "扉", "綟", "煽", "肇", "滬", "綮", "顧"] },
		{ "question": "戶", "answers": ["戻", "芦", "沪", "所", "肩", "房", "炉", "扁", "扇", "唳", "捩", "啓", "偏", "扈", "淚", "雇", "扉", "遍", "綟", "肇", "綮", "褊", "編", "篇", "蝙", "翩", "諞", "騙"] },
		{ "question": "吕", "answers": ["串", "營"] },
		{ "question": "太", "answers": ["汰", "粏", "葢", "駄"] },
		{ "question": "台", "answers": ["冶", "始", "治", "苔", "怡", "抬", "胎", "怠", "殆", "笞", "紿", "詒", "貽", "飴", "颱", "駘"] },
		{ "question": "夭", "answers": ["妖", "沃", "呑", "忝", "殀", "奏", "笑", "添", "喬", "飫", "僑", "蕎", "嬌", "橋", "矯", "轎", "蹻", "驕"] },
		{ "question": "右", "answers": ["佑", "若", "祐", "匿", "祐", "惹", "慝", "諾", "醢", "鰙"] },
		{ "question": "加", "answers": ["伽", "茄", "架", "迦", "枷", "珈", "痂", "袈", "笳", "賀", "跏", "嘉", "駕"] },
		{ "question": "久", "answers": ["灸", "玖", "疚", "粂", "柩", "畝"] },
		{ "question": "了", "answers": ["亨", "亟", "凾", "烹"] },
		{ "question": "牙", "answers": ["冴", "芽", "邪", "穿", "訝", "捓", "谺", "雅", "鴉"] },
		{ "question": "厷", "answers": ["宏", "肱", "紘", "雄"] },
		{ "question": "从", "answers": ["坐", "夾", "巫", "卒", "來", "俠", "座", "挫", "倅", "浹", "陜", "莢", "峽", "挾", "狹", "萊", "悴", "淬", "猝", "萃", "麥", "從", "僉", "筮", "筴", "瘁", "蓙", "碎", "翠", "誣", "覡", "粹", "麪", "匳", "慫", "麩", "樅", "膵", "篋", "鋏", "賚", "齒", "劍", "儉", "醉", "頰", "噬", "嶮", "憖", "麭", "險", "齔", "斂", "臉", "歛", "聳", "縱", "檢", "嚙", "蹤", "瞼", "雜", "麴", "簽", "孅", "懺", "齣", "齟", "齠", "瀲", "齡", "麵", "囃", "齦", "齧", "殲", "齬", "齪", "籡", "籤", "纖", "驗", "鹼", "囓", "齷", "齲", "齶", "讖", "靈"] },
		{ "question": "六", "answers": ["宍", "冥", "幎", "溟", "暝", "瞑", "螟"] },
		{ "question": "屯", "answers": ["沌", "邨", "瓲", "純", "鈍", "頓", "飩", "噸"] },
		{ "question": "分", "answers": ["扮", "吩", "岔", "芬", "忿", "枌", "氛", "盆", "瓰", "竕", "粉", "紛", "貧", "躮", "雰", "頒", "寡", "彜", "釁"] },
		{ "question": "天", "answers": ["吞", "忝", "昊", "送", "奏", "咲", "俣", "癸", "蚕", "朕", "茣", "渕", "葵", "湊", "揆", "虞", "蜈", "関", "誤", "輳", "麌", "鎹"] },
		{ "question": "失", "answers": ["佚", "迭", "帙", "秩", "跌", "軼", "鉄"] },
		{ "question": "句", "answers": ["佝", "劬", "拘", "狗", "苟", "枸", "敬", "鉤", "煦", "蒟", "駒", "檠", "警", "齣", "驚"] },
		{ "question": "它", "answers": ["佗", "陀", "沱", "柁", "蛇", "舵", "詑", "跎", "鉈", "駝", "鴕"] },
		{ "question": "宁", "answers": ["佇", "苧", "竚", "紵", "貯"] },
		{ "question": "㕣", "answers": ["兌", "冏", "沿", "船", "商", "烱", "袞", "鉛", "裔", "滾", "橘", "譎", "鷸"] },
		{ "question": "冊", "answers": ["刪", "柵", "珊", "跚"] },
		{ "question": "召", "answers": ["劭", "招", "沼", "邵", "昭", "迢", "紹", "超", "詔", "貂", "照", "韶", "髫", "齠"] },
		{ "question": "內", "answers": ["吶", "肭", "衲", "納", "蚋", "訥"] },
		{ "question": "爿", "answers": ["妝", "壯", "牀", "狀", "奘", "弉", "莊", "將", "淵", "寐", "肅", "裝", "寤", "寢", "臧", "嘯", "蕭", "牆", "藏", "繡", "瀟", "簫", "贓", "臟"] },
		{ "question": "尤", "answers": ["尨", "肬", "厖", "疣", "就", "稽", "蹴", "鷲"] },
		{ "question": "丑", "answers": ["忸", "狃", "紐", "衄", "羞", "鈕"] },
		{ "question": "厄", "answers": ["扼", "阨", "軛"] },
		{ "question": "爪", "answers": ["抓", "爬", "笊"] },
		{ "question": "斗", "answers": ["抖", "科", "料", "蚪", "斜", "斛", "斟", "斡", "魁", "蝌", "槲"] },
		{ "question": "乏", "answers": ["泛", "貶"] },
		{ "question": "市", "answers": ["沛", "姉", "肺", "柿", "旆", "閙", "鬧"] },
		{ "question": "巿", "answers": ["沛", "姉", "肺", "旆", "閙", "霈", "鬧"] },
		{ "question": "瓦", "answers": ["瓧", "瓩", "瓰", "瓲", "瓮", "瓱", "瓶", "瓷", "瓸", "甄", "甅", "甃", "甍", "甌", "甎", "甑", "甕", "甓"] },
		{ "question": "疒", "answers": ["疔", "疚", "疝", "疫", "疣", "疥", "病", "疲", "疾", "症", "疹", "疳", "痃", "痂", "疸", "疽", "疼", "疱", "痕", "痔", "痍", "疵", "痊", "痒", "痛", "痘", "痢", "痩", "痙", "痞", "痣", "痴", "嫉", "痿", "痾", "痰", "痺", "痼", "痳", "痲", "瘁", "痹", "瘍", "瘧", "瘋", "瘉", "瘟", "瘠", "瘤", "瘢", "瘡", "瘦", "瘰", "瘴", "瘻", "療", "癌", "癇", "癆", "癈", "癘", "癖", "癒", "癜", "癡", "癢", "癧", "癪", "癨", "癩", "癬", "癭", "癰", "癲", "癴"] },
		{ "question": "㓁", "answers": ["罕", "深", "探"] },
		{ "question": "册", "answers": ["删", "珊", "跚"] },
		{ "question": "切", "answers": ["苆", "窃", "砌"] },
		{ "question": "弗", "answers": ["佛", "沸", "彿", "怫", "狒", "拂", "費", "髴"] },
		{ "question": "母", "answers": ["每", "毒", "姆", "拇", "苺", "栂", "袰"] },
		{ "question": "由", "answers": ["画", "油", "宙", "届", "抽", "岫", "迪", "廸", "柚", "冑", "胄", "袖", "娉", "笛", "寅", "紬", "蚰", "舳", "軸", "釉", "聘", "演", "騁", "螾", "鼬"] },
		{ "question": "石", "answers": ["岩", "拓", "妬", "宕", "矼", "研", "砂", "砕", "柘", "斫", "砒", "砌", "破", "砲", "砿", "砥", "砧", "砺", "砠", "砦", "硅", "硬", "硝", "硫", "硯", "硲", "跖", "碁", "碍", "碓", "碇", "碗", "碚", "硼", "碌", "碎", "碑", "磁", "碑", "碩", "碧", "碪", "碣", "確", "磐", "磑", "磋", "碾", "磅", "碼", "磊", "磨", "鮖", "磔", "磬", "磧", "磚", "礁", "磯", "磽", "磴", "礎", "礒", "礑", "礪", "礙", "礦", "礫", "礬", "蠧", "蠹"] },
		{ "question": "玉", "answers": ["国", "宝", "掴", "筺", "瑩", "璧", "璽"] },
		{ "question": "目", "answers": ["直", "具", "盲", "泪", "苜", "県", "相", "省", "看", "盾", "冒", "眉", "盻", "眇", "眈", "眄", "真", "眠", "倶", "俱", "眛", "眩", "眞", "眼", "眺", "惧", "眷", "眥", "眦", "眸", "勖", "着", "帽", "循", "湘", "廂", "渺", "睇", "想", "慎", "睡", "督", "填", "睦", "遁", "楯", "鼎", "嗔", "瑁", "睫", "睨", "睛", "睚", "睥", "算", "槙", "夐", "睹", "箱", "緲", "瞎", "瞑", "瞋", "叡", "瞠", "瞞", "篡", "霜", "瞳", "瞭", "瞥", "簒", "闃", "颶", "濬", "瞰", "瞬", "鎮", "瓊", "瞼", "瞿", "矇", "瞻", "瞽", "顛", "纂", "孀", "矍", "鶪", "懼", "攫", "衢", "矚", "钁"] },
		{ "question": "占", "answers": ["店", "帖", "苫", "拈", "沾", "点", "砧", "站", "粘", "笘", "貼", "覘", "鮎", "霑", "黏", "點"] },
		{ "question": "未", "answers": ["妹", "味", "昧", "耕", "耗", "耙", "耘", "眛", "耜", "寐", "業", "耡", "誄", "魅", "耦", "耨", "鮇", "藉", "釐", "藕", "籍"] },
		{ "question": "永", "answers": ["泳", "咏", "怺", "昶", "詠", "漾", "樣"] },
		{ "question": "耳", "answers": ["取", "茸", "耶", "弭", "恥", "耽", "珥", "耿", "娵", "娶", "掫", "聆", "聊", "陬", "最", "敢", "揖", "葺", "揶", "聒", "聖", "摂", "爺", "椰", "楫", "聘", "聞", "聡", "聟", "輒", "聚", "聢", "趣", "撮", "餌", "諏", "聨", "輙", "緝", "輯", "橄", "厳", "聴", "聯", "聳", "瞰", "聲", "聰", "職", "叢", "聶", "蟶", "巌", "嚴", "囁", "懾", "攝", "聾", "儼", "聽", "巖", "驟", "躡", "廳", "鑷", "顳"] },
		{ "question": "皮", "answers": ["波", "彼", "披", "坡", "陂", "玻", "破", "被", "疲", "皰", "婆", "菠", "跛", "皴", "頗", "鞁", "皹", "皸", "皺", "簸"] },
		{ "question": "央", "answers": ["英", "怏", "映", "殃", "秧", "瑛", "鞅", "鴦", "霙"] },
		{ "question": "㠯", "answers": ["官", "阜", "追", "帥", "師", "菅", "埠", "耜", "棺", "遣", "獅", "管", "槌", "綰", "館", "舘", "篩", "縋", "薛", "鎚", "歸", "蘖", "櫱", "鰤", "譴", "鑓", "糱"] },
		{ "question": "劦", "answers": ["協", "恊", "脅", "脇"] },
		{ "question": "圣", "answers": ["径", "怪", "茎", "経", "軽", "頚"] },
		{ "question": "公", "answers": ["松", "瓮", "翁", "蚣", "衮", "訟", "菘", "頌", "総", "聡", "鬆", "鶲"] },
		{ "question": "付", "answers": ["府", "附", "咐", "坿", "拊", "苻", "柎", "俯", "符", "腑", "腐", "鮒"] },
		{ "question": "列", "answers": ["例", "冽", "洌", "烈", "裂"] },
		{ "question": "襾", "answers": ["価", "要", "票", "覃", "賈", "覆", "覇", "覈"] },
		{ "question": "覀", "answers": ["価", "要", "栗", "票", "粟", "覃", "腰", "慄", "剽", "賈", "漂", "僊", "嫖", "慓", "標", "遷", "潭", "蕈", "價", "篥", "瓢", "縹", "覆", "簟", "覇", "譚", "覈", "飄", "鐔", "驃", "鰾", "鱏", "韆"] },
		{ "question": "龹", "answers": ["券", "卷", "巻", "拳", "倦", "捲", "惓", "眷", "圈", "勝", "圏", "豢", "蜷", "綣", "滕", "縢", "謄", "藤", "騰", "籐", "鰧"] },
		{ "question": "交", "answers": ["効", "佼", "郊", "咬", "狡", "校", "效", "皎", "絞", "傚", "蛟", "較", "餃", "駮", "鮫", "鵁", "纐"] },
		{ "question": "术", "answers": ["述", "術"] },
		{ "question": "朮", "answers": ["述", "術"] },
		{ "question": "生", "answers": ["性", "姓", "星", "牲", "産", "隆", "旌", "笙", "甥", "惺", "猩", "甦", "腥", "醒", "薩", "窿"] },
		{ "question": "片", "answers": ["版", "淵", "牌", "牋", "牒", "肅", "魸", "嘯", "蕭", "繡", "瀟", "簫", "牘"] },
		{ "question": "広", "answers": ["拡", "昿", "砿", "鉱"] },
		{ "question": "共", "answers": ["供", "洪", "巷", "哄", "拱", "恭", "異", "港", "巽", "蛬", "殿", "閧", "選", "暴", "撰", "澱", "冀", "鬨", "翼", "戴", "糞", "臀", "瀑", "癜", "爆", "曝", "饌", "驥"] },
		{ "question": "乎", "answers": ["呼", "罅"] },
		{ "question": "亥", "answers": ["刻", "劾", "咳", "垓", "孩", "核", "該", "骸", "駭"] },
		{ "question": "示", "answers": ["宗", "奈", "祁", "祀", "社", "祇", "祢", "祈", "祉", "祗", "祠", "祚", "祓", "祟", "祕", "神", "祐", "祖", "祝", "祭", "票", "尉", "斎", "崇", "捺", "祷", "淙", "祥", "款", "禄", "棕", "視", "禁", "禅", "蒜", "剽", "禀", "祺", "祿", "漂", "蔚", "榊", "綜", "嫖", "慓", "粽", "禊", "福", "禍", "禎", "標", "慰", "踪", "凛", "熨", "禝", "隷", "禦", "頴", "噤", "瓢", "縹", "禧", "禪", "隸", "襟", "鎺", "禮", "禰", "禱", "鶎", "飄", "鰰", "驃", "鰾", "禳"] },
		{ "question": "孚", "answers": ["乳", "俘", "浮", "郛", "桴", "殍", "蜉", "艀", "孵"] },
		{ "question": "䒑", "answers": ["並", "岡", "羌", "罔", "前", "美", "逆", "姜", "差", "益", "従", "剛", "朔", "恙", "羔", "羞", "剪", "惘", "着", "善", "普", "滋", "揃", "厥", "孳", "業", "義", "慈", "塑", "煎", "羨", "溢", "嵯", "嵳", "溯", "嗟", "搓", "隘", "様", "磁", "網", "綱", "僕", "遡", "瑳", "愬", "槎", "槊", "漾", "養", "儀", "撲", "窯", "蕨", "箭", "磋", "獗", "翦", "樣", "鋼", "縦", "膳", "嶬", "樸", "璞", "縊", "縒", "躾", "羲", "犠", "蹉", "謚", "繕", "魍", "闕", "瀁", "礒", "鎰", "譜", "蟻", "蹶", "蹼", "艤", "羹", "議", "癢", "鱶"] },
		{ "question": "业", "answers": ["並", "晋", "虚", "普", "湿", "黹", "業", "僕", "嘘", "對", "戯", "霊", "撲", "墟", "樸", "歔", "璞", "繊", "黻", "顕", "叢", "譜", "黼", "蹼", "鑿"] },
		{ "question": "衣", "answers": ["依", "哀", "衾", "衮", "袋", "袈", "袞", "袤", "袰", "裁", "装", "裂", "裏", "裟", "裔", "裘", "裝", "製", "裳", "滾", "裹", "裴", "褒", "壊", "嬢", "懐", "壌", "褻", "襄", "襃", "穣", "襞", "懷", "壞", "譲", "醸", "攘", "壤", "孃", "曩", "襲", "禳", "穰", "釀", "讓", "驤"] },
		{ "question": "処", "answers": ["拠", "處"] },
		{ "question": "出", "answers": ["屈", "拙", "咄", "朏", "柮", "倔", "祟", "掘", "堀", "崛", "窟", "黜", "糶"] },
		{ "question": "朿", "answers": ["刺", "策", "棘", "棗", "蕀"] },
		{ "question": "正", "answers": ["征", "政", "柾", "歪", "症", "焉", "証", "鉦", "堽", "整"] },
		{ "question": "至", "answers": ["到", "室", "屋", "姪", "咥", "垤", "致", "倒", "桎", "窒", "握", "渥", "蛭", "幄", "耋", "榁", "腟", "輊", "臺", "膣", "緻", "臻", "擡", "鵄", "薹", "鰘", "齷"] },
		{ "question": "包", "answers": ["抱", "泡", "庖", "咆", "苞", "胞", "枹", "炮", "砲", "袍", "疱", "皰", "匏", "蚫", "萢", "飽", "雹", "鉋", "鞄", "靤", "髱", "鮑", "麭"] },
		{ "question": "区", "answers": ["欧", "殴", "枢", "躯", "駆", "鴎"] },
		{ "question": "圭", "answers": ["佳", "卦", "封", "娃", "哇", "奎", "挂", "桂", "珪", "恚", "掛", "涯", "崖", "畦", "崕", "啀", "硅", "袿", "街", "蛙", "幇", "罫", "褂", "睚", "窪", "閨", "鞋", "鮭", "幫"] },
		{ "question": "寺", "answers": ["侍", "持", "待", "峙", "恃", "時", "特", "痔", "畤", "等", "詩", "蒔", "塒"] },
		{ "question": "升", "answers": ["昇", "枡", "陞"] },
		{ "question": "早", "answers": ["卓", "草", "倬", "章", "悼", "啅", "掉", "棹", "覃", "罩", "障", "彰", "嶂", "綽", "樟", "潭", "璋", "蕈", "瘴", "簟", "譚", "鐔", "鱆", "鱏"] },
		{ "question": "必", "answers": ["泌", "秘", "祕", "密", "瑟", "蜜", "樒", "謐", "櫁"] },
		{ "question": "叧", "answers": ["拐", "枴"] },
		{ "question": "巨", "answers": ["拒", "苣", "炬", "矩", "秬", "距", "渠", "鉅"] },
		{ "question": "玄", "answers": ["弦", "呟", "畜", "眩", "痃", "率", "舷", "牽", "絃", "衒", "滋", "孳", "蓄", "慈", "鉉", "磁"] },
		{ "question": "尗", "answers": ["叔", "俶", "寂", "淑", "戚", "菽", "椒", "督", "槭", "蹙"] },
		{ "question": "上", "answers": ["叔", "峠", "俶", "寂", "淑", "戚", "裃", "菽", "椒", "督", "槭", "鞐", "蹙"] },
		{ "question": "齐", "answers": ["斉", "剤", "済", "斎"] },
		{ "question": "平", "answers": ["坪", "怦", "苹", "秤", "萍", "評", "鮃"] },
		{ "question": "尼", "answers": ["泥", "怩", "昵"] },
		{ "question": "毎", "answers": ["侮", "海", "悔", "梅", "敏", "莓", "晦", "誨", "繁", "繁"] },
		{ "question": "每", "answers": ["侮", "悔", "侮", "梅", "敏", "莓", "悔", "海", "晦", "敏", "梅", "誨", "繁", "繁"] },
		{ "question": "并", "answers": ["併", "剏", "屏", "胼", "迸", "瓶", "塀", "絣", "餅", "駢"] },
		{ "question": "卉", "answers": ["奔", "蠎"] },
		{ "question": "末", "answers": ["抹", "沫", "茉", "秣", "靺"] },
		{ "question": "夗", "answers": ["宛", "苑", "怨", "盌", "婉", "腕", "椀", "碗", "蜿", "豌", "鴛", "鋺"] },
		{ "question": "虍", "answers": ["虎", "虐", "虔", "虒", "虚", "彪", "處", "琥", "虜", "虛", "虞", "虜", "號", "嘘", "遞", "劇", "戯", "膚", "慮", "墟", "褫", "歔", "盧", "篪", "據", "罅", "遽", "虧", "戲", "濾", "廬", "鯱", "蘆", "櫨", "臚", "醵", "獻", "爐", "艫", "饕", "轤", "鑢", "鑪", "顱", "驢", "鱸"] },
		{ "question": "杀", "answers": ["刹", "殺", "弑"] },
		{ "question": "尓", "answers": ["弥", "祢", "称"] },
		{ "question": "尔", "answers": ["弥", "祢", "称"] },
		{ "question": "电", "answers": ["奄", "俺", "亀", "庵", "掩", "淹", "菴", "罨", "縄", "蝿", "穐", "閹", "竃"] },
		{ "question": "仒", "answers": ["於", "唹", "淤", "閼", "鯲"] },
		{ "question": "夹", "answers": ["侠", "狭", "峡", "挟", "頬"] },
		{ "question": "有", "answers": ["肴", "侑", "郁", "宥", "囿", "淆", "随", "堕", "賄", "鮪", "髄"] },
		{ "question": "此", "answers": ["些", "呰", "柴", "砦", "眥", "眦", "疵", "紫", "貲", "觜", "雌", "髭", "嘴"] },
		{ "question": "竹", "answers": ["竺", "竿", "竽", "笑", "笈", "笋", "笏", "笆", "笊", "笄", "第", "笛", "符", "笹", "笥", "笠", "笘", "笞", "笵", "笳", "笨", "笙", "答", "等", "筆", "筋", "策", "筒", "筈", "筑", "筏", "筍", "筌", "筅", "筐", "筬", "筝", "筓", "節", "筺", "筥", "筵", "筧", "筰", "筮", "筱", "筴", "筲", "算", "管", "箇", "箋", "箕", "箔", "箆", "箘", "箜", "箍", "箝", "箒", "箏", "箚", "箙", "劄", "箱", "範", "箸", "箭", "箪", "篇", "篁", "篌", "篆", "篋", "箴", "節", "築", "篤", "篦", "篭", "噬", "篝", "篩", "篥", "簑", "篡", "篪", "篠", "簒", "簔", "篷", "簍", "簓", "簇", "簀", "簗", "篳", "簡", "簞", "簣", "簧", "簟", "簿", "櫛", "簸", "簾", "簷", "簽", "簫", "籀", "籍", "纂", "簪", "籌", "籃", "籔", "籐", "籖", "籒", "籠", "籟", "籡", "籙", "籥", "籤", "籬"] },
		{ "question": "代", "answers": ["岱", "玳", "袋", "貸", "黛"] },
		{ "question": "免", "answers": ["兔", "俛", "勉", "勉", "挽", "娩", "冤", "逸", "冕", "寃", "晚", "晩", "菟", "逸", "輓", "鮸", "巉", "纔", "讒"] },
		{ "question": "矛", "answers": ["茅", "柔", "矜", "務", "袤", "揉", "糅", "橘", "蹂", "懋", "鞣", "霧", "譎", "鶩", "鷸"] },
		{ "question": "吅", "answers": ["咒", "品", "咢", "哭", "區", "喪", "嵒", "愕", "鄂", "萼", "單", "傴", "僉", "嘔", "嫗", "嶇", "器", "匳", "嬋", "憚", "鄲", "劍", "儉", "彈", "樞", "歐", "毆", "操", "噪", "嶮", "懆", "澡", "甌", "諤", "殫", "戰", "險", "器", "燥", "鍔", "癌", "斂", "臉", "歛", "襄", "襌", "禪", "檢", "臨", "顎", "簞", "蟬", "軀", "謳", "瞼", "繰", "藻", "簽", "勸", "獸", "鰐", "灌", "懽", "攘", "鶚", "闡", "躁", "瀲", "譟", "壤", "嚴", "孃", "囂", "曩", "權", "歡", "驅", "鷗", "驒", "囊", "儼", "禳", "籡", "穰", "鱓", "巖", "罐", "驗", "鹼", "齶", "讙", "釀", "觀", "讓", "鑵", "顴", "驤", "驩", "鸛"] },
		{ "question": "北", "answers": ["乖", "背", "乘", "剩", "燕", "冀", "嚥", "臙", "讌", "驥"] },
		{ "question": "叹", "answers": ["亟", "凾", "極"] },
		{ "question": "吉", "answers": ["佶", "劼", "拮", "桔", "結", "詰", "臺", "頡", "髻", "擡", "薹", "黠", "襭", "纈"] },
		{ "question": "多", "answers": ["侈", "移", "夥"] },
		{ "question": "朱", "answers": ["侏", "茱", "株", "殊", "珠", "蛛", "誅", "銖"] },
		{ "question": "宅", "answers": ["侘", "咤", "詫"] },
		{ "question": "兆", "answers": ["佻", "逃", "挑", "姚", "桃", "晁", "眺", "窕", "跳", "誂", "銚"] },
		{ "question": "帀", "answers": ["佩", "師", "珮", "獅", "魳", "篩", "衞", "鰤"] },
		{ "question": "百", "answers": ["佰", "陌", "宿", "瓸", "竡", "弼", "粨", "貊", "蓿", "縮"] },
		{ "question": "羊", "answers": ["佯", "洋", "庠", "祥", "羝", "羚", "痒", "祥", "達", "善", "遅", "翔", "群", "詳", "羯", "膳", "撻", "鮮", "燵", "繕", "羶", "羸", "蘚", "闥", "韃", "癬"] },
		{ "question": "任", "answers": ["凭", "荏", "姙", "恁", "袵", "賃"] },
		{ "question": "夸", "answers": ["刳", "胯", "袴", "匏", "瓠", "誇", "跨"] },
		{ "question": "甘", "answers": ["坩", "拑", "邯", "某", "柑", "疳", "紺", "甜", "蚶", "媒", "嵌", "酣", "楳", "煤", "鉗", "箝", "謀"] },
		{ "question": "㣺", "answers": ["忝", "恭", "添", "慕"] },
		{ "question": "幼", "answers": ["拗", "窈", "黝"] },
		{ "question": "斥", "answers": ["拆", "泝", "柝", "訴"] },
		{ "question": "䖝", "answers": ["虱", "風", "嵐", "颪", "楓", "颯", "颱", "瘋", "諷", "颶", "飄", "飆"] },
		{ "question": "虫", "answers": ["虱", "風", "独", "虹", "虻", "蚕", "蚊", "蚤", "蚓", "蚪", "蚌", "蚩", "蚣", "蚋", "強", "蛍", "蛇", "掻", "蛋", "蛎", "蛄", "蚰", "蛉", "蚯", "蚶", "蚫", "蛆", "蛮", "嵐", "蛙", "蛤", "蛭", "蛛", "蛞", "蛬", "蛩", "蛯", "蛔", "蛟", "颪", "触", "蜂", "蛾", "蛸", "楓", "搔", "蜎", "嗤", "蜒", "蜉", "蜀", "蛻", "蜊", "蜍", "蜈", "蛹", "蜑", "蜆", "蜃", "蜹", "蜋", "蜓", "蜜", "蜘", "蝋", "蜴", "蜿", "蜚", "蜥", "蜻", "蜩", "蜷", "颯", "颱", "瘋", "蝦", "蝕", "蝉", "蝶", "蝿", "蝱", "蝨", "蝠", "蝮", "蝌", "蝴", "蝙", "蝓", "蝗", "蝟", "蝎", "蝣", "蝸", "蟒", "蝘", "蝲", "濁", "融", "蟇", "蟆", "螂", "螟", "諷", "襁", "螈", "螗", "螢", "獨", "燭", "螺", "蟋", "螽", "螳", "蟀", "螯", "螻", "螫", "蟄", "蠎", "颶", "雖", "繈", "螾", "蟎", "騒", "繭", "蟬", "蟠", "蟯", "櫁", "繦", "蟪", "蟲", "蟹", "蟻", "蠅", "蠏", "蠍", "蟾", "蟶", "蟷", "蠖", "蠆", "蠊", "蠣", "蠕", "蠑", "躅", "飄", "觸", "騷", "蠟", "蠢", "蠡", "飆", "屬", "蠧", "蠱", "髑", "蠹", "蠻", "蠶"] },
		{ "question": "内", "answers": ["肭", "衲", "納", "蚋", "訥", "蜹"] },
		{ "question": "四", "answers": ["泗", "駟"] },
		{ "question": "世", "answers": ["泄", "笹", "紲", "葉", "貰", "喋", "渫", "牒", "蝶", "緤", "諜", "鰈"] },
		{ "question": "囚", "answers": ["泅", "媼", "慍", "溫", "膃", "褞", "瘟", "薀", "縕", "饂", "蘊", "韞", "鰮"] },
		{ "question": "民", "answers": ["泯", "氓", "眠", "罠", "愍", "緡"] },
		{ "question": "車", "answers": ["軋", "軍", "軌", "俥", "庫", "連", "軒", "陣", "転", "軟", "斬", "軛", "運", "軽", "揮", "軸", "渾", "軻", "軫", "軼", "葷", "較", "載", "蓮", "暈", "暉", "軾", "輅", "輊", "輌", "輀", "漸", "輔", "漣", "塹", "嶄", "慚", "輒", "輓", "褌", "皹", "皸", "輕", "輪", "輝", "撃", "輩", "範", "暫", "慙", "槧", "輙", "輟", "輜", "輦", "輛", "輸", "輯", "輻", "輹", "輳", "諢", "轄", "繋", "輿", "轅", "轂", "輾", "縺", "擊", "轆", "轌", "轉", "轍", "繫", "轎", "鏈", "鏨", "鶤", "轗", "轟", "囀", "轜", "轡", "轢", "轤"] },
		{ "question": "⺷", "answers": ["羌", "美", "姜", "恙", "羔", "羞", "義", "羨", "漾", "養", "儀", "窯", "樣", "嶬", "躾", "羲", "犠", "瀁", "礒", "蟻", "艤", "羹", "議", "癢", "鱶"] },
		{ "question": "米", "answers": ["籵", "迷", "粁", "粂", "籾", "屎", "粉", "料", "粋", "粍", "粃", "粏", "氣", "断", "釈", "粒", "菊", "粗", "粘", "掬", "悉", "粕", "番", "歯", "奥", "粧", "粥", "粟", "屡", "椈", "粢", "粤", "粨", "釉", "数", "継", "楼", "愾", "粱", "粳", "粲", "糀", "奧", "精", "粽", "粹", "審", "麹", "糊", "噛", "糎", "播", "幡", "蕃", "潘", "糅", "糂", "糖", "隣", "薮", "憐", "彜", "懊", "膰", "澳", "燔", "糒", "鄰", "齢", "謎", "鞠", "糠", "燦", "糟", "糞", "燐", "蟋", "麋", "燠", "糜", "糝", "類", "藩", "翻", "糧", "襖", "彝", "旛", "蟠", "瀋", "繙", "麴", "類", "糯", "糲", "釋", "飜", "糴", "鬻", "驎", "糱", "竊", "鷭", "鱗", "麟", "糶"] },
		{ "question": "冬", "answers": ["苳", "柊", "疼", "終", "鮗", "螽", "鼕"] },
		{ "question": "氾", "answers": ["范", "笵"] },
		{ "question": "卯", "answers": ["茆", "柳", "昴", "聊", "霤"] },
		{ "question": "刅", "answers": ["刱", "梁", "粱", "簗"] },
		{ "question": "血", "answers": ["卹", "恤", "洫", "衄", "衆"] },
		{ "question": "臼", "answers": ["兒", "臾", "舁", "倪", "叟", "啗", "猊", "舂", "埳", "陷", "焰", "嫂", "萸", "搜", "插", "毀", "鼠", "腴", "滔", "溲", "歃", "睨", "舅", "潟", "諂", "諛", "貎", "寫", "稻", "瘦", "閻", "霓", "艘", "蹈", "燬", "餡", "舊", "瀉", "鬩", "鯢", "麑", "韜", "鑿"] },
		{ "question": "犮", "answers": ["拔", "祓", "跋", "魃", "髮", "黻"] },
		{ "question": "言", "answers": ["計", "信", "訂", "訃", "記", "訓", "討", "託", "訊", "訖", "訌", "訐", "許", "設", "訪", "訳", "訟", "訣", "這", "訛", "訝", "訥", "証", "評", "詞", "訴", "詠", "詐", "詔", "診", "詑", "註", "詛", "詈", "訶", "詁", "詆", "詒", "話", "詩", "試", "誠", "詰", "誇", "詳", "誉", "該", "詣", "詮", "詫", "詭", "詢", "誄", "詬", "誅", "誂", "詼", "語", "読", "説", "誤", "誌", "認", "罰", "獄", "誘", "誓", "滸", "誨", "誡", "誣", "誦", "誚", "誑", "誥", "談", "調", "課", "諸", "誕", "論", "請", "諾", "謁", "誰", "諌", "誼", "諏", "誹", "諒", "諄", "諚", "諍", "諂", "諛", "謡", "諮", "謀", "諭", "諧", "諦", "謂", "諫", "諺", "諜", "憺", "澹", "諤", "諠", "諢", "謔", "諞", "諳", "諷", "諡", "擔", "諸", "謁", "講", "謝", "謹", "謙", "謄", "謎", "謌", "燮", "檐", "謚", "諱", "謇", "謐", "謗", "謖", "謨", "譁", "嶽", "膽", "謠", "儲", "謬", "謦", "謾", "鞫", "謳", "謫", "瞻", "謹", "識", "警", "譜", "藷", "蟾", "簷", "譌", "譚", "譏", "譎", "譛", "藹", "證", "議", "護", "譲", "譫", "譬", "譟", "贍", "譯", "譽", "譖", "譴", "辯", "讃", "巒", "彎", "讀", "攣", "欒", "讌", "讐", "讎", "戀", "變", "靄", "讙", "讖", "讒", "讓", "臠", "蠻", "灣", "讚", "鑾", "癴", "鸞"] },
		{ "question": "自", "answers": ["首", "臭", "夏", "息", "臭", "戛", "馗", "道", "厦", "嗅", "嗄", "廈", "鼻", "榎", "熄", "導", "憩", "嚊", "嬶", "鼾", "馘", "邊"] },
		{ "question": "刖", "answers": ["前", "俞", "剪", "愉", "揃", "揄", "渝", "煎", "愈", "瑜", "逾", "榆", "瘉", "箭", "蝓", "翦", "輸", "諭", "踰", "覦", "鍮"] },
		{ "question": "灬", "answers": ["点", "為", "烈", "烋", "烝", "羔", "魚", "黒", "庶", "烹", "然", "無", "煮", "焦", "爲", "黑", "照", "蒸", "煎", "煦", "魞", "煮", "漁", "墨", "遮", "熊", "煕", "熏", "蔗", "盡", "熱", "熟", "黙", "潟", "勲", "窯", "蕉", "魯", "憔", "魴", "熙", "熈", "熬", "魳", "魸", "魬", "寫", "墨", "薫", "燕", "樵", "儘", "黛", "鮎", "鮒", "黔", "鮃", "鮓", "鮑", "鮗", "鮖", "熹", "薊", "鮇", "默", "鮮", "礁", "鮪", "鮭", "鮫", "黜", "黝", "鮟", "鮨", "鮠", "鮴", "隰", "鮱", "點", "濕", "鯉", "黠", "鯀", "鯊", "鯒", "鯑", "鯏", "鮹", "蹠", "瀉", "燼", "鯎", "鮸", "鯨", "鯖", "蘇", "鯵", "鯛", "櫓", "嚥", "鯣", "鯢", "鯤", "鯲", "鯡", "鯔", "鯱", "鯰", "羹", "羆", "鰙", "鰐", "鰍", "黥", "鰓", "鰉", "鰔", "鰕", "鰌", "鰈", "鰆", "鰒", "鰊", "鰄", "鰛", "臙", "蘚", "壥", "鰚", "鰘", "黨", "鰯", "鰭", "黯", "鰮", "鰥", "鰤", "鰰", "艪", "贐", "鰧", "鱈", "鰺", "纒", "鰻", "儻", "鷓", "鱆", "鱇", "鰾", "癬", "鰹", "鱒", "黴", "鷦", "鱚", "讌", "鱛", "鱏", "鱓", "顯", "鱗", "鱠", "鱧", "鱟", "鱩", "黶", "鱶", "鱲", "黷", "鱸"] },
		{ "question": "各", "answers": ["客", "洛", "恪", "挌", "狢", "格", "珞", "烙", "略", "落", "絡", "喀", "路", "酪", "賂", "輅", "貉", "閣", "蕗", "駱", "骼", "擱", "額", "露", "鷺"] },
		{ "question": "系", "answers": ["係", "孫", "遜", "縣", "鯀", "懸", "纛"] },
		{ "question": "旨", "answers": ["指", "脂", "詣", "嘗", "稽", "鮨"] },
		{ "question": "合", "answers": ["拾", "姶", "恰", "哈", "洽", "荅", "拿", "袷", "剳", "盒", "答", "給", "塔", "搭", "蛤", "翕", "閤", "箚", "劄", "歙", "鴿", "鞳", "龕"] },
		{ "question": "关", "answers": ["送", "咲", "朕", "渕", "関", "鎹"] },
		{ "question": "灰", "answers": ["炭", "恢", "詼"] },
		{ "question": "癶", "answers": ["発", "癸", "登", "廃", "葵", "溌", "揆", "發", "澄", "潑", "嶝", "撥", "廢", "醗", "橙", "燈", "磴", "癈", "醱", "證", "鐙"] },
		{ "question": "貝", "answers": ["負", "則", "貞", "員", "財", "貢", "唄", "狽", "屓", "貨", "側", "敗", "責", "貧", "販", "貫", "偵", "貪", "貶", "厠", "買", "貯", "費", "賀", "測", "貸", "貿", "貴", "貼", "貰", "幀", "廁", "惻", "貽", "賁", "貳", "資", "損", "賃", "債", "賊", "賄", "賂", "賎", "禎", "勣", "隕", "賈", "貲", "遉", "圓", "慣", "漬", "賑", "匱", "嘖", "槓", "瑣", "熕", "殞", "實", "禎", "賓", "賞", "賛", "質", "遺", "賦", "噴", "墳", "賜", "賠", "賓", "憤", "潰", "賤", "濆", "賚", "價", "賣", "積", "賢", "賭", "膩", "磧", "赬", "賴", "績", "購", "償", "嬰", "嬪", "擯", "簀", "賻", "賽", "賺", "濱", "鎖", "贈", "蹟", "瀆", "攅", "鵙", "櫃", "檳", "濺", "簣", "殯", "贄", "贅", "韻", "贋", "嬾", "懶", "犢", "牘", "獺", "藾", "贇", "贊", "贈", "瀨", "嚶", "罌", "繽", "贍", "贏", "竇", "寶", "齎", "瓔", "纉", "癪", "癩", "饋", "贔", "贐", "櫻", "續", "讃", "躓", "籟", "覿", "贓", "贖", "攢", "癭", "讀", "鑚", "纓", "鬢", "屭", "纘", "讚", "黷", "鑽", "鸚"] },
		{ "question": "囬", "answers": ["面", "湎", "靤", "緬", "麺", "靦", "麵", "靨"] },
		{ "question": "刑", "answers": ["型", "荊"] },
		{ "question": "聿", "answers": ["建", "律", "津", "書", "健", "庸", "晝", "筆", "葎", "畫", "傭", "腱", "肄", "肆", "劃", "肇", "慵", "鍵"] },
		{ "question": "㦮", "answers": ["浅", "残", "桟", "践", "賎", "銭"] },
		{ "question": "亦", "answers": ["変", "奕", "弯", "恋", "迹", "蛮", "湾", "跡"] },
		{ "question": "更", "answers": ["便", "哽", "梗", "硬", "甦", "粳", "鞭"] },
		{ "question": "甬", "answers": ["勇", "俑", "通", "涌", "桶", "痛", "蛹", "踊", "慂", "誦", "樋", "鯒"] },
		{ "question": "用", "answers": ["勇", "俑", "通", "涌", "桶", "備", "痛", "蛹", "踊", "慂", "誦", "樋", "憊", "糒", "鯒", "鞴"] },
		{ "question": "屰", "answers": ["逆", "朔", "厥", "塑", "溯", "遡", "愬", "槊", "蕨", "獗", "闕", "蹶"] },
		{ "question": "呆", "answers": ["保", "堡", "棠", "葆", "褓", "褒", "襃"] },
		{ "question": "龵", "answers": ["看", "拜", "湃"] },
		{ "question": "次", "answers": ["姿", "茨", "咨", "恣", "盗", "瓷", "粢", "資", "諮", "懿"] },
		{ "question": "成", "answers": ["城", "晟", "盛", "筬", "誠", "鯎"] },
		{ "question": "亘", "answers": ["宣", "恒", "垣", "姮", "桓", "萱", "喧", "愃", "暄", "諠", "鰚"] },
		{ "question": "先", "answers": ["洗", "筅", "跣", "銑", "贊", "攢", "纘", "讚", "鑽"] },
		{ "question": "戌", "answers": ["威", "咸", "減", "喊", "感", "歳", "滅", "蔑", "箴", "緘", "縅", "憾", "撼", "鍼", "鰔", "鰄", "鹹", "轗"] },
		{ "question": "巟", "answers": ["荒", "慌"] },
		{ "question": "谷", "answers": ["俗", "卻", "浴", "容", "峪", "郤", "欲", "逧", "裕", "硲", "谺", "溶", "蓉", "熔", "榕", "慾", "壑", "豁", "谿", "鎔"] },
		{ "question": "而", "answers": ["耐", "喘", "惴", "揣", "湍", "猯", "瑞", "輀", "需", "端", "儒", "嬬", "濡", "孺", "懦", "臑", "襦", "蠕", "繻", "糯", "轜", "顬"] },
		{ "question": "㐱", "answers": ["珍", "殄", "疹", "袗", "畛", "參", "診", "軫", "趁", "勠", "寥", "廖", "摎", "滲", "蓼", "蔘", "慘", "戮", "樛", "膠", "繆", "糝", "謬", "醪", "餮", "鏐", "驂", "鰺"] },
		{ "question": "下", "answers": ["峠", "雫", "梺", "裃", "颪", "鞐"] },
		{ "question": "丙", "answers": ["柄", "炳", "陋", "病", "鞆"] },
		{ "question": "冃", "answers": ["冒", "冑", "冕", "曼", "厭", "壓", "靨", "魘", "黶"] },
		{ "question": "㓞", "answers": ["契", "挈", "喫", "楔", "禊", "潔", "齧", "囓"] },
		{ "question": "瓜", "answers": ["弧", "孤", "狐", "呱", "菰", "瓠", "觚", "瓢", "瓣"] },
		{ "question": "肖", "answers": ["削", "消", "宵", "哨", "屑", "峭", "悄", "梢", "逍", "硝", "稍", "蛸", "筲", "誚", "趙", "霄", "銷", "鞘", "鮹"] },
		{ "question": "足", "answers": ["促", "捉", "跂", "趺", "趾", "距", "跏", "跖", "跌", "跚", "跛", "跋", "跎", "路", "跡", "跳", "践", "跨", "跟", "跣", "跪", "跫", "踊", "跼", "跿", "踉", "踏", "踪", "踝", "踟", "踞", "踑", "踐", "蹄", "蕗", "蹂", "踵", "踰", "踴", "蹊", "蹉", "蹌", "蹇", "蹐", "蹈", "蹟", "蹙", "蹠", "蹣", "蹤", "蹕", "蹴", "蹶", "蹲", "蹼", "躇", "蹻", "躅", "躄", "躁", "躃", "躍", "露", "躋", "躊", "齪", "躓", "躑", "躔", "躙", "鷺", "躡", "躪"] },
		{ "question": "甶", "answers": ["卑", "俾", "婢", "牌", "脾", "稗", "裨", "睥", "痺", "碑", "髀", "鵯", "顰"] },
		{ "question": "走", "answers": ["赴", "起", "徒", "赳", "越", "超", "趁", "跿", "趙", "趣", "趨"] },
		{ "question": "里", "answers": ["厘", "俚", "埋", "哩", "浬", "狸", "黒", "野", "理", "童", "量", "裡", "裏", "墨", "僮", "墅", "甅", "竰", "黙", "憧", "撞", "糎", "幢", "廛", "黛", "橦", "瞳", "糧", "鯉", "釐", "艟", "鐘", "纏", "霾", "躔"] },
		{ "question": "因", "answers": ["姻", "咽", "茵", "恩", "烟"] },
		{ "question": "考", "answers": ["拷", "栲"] },
		{ "question": "夋", "answers": ["俊", "唆", "峻", "悛", "浚", "梭", "逡", "竣", "皴", "酸", "駿"] },
		{ "question": "余", "answers": ["叙", "除", "途", "徐", "荼", "斜", "敍", "畭", "畬", "塗", "蜍", "餘"] },
		{ "question": "争", "answers": ["浄", "筝", "静", "諍", "錚", "瀞"] },
		{ "question": "壮", "answers": ["荘", "装"] },
		{ "question": "束", "answers": ["勅", "剌", "速", "悚", "敕", "疎", "喇", "溂", "竦", "辣", "嗽", "嫩", "漱", "蝲", "整", "頼", "賴", "瀬", "嬾", "懶", "獺", "藾", "瀨", "癩", "籟"] },
		{ "question": "同", "answers": ["洞", "恫", "胴", "桐", "筒", "銅", "興", "釁", "爨"] },
		{ "question": "式", "answers": ["拭", "弑", "試", "軾"] },
		{ "question": "孛", "answers": ["勃", "悖"] },
		{ "question": "呂", "answers": ["侶", "宮", "梠", "営", "筥", "絽", "閭", "營", "麿", "櫚"] },
		{ "question": "安", "answers": ["按", "案", "晏", "鞍", "鮟"] },
		{ "question": "回", "answers": ["廻", "徊", "茴", "迴", "蛔", "亶", "嗇", "稟", "禀", "鄙", "圖", "凜", "凛", "壇", "廩", "懍", "擅", "薔", "墻", "檀", "氈", "檣", "牆", "穡", "艢", "羶", "顫"] },
		{ "question": "曳", "answers": ["洩", "絏"] },
		{ "question": "我", "answers": ["俄", "峨", "峩", "哦", "娥", "莪", "義", "蛾", "儀", "餓", "嶬", "犠", "鵝", "鵞", "礒", "蟻", "艤", "議"] },
		{ "question": "臣", "answers": ["臥", "姫", "宦", "堅", "腎", "竪", "蔵", "監", "緊", "慳", "熈", "臧", "賢", "樫", "豎", "覧", "臨", "藏", "臓", "鏗", "贓", "臟", "覽", "鰹", "鑒", "鹽"] },
		{ "question": "后", "answers": ["垢", "逅", "詬"] },
		{ "question": "产", "answers": ["彦", "産", "偐", "諺", "顔"] },
		{ "question": "死", "answers": ["屍", "葬", "薨", "斃"] },
		{ "question": "州", "answers": ["洲", "酬"] },
		{ "question": "酉", "answers": ["酋", "酊", "酒", "配", "酌", "酎", "酔", "酖", "逎", "尊", "酢", "猶", "奠", "酣", "酥", "酬", "酪", "楢", "猷", "酩", "遒", "酸", "酵", "酷", "酲", "酳", "遵", "醇", "鄭", "噂", "醋", "醂", "蕕", "醉", "醒", "醐", "樽", "醍", "醗", "醜", "醤", "醢", "醬", "擲", "醪", "醫", "醱", "蹲", "醯", "醸", "鰌", "醵", "醴", "醺", "躑", "鱒", "釀", "釁"] },
		{ "question": "引", "answers": ["矧", "蚓"] },
		{ "question": "西", "answers": ["茜", "廼", "哂", "洒", "晒", "栖", "迺", "堙", "湮", "煙", "甄"] },
		{ "question": "弟", "answers": ["剃", "俤", "悌", "涕", "梯", "睇", "鵜"] },
		{ "question": "老", "answers": ["姥", "耆", "耄", "蛯", "耋", "嗜", "蓍", "鮱", "鰭"] },
		{ "question": "吴", "answers": ["俣", "茣", "虞", "蜈", "誤", "麌"] },
		{ "question": "夾", "answers": ["俠", "浹", "陜", "莢", "峽", "挾", "狹", "筴", "篋", "鋏", "頰"] },
		{ "question": "見", "answers": ["俔", "規", "現", "視", "覓", "覚", "硯", "覗", "覘", "視", "寛", "蜆", "筧", "覡", "寬", "撹", "槻", "親", "窺", "靦", "覦", "覩", "覧", "覯", "覬", "観", "覲", "覺", "襯", "覿", "覽", "攪", "觀"] },
		{ "question": "矣", "answers": ["俟", "挨", "埃", "欸", "竢"] },
		{ "question": "仌", "answers": ["俎", "傘"] },
		{ "question": "利", "answers": ["俐", "悧", "莉", "梨", "犁", "痢", "蜊", "鯏"] },
		{ "question": "幷", "answers": ["剏", "屛", "絣", "腁", "逬", "餠", "騈"] },
		{ "question": "巠", "answers": ["剄", "勁", "徑", "莖", "脛", "逕", "痙", "經", "輕", "頸"] },
		{ "question": "克", "answers": ["剋", "兢"] },
		{ "question": "甫", "answers": ["匍", "捕", "浦", "哺", "圃", "脯", "逋", "博", "補", "葡", "傅", "蒲", "搏", "溥", "輔", "榑", "膊", "敷", "舗", "鋪", "舖", "薄", "縛", "餔", "賻", "簿", "黼"] },
		{ "question": "只", "answers": ["咫", "枳"] },
		{ "question": "夷", "answers": ["姨", "洟", "痍", "銕"] },
		{ "question": "旬", "answers": ["徇", "恂", "洵", "荀", "殉", "絢", "筍", "詢"] },
		{ "question": "匆", "answers": ["怱", "偬", "葱"] },
		{ "question": "匈", "answers": ["恟", "洶", "胸"] },
		{ "question": "光", "answers": ["恍", "洸", "晃", "胱", "絖", "幌", "滉", "觥", "輝", "耀"] },
		{ "question": "手", "answers": ["拏", "挙", "拳", "拿", "挈", "掌", "掣", "搴", "撃", "摩", "摯", "擘", "擧", "擊", "攀", "欅", "襷", "攣", "癴"] },
		{ "question": "丞", "answers": ["拯", "烝", "蒸"] },
		{ "question": "存", "answers": ["拵", "荐", "栫"] },
		{ "question": "門", "answers": ["閂", "閃", "們", "問", "閉", "捫", "閊", "間", "開", "閑", "閏", "悶", "閔", "椚", "閘", "閙", "聞", "関", "閣", "閥", "閤", "閨", "閧", "閲", "潤", "澗", "㵎", "嫺", "嫻", "憫", "閭", "閻", "閼", "閹", "閾", "燗", "闇", "擱", "闊", "濶", "闃", "闍", "闌", "癇", "簡", "闘", "闖", "闔", "闕", "繝", "蘭", "櫚", "藺", "關", "欄", "闡", "瀾", "闢", "闥", "爛", "欄", "襴", "躙", "躪"] },
		{ "question": "缶", "answers": ["缸", "缺", "陶", "淘", "萄", "掏", "徭", "搖", "綯", "瑤", "遙", "罅", "謠", "罌", "寶", "鷂", "罍", "罎", "罐", "鬱"] },
		{ "question": "疋", "answers": ["胥", "旋", "蛋", "婿", "疎", "疏", "壻", "楚", "疑", "蔬", "凝", "擬", "嚏", "嶷", "礎", "礙", "癡"] },
		{ "question": "匃", "answers": ["曷", "偈", "葛", "揭", "渴", "歇", "遏", "碣", "竭", "蝎", "羯", "謁", "鞨", "蠍", "藹", "靄"] },
		{ "question": "亾", "answers": ["曷", "偈", "葛", "揭", "渴", "歇", "遏", "碣", "竭", "蝎", "羯", "謁", "鞨", "蠍", "藹", "靄"] },
		{ "question": "兮", "answers": ["盻", "諡"] },
		{ "question": "丏", "answers": ["眄", "麪"] },
		{ "question": "伏", "answers": ["茯", "袱"] },
		{ "question": "如", "answers": ["茹", "恕", "絮"] },
		{ "question": "名", "answers": ["茗", "酩", "銘"] },
		{ "question": "行", "answers": ["衍", "桁", "術", "裄", "衒", "街", "絎", "愆", "衙", "銜", "衝", "衛", "衡", "衞", "鵆", "衢"] },
		{ "question": "罒", "answers": ["罘", "罠", "罟", "曼", "買", "詈", "置", "罪", "夢", "署", "罫", "堽", "蜀", "楞", "罧", "罨", "罩", "徳", "罰", "漫", "慢", "蔑", "蔓", "幔", "睾", "署", "罷", "罵", "儚", "甍", "賣", "德", "憲", "壊", "濁", "懐", "懌", "薨", "罹", "澤", "擇", "獨", "聴", "爵", "曙", "薯", "燭", "縵", "瀆", "擺", "謾", "羂", "羃", "羅", "鏝", "繹", "犢", "牘", "襪", "羆", "懷", "壞", "躅", "饅", "竇", "譯", "觸", "釋", "鐸", "鰥", "鬘", "續", "屬", "鰻", "蘿", "覿", "贖", "羇", "聽", "覽", "讀", "鑒", "髑", "韈", "邏", "驛", "羈", "廳", "黷", "鑼"] },
		{ "question": "者", "answers": ["者", "都", "著", "渚", "猪", "偖", "暑", "煮", "堵", "奢", "屠", "猪", "都", "渚", "著", "署", "楮", "暑", "煮", "緒", "睹", "署", "諸", "箸", "潴", "緖", "賭", "赭", "覩", "諸", "曙", "薯", "闍", "儲", "藷", "瀦", "躇"] },
		{ "question": "皀", "answers": ["卽", "卿", "喞", "節", "慨", "厩", "廐", "廏", "漑", "曁"] },
		{ "question": "豕", "answers": ["家", "逐", "啄", "冢", "豚", "琢", "隊", "遂", "塚", "琢", "嫁", "蒙", "溷", "豢", "豪", "劇", "墜", "稼", "毅", "遯", "濛", "隧", "據", "壕", "濠", "朦", "曚", "檬", "燧", "遽", "燹", "矇", "邃", "瀦", "艨", "醵"] },
		{ "question": "帚", "answers": ["帰", "婦", "掃", "箒", "歸"] },
		{ "question": "完", "answers": ["院", "莞", "浣", "皖"] },
		{ "question": "具", "answers": ["真", "倶", "俱", "惧", "慎", "填", "嗔", "槙", "瞋", "颶", "鎮", "顛"] },
		{ "question": "廷", "answers": ["庭", "挺", "梃", "艇", "蜓", "霆"] },
		{ "question": "咅", "answers": ["倍", "剖", "部", "陪", "培", "菩", "焙", "碚", "蔀", "賠"] },
		{ "question": "㐬", "answers": ["流", "琉", "梳", "硫", "疏", "旒", "蔬", "醯"] },
		{ "question": "兴", "answers": ["挙", "誉"] },
		{ "question": "君", "answers": ["郡", "裙", "窘", "群"] },
		{ "question": "舟", "answers": ["航", "般", "舫", "船", "舶", "舷", "舵", "舸", "舳", "搬", "艇", "艀", "槃", "盤", "磐", "瘢", "艘", "艙", "艚", "艝", "艟", "艤", "艢", "艨", "艦", "艪", "艫"] },
		{ "question": "昔", "answers": ["借", "惜", "措", "醋", "錯", "藉", "鵲", "籍"] },
		{ "question": "丗", "answers": ["帯", "棄", "滞"] },
		{ "question": "固", "answers": ["個", "凅", "涸", "痼", "箇", "錮"] },
		{ "question": "耒", "answers": ["耕", "耗", "耙", "耘", "耜", "耡", "誄", "耦", "耨", "藉", "藕", "籍"] },
		{ "question": "告", "answers": ["造", "浩", "晧", "梏", "皓", "窖", "酷", "慥", "誥", "靠", "鵠"] },
		{ "question": "吿", "answers": ["造", "浩", "晧", "梏", "皓", "窖", "酷", "誥", "靠", "鵠"] },
		{ "question": "䏍", "answers": ["能", "態", "熊", "罷", "擺", "羆"] },
		{ "question": "夅", "answers": ["降", "絳"] },
		{ "question": "冎", "answers": ["骨", "過", "渦", "堝", "萵", "滑", "禍", "骭", "猾", "榾", "骰", "窩", "禍", "蝸", "骸", "骼", "鍋", "髀", "髄", "鶻", "髏", "髑", "髓", "體"] },
		{ "question": "坐", "answers": ["座", "挫", "蓙"] },
		{ "question": "身", "answers": ["射", "躬", "躯", "躮", "躱", "窮", "躾", "謝", "軀", "麝", "軈"] },
		{ "question": "寽", "answers": ["将", "埒", "奨", "蒋", "醤"] },
		{ "question": "金", "answers": ["針", "釘", "釣", "釦", "釧", "崟", "釵", "鈍", "欽", "鈎", "釿", "鈞", "鈕", "鈑", "鈔", "鉄", "鉱", "鉛", "鉢", "鈴", "鉤", "鈷", "鉦", "鉗", "鉉", "鉞", "鉅", "鉋", "鉈", "鈿", "銀", "銭", "銅", "銃", "銘", "銑", "銚", "鉾", "銜", "銖", "銕", "銓", "銛", "鋩", "鋭", "鋳", "鋤", "鋲", "鋪", "鋒", "劉", "鋏", "銹", "銷", "錵", "錺", "録", "鋼", "錯", "錠", "錬", "錦", "錮", "鋸", "錫", "錆", "錘", "錐", "錨", "錏", "錙", "錣", "錻", "鋺", "錚", "錢", "錄", "鍛", "鍵", "鍋", "鍔", "鍬", "鍾", "鍍", "鍼", "鍮", "鍠", "鍊", "鎖", "鎮", "鎌", "鎧", "鎗", "鎚", "鎔", "鎰", "鎹", "鎬", "鎺", "鎭", "鏡", "鏑", "鏖", "鏘", "鏈", "鏤", "鏨", "鏃", "鏝", "鏐", "鐘", "鐙", "鐚", "鏗", "鐔", "鐃", "鐐", "鐓", "鐸", "鐫", "鐶", "鐺", "鐵", "鑓", "籙", "鑄", "鑑", "鑒", "鑠", "鑢", "鑞", "鑚", "鑛", "鑪", "鑵", "鑰", "鑷", "鑼", "鑾", "鑽", "钁", "鑿"] },
		{ "question": "直", "answers": ["値", "埴", "植", "殖", "置"] },
		{ "question": "龸", "answers": ["党", "堂", "常", "掌", "棠", "當", "嘗", "裳", "嫦", "賞", "瞠", "償", "螳", "礑", "襠", "蟷", "黨", "鐺", "儻"] },
		{ "question": "非", "answers": ["俳", "匪", "排", "徘", "菲", "悲", "扉", "斐", "腓", "琲", "罪", "緋", "蜚", "榧", "裴", "翡", "輩", "誹", "靠", "霏", "鯡", "靡"] },
		{ "question": "巩", "answers": ["恐", "筑", "蛩", "跫", "鞏", "築"] },
		{ "question": "㑒", "answers": ["剣", "倹", "険", "検", "験", "鹸"] },
		{ "question": "斉", "answers": ["剤", "済"] },
		{ "question": "辰", "answers": ["振", "辱", "娠", "唇", "宸", "晨", "脣", "農", "蜃", "溽", "蓐", "賑", "震", "儂", "褥", "濃", "耨", "縟", "膿"] },
		{ "question": "羽", "answers": ["扇", "翁", "翆", "栩", "翅", "習", "翌", "翊", "翔", "翕", "勠", "搨", "摺", "翠", "煽", "寥", "廖", "慴", "摎", "榻", "蓼", "翡", "翫", "戮", "樛", "膠", "翦", "翩", "翰", "歙", "褶", "翼", "濯", "擢", "繆", "翳", "曜", "翻", "謬", "戳", "櫂", "醪", "燿", "翹", "瀚", "鏐", "耀", "躍", "鶲", "糴", "糶"] },
		{ "question": "秀", "answers": ["透", "莠", "綉", "誘", "銹"] },
		{ "question": "兵", "answers": ["浜", "鋲"] },
		{ "question": "夆", "answers": ["峰", "峯", "逢", "烽", "蜂", "蓬", "鋒", "縫", "篷"] },
		{ "question": "良", "answers": ["娘", "浪", "狼", "莨", "郞", "琅", "朗", "蜋", "廊", "榔", "踉", "瑯", "螂"] },
		{ "question": "戻", "answers": ["涙", "唳", "捩", "綟"] },
		{ "question": "兑", "answers": ["悦", "脱", "税", "説", "鋭", "閲"] },
		{ "question": "妟", "answers": ["宴", "偃", "堰", "蝘", "鼴"] },
		{ "question": "旡", "answers": ["既", "慨", "厩", "廐", "漑", "曁"] },
		{ "question": "吾", "answers": ["悟", "唔", "圄", "梧", "晤", "牾", "衙", "語", "寤", "鼯", "齬"] },
		{ "question": "呉", "answers": ["娯", "茣", "虞", "蜈", "誤"] },
		{ "question": "隹", "answers": ["隻", "准", "隼", "進", "推", "唯", "堆", "惟", "雀", "售", "崔", "帷", "集", "雄", "雇", "焦", "椎", "雁", "準", "雅", "勧", "携", "催", "稚", "碓", "匯", "雎", "雉", "雍", "雋", "雑", "維", "雌", "奪", "潅", "截", "摧", "確", "権", "歓", "誰", "蕉", "憔", "奮", "獲", "擁", "樵", "錐", "薙", "壅", "暹", "霍", "雕", "罹", "礁", "濯", "擢", "襍", "膺", "雖", "虧", "應", "舊", "曜", "観", "難", "離", "穫", "雛", "戳", "櫂", "騅", "甕", "燿", "瞿", "雜", "雙", "羅", "贋", "蠖", "藺", "勸", "難", "護", "灌", "耀", "懽", "矍", "躍", "顧", "鶴", "儺", "囃", "廱", "懼", "癨", "權", "歡", "灘", "攤", "糴", "蘿", "攫", "鷦", "躙", "讐", "讎", "癰", "邏", "罐", "鷹", "讙", "軈", "衢", "觀", "鑵", "籬", "糶", "躪", "顴", "驩", "鑼", "鸛", "钁"] },
		{ "question": "双", "answers": ["桑", "啜", "畷", "綴", "輟", "錣"] },
		{ "question": "折", "answers": ["哲", "逝", "浙", "晢", "晣", "誓"] },
		{ "question": "東", "answers": ["凍", "陳", "棟", "練", "諌", "錬", "蘭", "鶇", "欄"] },
		{ "question": "若", "answers": ["匿", "惹", "慝", "諾", "鰙"] },
		{ "question": "食", "answers": ["飢", "飲", "飯", "喰", "飼", "飾", "飽", "飭", "飩", "飫", "飴", "養", "餓", "餌", "餅", "蝕", "餉", "餃", "館", "餐", "餔", "餒", "餘", "餡", "餤", "餞", "餠", "瀁", "餮", "餬", "饂", "餽", "餾", "癢", "饉", "饅", "饐", "饌", "饑", "饋", "饒", "饗", "饕", "鱶"] },
		{ "question": "岡", "answers": ["剛", "綱", "鋼"] },
		{ "question": "辛", "answers": ["宰", "梓", "辜", "辞", "辟", "滓", "辣", "僻", "劈", "避", "壁", "嬖", "縡", "薜", "薛", "辨", "擘", "檗", "臂", "癖", "璧", "甓", "襞", "辭", "蘗", "蘖", "躄", "辮", "瓣", "譬", "櫱", "躃", "闢", "霹", "辯", "糱"] },
		{ "question": "全", "answers": ["栓", "痊", "筌", "詮", "銓"] },
		{ "question": "氺", "answers": ["泰", "剥", "剝", "黍", "禄", "碌", "祿", "様", "緑", "漆", "綠", "暴", "膝", "黎", "滕", "録", "錄", "黏", "藤", "瀑", "藜", "爆", "曝", "懷", "壞", "鰥", "籐", "籙", "黐"] },
		{ "question": "奉", "answers": ["俸", "捧", "棒"] },
		{ "question": "侖", "answers": ["倫", "崙", "崘", "淪", "綸", "輪", "論"] },
		{ "question": "奄", "answers": ["俺", "庵", "掩", "淹", "菴", "罨", "閹"] },
		{ "question": "妻", "answers": ["凄", "悽", "淒", "棲", "褄"] },
		{ "question": "步", "answers": ["捗", "陟", "涉", "瀕", "蘋", "騭", "顰"] },
		{ "question": "歩", "answers": ["捗", "渉", "頻", "瀕", "蘋", "顰"] },
		{ "question": "录", "answers": ["剥", "禄", "碌", "緑", "録", "籙"] },
		{ "question": "昗", "answers": ["冥", "幎", "溟", "暝", "瞑", "螟"] },
		{ "question": "彔", "answers": ["剝", "碌", "祿", "綠", "錄", "籙"] },
		{ "question": "亜", "answers": ["唖", "悪"] },
		{ "question": "委", "answers": ["倭", "萎", "矮", "痿", "魏", "巍"] },
		{ "question": "会", "answers": ["桧", "絵"] },
		{ "question": "巻", "answers": ["倦", "捲", "惓", "圏", "蜷", "綣"] },
		{ "question": "卷", "answers": ["倦", "捲", "惓", "圈", "蜷", "綣"] },
		{ "question": "幸", "answers": ["倖", "執", "圉", "報", "睾", "摯", "懌", "澤", "擇", "蟄", "贄", "繹", "譯", "釋", "鐸", "鷙", "驛"] },
		{ "question": "夲", "answers": ["皋", "槔"] },
		{ "question": "亚", "answers": ["晋", "霊"] },
		{ "question": "危", "answers": ["脆", "跪", "詭", "鮠"] },
		{ "question": "丹", "answers": ["栴", "旃"] },
		{ "question": "㕚", "answers": ["蚤", "搔", "騷"] },
		{ "question": "豖", "answers": ["啄", "冢", "塚", "琢"] },
		{ "question": "周", "answers": ["凋", "週", "彫", "惆", "稠", "蜩", "綢", "調", "雕", "簓", "鯛"] },
		{ "question": "狄", "answers": ["荻", "逖"] },
		{ "question": "镸", "answers": ["套", "肆", "髢", "髪", "髦", "髣", "髥", "髫", "髯", "髴", "髱", "髮", "髭", "髻", "髷", "鬆", "鬘", "鬚", "鬟", "鬢", "鬣"] },
		{ "question": "寿", "answers": ["涛", "梼", "祷", "畴", "鋳"] },
		{ "question": "売", "answers": ["涜", "続", "読"] },
		{ "question": "旲", "answers": ["莫", "募", "墓", "幕", "漠", "摸", "寞", "獏", "暮", "模", "慕", "膜", "冪", "蟇", "蟆", "謨", "貘", "羃", "驀"] },
		{ "question": "豸", "answers": ["豹", "豺", "貂", "貊", "貉", "貌", "貎", "墾", "懇", "藐", "貘", "霾"] },
		{ "question": "夌", "answers": ["凌", "陵", "菱", "崚", "稜", "綾", "薐"] },
		{ "question": "圥", "answers": ["凌", "陸", "陵", "菱", "崚", "逵", "勢", "睦", "稜", "綾", "熱", "薐", "褻", "藝", "囈"] },
		{ "question": "奇", "answers": ["倚", "剞", "寄", "崎", "埼", "掎", "猗", "椅", "欹", "畸", "綺", "騎", "羇"] },
		{ "question": "居", "answers": ["倨", "据", "裾", "踞", "鋸"] },
		{ "question": "屈", "answers": ["倔", "掘", "堀", "崛", "窟"] },
		{ "question": "兒", "answers": ["倪", "猊", "睨", "貎", "霓", "鬩", "鯢", "麑"] },
		{ "question": "空", "answers": ["倥", "控", "腔", "箜"] },
		{ "question": "卒", "answers": ["倅", "悴", "淬", "猝", "萃", "瘁", "碎", "翠", "粹", "膵", "醉"] },
		{ "question": "叔", "answers": ["俶", "寂", "淑", "菽", "椒", "督"] },
		{ "question": "昌", "answers": ["倡", "唱", "娼", "菖", "猖", "椙"] },
		{ "question": "靑", "answers": ["倩", "情", "猜", "菁", "晴", "靖", "睛", "精", "蜻", "請", "錆", "靜", "鯖", "瀞", "鶄"] },
		{ "question": "青", "answers": ["倩", "清", "情", "猜", "菁", "晴", "靖", "睛", "静", "精", "蜻", "請", "錆", "靜", "鯖", "瀞", "鶄"] },
		{ "question": "円", "answers": ["倩", "情", "猜", "菁", "晴", "靖", "睛", "精", "蜻", "請", "錆", "靜", "鯖", "瀞", "鶄"] },
		{ "question": "卓", "answers": ["倬", "悼", "啅", "掉", "棹", "罩", "綽"] },
		{ "question": "卑", "answers": ["俾", "婢", "牌", "脾", "稗", "裨", "睥", "痺", "碑", "髀", "鵯", "顰"] },
		{ "question": "卑", "answers": ["俾", "婢", "牌", "脾", "稗", "裨", "睥", "痺", "碑", "髀", "鵯", "顰"] },
		{ "question": "府", "answers": ["俯", "符", "腑", "腐"] },
		{ "question": "兩", "answers": ["倆", "裲", "輛", "魎"] },
		{ "question": "再", "answers": ["冓", "溝", "媾", "搆", "構", "遘", "篝", "講", "購", "覯"] },
		{ "question": "兔", "answers": ["冤", "寃", "菟", "逸", "巉", "纔", "讒"] },
		{ "question": "易", "answers": ["剔", "裼", "蜴", "賜", "錫", "鯣", "鶍"] },
		{ "question": "京", "answers": ["勍", "涼", "掠", "景", "就", "椋", "影", "憬", "諒", "鯨", "蹴", "黥", "鷲"] },
		{ "question": "希", "answers": ["唏", "晞", "欷", "稀", "鯑"] },
		{ "question": "孝", "answers": ["哮", "教", "酵"] },
		{ "question": "戾", "answers": ["唳", "捩", "淚", "綟"] },
		{ "question": "角", "answers": ["埆", "斛", "桷", "觝", "解", "触", "觚", "觜", "觥", "槲", "嘴", "廨", "懈", "邂", "鵤", "觴", "蟹", "蠏", "觸"] },
		{ "question": "壯", "answers": ["奘", "弉", "莊", "裝"] },
		{ "question": "肙", "answers": ["娟", "悁", "捐", "涓", "狷", "絹", "蜎", "鵑", "羂"] },
		{ "question": "沙", "answers": ["娑", "莎", "裟", "鯊"] },
		{ "question": "那", "answers": ["娜", "梛"] },
		{ "question": "甹", "answers": ["娉", "聘", "騁"] },
		{ "question": "旱", "answers": ["悍", "捍", "桿", "稈", "駻"] },
		{ "question": "困", "answers": ["悃", "梱"] },
		{ "question": "邑", "answers": ["悒", "扈", "滬", "廱", "癰"] },
		{ "question": "圼", "answers": ["捏", "涅"] },
		{ "question": "牟", "answers": ["桙", "眸", "鉾", "鴾"] },
		{ "question": "匡", "answers": ["框", "筐"] },
		{ "question": "㞢", "answers": ["蚩", "嗤"] },
		{ "question": "延", "answers": ["涎", "莚", "蜒", "蜑", "筵", "誕"] },
		{ "question": "休", "answers": ["烋", "鮴"] },
		{ "question": "呈", "answers": ["郢", "逞", "程", "裎", "酲", "鐵"] },
		{ "question": "含", "answers": ["莟", "頷"] },
		{ "question": "吳", "answers": ["茣", "虞", "蜈", "誤", "麌"] },
		{ "question": "夨", "answers": ["茣", "虞", "蜈", "誤", "麌"] },
		{ "question": "豆", "answers": ["荳", "豈", "逗", "短", "登", "喜", "痘", "凱", "厨", "剴", "彭", "壹", "豊", "鼓", "嘉", "僖", "澄", "嬉", "廚", "噎", "嶝", "澎", "磑", "皚", "豌", "頭", "樹", "膨", "豎", "橙", "熹", "殪", "燈", "磴", "覬", "禧", "戲", "闘", "鎧", "鼕", "瞽", "禮", "豐", "艶", "證", "鐙", "醴", "鬪", "饐", "懿", "鱚", "體", "鱧", "艷"] },
		{ "question": "㐆", "answers": ["殷", "慇"] },
		{ "question": "忍", "answers": ["荵", "綛", "認"] },
		{ "question": "攴", "answers": ["冦", "寇", "敍", "敲"] },
		{ "question": "虎", "answers": ["虒", "彪", "琥", "號", "遞", "褫", "篪", "鯱", "饕"] },
		{ "question": "厸", "answers": ["晉", "參", "滲", "蔘", "慘", "縉", "糝", "驂", "鰺"] },
		{ "question": "雨", "answers": ["雪", "雫", "雲", "雰", "電", "雷", "零", "雹", "需", "漏", "震", "霊", "樗", "霄", "霈", "霆", "曇", "儒", "擂", "霓", "霎", "霑", "霙", "霏", "霖", "澪", "霍", "蕾", "霜", "霞", "嬬", "濡", "孺", "懦", "艝", "霤", "臑", "轌", "繧", "霧", "壜", "霪", "襦", "孀", "霰", "蠕", "繻", "糯", "露", "霸", "霹", "櫺", "轜", "癨", "鱈", "罎", "霽", "霾", "顬", "靂", "靆", "靄", "鱩", "靈", "靉"] },
		{ "question": "求", "answers": ["球", "救", "毬", "逑", "裘"] },
		{ "question": "佰", "answers": ["宿", "蓿", "縮"] },
		{ "question": "冏", "answers": ["商", "烱", "裔", "橘", "譎", "鷸"] },
		{ "question": "罙", "answers": ["深", "探"] },
		{ "question": "長", "answers": ["帳", "張", "悵", "脹", "漲"] },
		{ "question": "重", "answers": ["動", "董", "働", "腫", "種", "慟", "衝", "勲", "薫", "踵", "鍾"] },
		{ "question": "戒", "answers": ["械", "誡"] },
		{ "question": "建", "answers": ["健", "腱", "鍵"] },
		{ "question": "隶", "answers": ["康", "逮", "棣", "慷", "隷", "糠", "隸", "鱇", "靆"] },
		{ "question": "采", "answers": ["菜", "採", "彩", "綵"] },
		{ "question": "果", "answers": ["巣", "菓", "巢", "裸", "彙", "剿", "勦", "夥", "裹", "課", "樔", "踝", "顆"] },
		{ "question": "則", "answers": ["側", "厠", "測", "廁", "惻"] },
		{ "question": "亭", "answers": ["停", "渟"] },
		{ "question": "㝵", "answers": ["得", "碍"] },
		{ "question": "畐", "answers": ["副", "匐", "富", "幅", "福", "逼", "蔔", "福", "蝠", "輻"] },
		{ "question": "坴", "answers": ["陸", "逵", "勢", "睦", "熱", "褻", "藝", "囈"] },
		{ "question": "夜", "answers": ["液", "掖", "腋", "鵺"] },
		{ "question": "其", "answers": ["基", "萁", "期", "棋", "欺", "斯", "棊", "朞", "碁", "祺", "旗", "箕", "厮", "綦", "嘶", "廝", "撕", "踑", "騏", "麒", "簸"] },
		{ "question": "昆", "answers": ["混", "崑", "菎", "棍", "焜", "鯤"] },
		{ "question": "受", "answers": ["授", "綬"] },
		{ "question": "吊", "answers": ["常", "嫦"] },
		{ "question": "妾", "answers": ["接", "椄", "霎"] },
		{ "question": "务", "answers": ["務", "霧"] },
		{ "question": "或", "answers": ["域", "國", "惑", "摑", "幗", "閾", "馘"] },
		{ "question": "乡", "answers": ["郷", "雍", "擁", "壅", "甕", "嚮", "響", "饗"] },
		{ "question": "舎", "answers": ["捨", "舗"] },
		{ "question": "頁", "answers": ["頂", "頃", "順", "項", "須", "預", "傾", "頑", "煩", "頒", "頓", "頏", "頌", "領", "頚", "碩", "頗", "頬", "頡", "頭", "頼", "頰", "穎", "頸", "噸", "頴", "頤", "頷", "頽", "蕷", "頻", "嶺", "顆", "顔", "題", "類", "額", "顕", "顎", "顋", "顏", "願", "瀬", "顛", "瀕", "顚", "蘋", "類", "襭", "顧", "囂", "纈", "纐", "巓", "鬚", "顫", "顬", "顯", "顰", "癲", "顱", "顴", "顳"] },
		{ "question": "宓", "answers": ["密", "蜜", "樒", "櫁"] },
		{ "question": "垂", "answers": ["郵", "唾", "捶", "陲", "睡", "錘"] },
		{ "question": "侌", "answers": ["陰", "蔭"] },
		{ "question": "龺", "answers": ["乾", "朝", "戟", "幹", "斡", "潮", "嘲", "廟", "翰", "澣", "韓", "瀚"] },
		{ "question": "参", "answers": ["惨", "鯵"] },
		{ "question": "丸", "answers": ["執", "孰", "勢", "塾", "熱", "熟", "摯", "蟄", "褻", "贄", "藝", "囈", "鷙"] },
		{ "question": "釆", "answers": ["釈", "悉", "番", "釉", "奧", "審", "播", "幡", "蕃", "潘", "懊", "膰", "澳", "燔", "蟋", "燠", "藩", "翻", "襖", "旛", "蟠", "瀋", "繙", "釋", "飜", "竊", "鷭"] },
		{ "question": "炎", "answers": ["淡", "啖", "毯", "痰", "談", "餤"] },
		{ "question": "苗", "answers": ["描", "猫", "錨"] },
		{ "question": "享", "answers": ["郭", "惇", "淳", "孰", "敦", "椁", "塾", "廓", "熟", "醇", "槨", "諄", "暾", "燉", "鶉", "鐓"] },
		{ "question": "卦", "answers": ["掛", "罫", "褂"] },
		{ "question": "甚", "answers": ["勘", "堪", "湛", "尠", "戡", "斟", "椹", "碪", "糂"] },
		{ "question": "毌", "answers": ["貫", "慣", "實"] },
		{ "question": "匊", "answers": ["菊", "掬", "椈", "麹", "鞠", "麴"] },
		{ "question": "禺", "answers": ["偶", "遇", "隅", "寓", "嵎", "萬", "愚", "耦", "邁", "勵", "癘", "藕", "礪", "蠆", "蠣", "糲"] },
		{ "question": "匂", "answers": ["掲", "喝", "渇", "偈", "葛", "揭", "褐", "歇", "碣", "竭", "謁", "蝎", "羯", "鞨", "藹", "靄"] },
		{ "question": "赤", "answers": ["赦", "赧", "赫", "赭", "赬", "嚇", "螫"] },
		{ "question": "匋", "answers": ["陶", "淘", "萄", "掏", "綯"] },
		{ "question": "波", "answers": ["婆", "菠"] },
		{ "question": "朋", "answers": ["崩", "萠", "堋", "弸", "棚", "硼", "繃", "鵬"] },
		{ "question": "鼡", "answers": ["猟", "蝋"] },
		{ "question": "厓", "answers": ["涯", "崖", "崕", "啀", "睚"] },
		{ "question": "為", "answers": ["偽", "譌"] },
		{ "question": "囷", "answers": ["菌", "箘", "麕"] },
		{ "question": "宗", "answers": ["崇", "淙", "棕", "綜", "粽", "踪", "鶎"] },
		{ "question": "曲", "answers": ["曹", "農", "豊", "遭", "漕", "槽", "儂", "濃", "髷", "糟", "膿", "艚", "禮", "艶", "醴", "體", "鱧"] },
		{ "question": "貞", "answers": ["偵", "幀", "禎", "遉", "禎", "赬"] },
		{ "question": "扁", "answers": ["偏", "遍", "褊", "編", "篇", "蝙", "翩", "諞", "騙"] },
		{ "question": "林", "answers": ["麻", "彬", "淋", "埜", "婪", "梵", "梺", "森", "焚", "琳", "禁", "楚", "痳", "罧", "歴", "暦", "嘛", "麼", "摩", "麾", "潸", "醂", "磨", "噤", "霖", "縻", "糜", "礎", "襟", "麿", "麓", "靡", "魔", "爨"] },
		{ "question": "攸", "answers": ["悠", "筱"] },
		{ "question": "㸒", "answers": ["淫", "婬", "霪"] },
		{ "question": "㸚", "answers": ["爽", "爾", "濔", "彌", "邇", "璽", "禰", "瀰"] },
		{ "question": "爻", "answers": ["爽", "爾", "駁", "樊", "學", "濔", "彌", "邇", "璽", "禰", "攀", "瀰", "礬", "覺", "攪", "鷽", "鱟", "黌"] },
		{ "question": "念", "answers": ["捻", "唸", "稔", "鯰"] },
		{ "question": "皇", "answers": ["凰", "徨", "惶", "隍", "煌", "遑", "蝗", "篁", "鍠", "鰉"] },
		{ "question": "官", "answers": ["菅", "棺", "管", "綰", "館", "舘"] },
		{ "question": "思", "answers": ["偲", "腮", "慮", "濾", "顋", "鰓", "鑢"] },
		{ "question": "是", "answers": ["匙", "提", "堤", "寔", "醍", "題"] },
		{ "question": "疌", "answers": ["捷", "睫"] },
		{ "question": "定", "answers": ["淀", "掟", "碇", "綻", "聢", "諚", "錠"] },
		{ "question": "明", "answers": ["萌", "盟"] },
		{ "question": "花", "answers": ["椛", "糀", "錵"] },
		{ "question": "來", "answers": ["萊", "麥", "麪", "麩", "賚", "憖", "麭", "麴", "麵"] },
		{ "question": "亞", "answers": ["啞", "堊", "椏", "惡", "壼", "錏", "鐚"] },
		{ "question": "匽", "answers": ["偃", "堰", "蝘", "鼴"] },
		{ "question": "皆", "answers": ["偕", "階", "揩", "楷", "諧"] },
		{ "question": "彥", "answers": ["偐", "諺", "顏"] },
		{ "question": "彦", "answers": ["偐", "諺", "顔"] },
		{ "question": "曷", "answers": ["偈", "葛", "揭", "渴", "歇", "遏", "碣", "竭", "蝎", "羯", "謁", "鞨", "蠍", "藹", "靄"] },
		{ "question": "者", "answers": ["偖", "堵", "奢", "屠", "猪", "都", "渚", "著", "楮", "暑", "煮", "睹", "署", "箸", "潴", "緖", "賭", "赭", "覩", "諸", "曙", "薯", "闍", "儲", "藷", "躇"] },
		{ "question": "怱", "answers": ["偬", "葱"] },
		{ "question": "兪", "answers": ["偸", "愉", "喩", "揄", "渝", "愈", "楡", "瑜", "逾", "瘉", "蝓", "輸", "諭", "踰", "覦", "鍮", "癒"] },
		{ "question": "前", "answers": ["剪", "揃", "煎", "箭", "翦"] },
		{ "question": "荅", "answers": ["剳", "塔", "搭", "鞳"] },
		{ "question": "助", "answers": ["勗", "耡", "鋤"] },
		{ "question": "於", "answers": ["唹", "淤", "閼", "鯲"] },
		{ "question": "叕", "answers": ["啜", "畷", "綴", "輟", "錣"] },
		{ "question": "臽", "answers": ["啗", "埳", "陷", "焰", "諂", "閻", "餡"] },
		{ "question": "阿", "answers": ["婀", "痾"] },
		{ "question": "宛", "answers": ["婉", "腕", "椀", "碗", "蜿", "豌", "鋺"] },
		{ "question": "取", "answers": ["娵", "娶", "掫", "陬", "最", "聚", "趣", "撮", "諏", "輙", "叢", "驟"] },
		{ "question": "爭", "answers": ["崢", "淨", "箏", "諍", "錚", "靜", "瀞"] },
		{ "question": "罔", "answers": ["惘", "網", "魍"] },
		{ "question": "麦", "answers": ["麸", "麹", "麺"] },
		{ "question": "舛", "answers": ["桝", "桀", "傑", "舜", "舞", "隣", "憐", "磔", "蕣", "鄰", "燐", "瞬", "驎", "鱗", "麟"] },
		{ "question": "首", "answers": ["馗", "道", "導", "馘"] },
		{ "question": "析", "answers": ["淅", "晰", "晳", "皙", "蜥"] },
		{ "question": "尙", "answers": ["淌", "敞"] },
		{ "question": "尚", "answers": ["淌", "敞", "厰", "廠"] },
		{ "question": "革", "answers": ["勒", "靱", "靭", "靫", "靴", "鞄", "靼", "鞁", "靺", "鞅", "鞆", "鞍", "鞐", "鞋", "鞏", "鞘", "鞠", "鞜", "鞭", "鞫", "鞦", "鞳", "鞨", "鞣", "覇", "鞴", "霸", "韃", "羇", "韈", "韆", "羈"] },
		{ "question": "松", "answers": ["菘", "鬆"] },
		{ "question": "音", "answers": ["竟", "暗", "意", "韵", "境", "韶", "億", "幟", "憶", "噫", "熾", "諳", "薏", "臆", "闇", "職", "織", "鏡", "識", "韻", "響", "黯", "響"] },
		{ "question": "冒", "answers": ["勖", "帽", "瑁"] },
		{ "question": "囱", "answers": ["悤", "總", "聰"] },
		{ "question": "夊", "answers": ["悤", "總", "聰"] },
		{ "question": "叚", "answers": ["假", "葭", "暇", "瑕", "遐", "蝦", "霞", "鰕"] },
		{ "question": "品", "answers": ["區", "嵒", "傴", "嘔", "嫗", "嶇", "樞", "歐", "毆", "操", "噪", "懆", "澡", "甌", "燥", "癌", "臨", "軀", "謳", "繰", "藻", "躁", "譟", "驅", "鷗"] },
		{ "question": "厽", "answers": ["參", "滲", "蔘", "慘", "糝", "驂", "鰺"] },
		{ "question": "戔", "answers": ["淺", "牋", "殘", "棧", "盞", "箋", "綫", "賤", "踐", "錢", "餞", "濺"] },
		{ "question": "条", "answers": ["條", "滌", "篠"] },
		{ "question": "昜", "answers": ["場", "湯", "陽", "揚", "腸", "傷", "楊", "暘", "煬", "瘍", "暢", "蕩", "殤", "盪", "觴", "蘯"] },
		{ "question": "軍", "answers": ["運", "揮", "渾", "葷", "暈", "暉", "褌", "皹", "皸", "輝", "諢", "鶤"] },
		{ "question": "昷", "answers": ["温", "褞", "瘟", "饂", "鰛", "韞"] },
		{ "question": "胡", "answers": ["湖", "瑚", "糊", "蝴", "醐", "餬"] },
		{ "question": "斿", "answers": ["遊", "游", "蝣"] },
		{ "question": "枼", "answers": ["葉", "喋", "渫", "牒", "蝶", "緤", "諜", "鰈"] },
		{ "question": "壴", "answers": ["喜", "彭", "鼓", "嘉", "僖", "嬉", "廚", "澎", "樹", "膨", "熹", "禧", "鼕", "瞽", "鱚"] },
		{ "question": "尭", "answers": ["焼", "暁"] },
		{ "question": "㒸", "answers": ["隊", "遂", "墜", "隧", "燧", "邃"] },
		{ "question": "尃", "answers": ["博", "傅", "搏", "溥", "榑", "膊", "薄", "縛", "賻", "簿"] },
		{ "question": "両", "answers": ["満", "輌"] },
		{ "question": "咼", "answers": ["過", "渦", "堝", "萵", "禍", "窩", "禍", "蝸", "鍋"] },
		{ "question": "咸", "answers": ["減", "喊", "感", "箴", "緘", "憾", "撼", "鍼", "鰔", "鹹", "轗"] },
		{ "question": "色", "answers": ["絶", "艶", "艷"] },
		{ "question": "禹", "answers": ["属", "嘱", "齲"] },
		{ "question": "充", "answers": ["統", "銃"] },
		{ "question": "复", "answers": ["復", "愎", "腹", "複", "履", "蝮", "輹", "覆", "馥", "鰒"] },
		{ "question": "㞋", "answers": ["報", "赧"] },
		{ "question": "害", "answers": ["割", "瞎", "轄", "豁"] },
		{ "question": "苟", "answers": ["敬", "檠", "警", "驚"] },
		{ "question": "乑", "answers": ["衆", "聚", "驟"] },
		{ "question": "倉", "answers": ["創", "蒼", "愴", "搶", "滄", "槍", "瘡", "艙", "蹌", "鎗"] },
		{ "question": "酋", "answers": ["尊", "猶", "奠", "楢", "猷", "遒", "遵", "鄭", "噂", "蕕", "樽", "擲", "蹲", "鰌", "躑", "鱒"] },
		{ "question": "屋", "answers": ["握", "渥", "幄", "齷"] },
		{ "question": "韋", "answers": ["偉", "幃", "圍", "違", "葦", "衛", "緯", "諱", "韓", "韜", "韞"] },
		{ "question": "戉", "answers": ["越", "鉞"] },
		{ "question": "爰", "answers": ["援", "媛", "湲", "暖", "煖", "緩"] },
		{ "question": "卸", "answers": ["御", "啣", "禦"] },
		{ "question": "臤", "answers": ["堅", "腎", "竪", "緊", "慳", "賢", "樫", "豎", "鏗", "鰹"] },
		{ "question": "冝", "answers": ["畳", "疊"] },
		{ "question": "㚘", "answers": ["替", "僣", "賛", "潜", "輦", "攅", "譛", "纉", "讃", "鑚"] },
		{ "question": "単", "answers": ["弾", "戦", "禅", "褝", "蝉", "箪", "騨"] },
		{ "question": "度", "answers": ["渡", "鍍"] },
		{ "question": "並", "answers": ["普", "譜"] },
		{ "question": "旁", "answers": ["傍", "滂", "蒡", "榜", "膀", "磅", "謗"] },
		{ "question": "丅", "answers": ["敢", "隔", "膈", "融", "橄", "厳", "瞰", "巌", "獻", "嚴", "儼", "鬻", "巖"] },
		{ "question": "奐", "answers": ["換", "喚", "渙", "煥"] },
		{ "question": "契", "answers": ["喫", "楔", "禊"] },
		{ "question": "显", "answers": ["湿", "顕"] },
		{ "question": "迶", "answers": ["随", "髄"] },
		{ "question": "胥", "answers": ["婿", "壻"] },
		{ "question": "莫", "answers": ["募", "墓", "幕", "漠", "摸", "寞", "獏", "暮", "模", "慕", "膜", "冪", "蟇", "蟆", "謨", "貘", "羃", "驀"] },
		{ "question": "郎", "answers": ["廊", "榔", "瑯", "螂", "嚮", "響", "饗"] },
		{ "question": "玨", "answers": ["琴", "琶", "琵", "瑟"] },
		{ "question": "兹", "answers": ["滋", "孳", "慈", "磁"] },
		{ "question": "玆", "answers": ["滋", "孳", "慈", "磁"] },
		{ "question": "盾", "answers": ["循", "遁", "楯"] },
		{ "question": "発", "answers": ["廃", "溌", "醗"] },
		{ "question": "某", "answers": ["媒", "楳", "煤", "謀"] },
		{ "question": "俞", "answers": ["愉", "揄", "渝", "愈", "瑜", "逾", "榆", "瘉", "蝓", "輸", "諭", "踰", "覦", "鍮"] },
		{ "question": "風", "answers": ["嵐", "颪", "楓", "颯", "颱", "瘋", "諷", "颶", "飄", "飆"] },
		{ "question": "侯", "answers": ["喉", "猴", "篌"] },
		{ "question": "勇", "answers": ["湧", "踴"] },
		{ "question": "英", "answers": ["瑛", "霙"] },
		{ "question": "豈", "answers": ["凱", "剴", "磑", "皚", "覬", "鎧"] },
		{ "question": "宣", "answers": ["萱", "喧", "愃", "暄", "諠", "鰚"] },
		{ "question": "倠", "answers": ["雁", "膺", "應", "贋", "鷹", "軈"] },
		{ "question": "癸", "answers": ["葵", "揆"] },
		{ "question": "韭", "answers": ["韮", "薤", "懴", "殱", "韲", "孅", "懺", "籖", "殲", "籤", "齏", "纖", "讖"] },
		{ "question": "卽", "answers": ["卿", "喞", "節"] },
		{ "question": "即", "answers": ["卿", "節", "節", "櫛"] },
		{ "question": "呑", "answers": ["喬", "僑", "蕎", "嬌", "橋", "矯", "轎", "蹻", "驕"] },
		{ "question": "咠", "answers": ["揖", "葺", "楫", "緝", "輯"] },
		{ "question": "秋", "answers": ["萩", "啾", "愀", "湫", "愁", "楸", "甃", "鍬", "鞦", "鰍"] },
		{ "question": "相", "answers": ["湘", "廂", "想", "箱", "霜", "孀"] },
		{ "question": "男", "answers": ["甥", "虜", "舅", "嬲"] },
		{ "question": "奏", "answers": ["湊", "輳"] },
		{ "question": "知", "answers": ["智", "痴", "蜘", "聟", "踟"] },
		{ "question": "伐", "answers": ["筏", "閥"] },
		{ "question": "武", "answers": ["斌", "賦", "錻", "鵡", "贇"] },
		{ "question": "帛", "answers": ["棉", "綿", "錦", "幫"] },
		{ "question": "娄", "answers": ["屡", "数", "楼", "薮"] },
		{ "question": "畏", "answers": ["隈", "猥"] },
		{ "question": "鬼", "answers": ["傀", "塊", "蒐", "嵬", "愧", "隗", "魂", "魁", "槐", "瑰", "魅", "魃", "魄", "醜", "魍", "魎", "魏", "餽", "魔", "巍", "魑", "魘"] },
		{ "question": "欮", "answers": ["厥", "蕨", "獗", "闕", "蹶"] },
		{ "question": "彖", "answers": ["喙", "掾", "椽", "篆", "緣", "蠡"] },
		{ "question": "客", "answers": ["喀", "額"] },
		{ "question": "胃", "answers": ["喟", "渭", "膚", "蝟", "謂"] },
		{ "question": "帝", "answers": ["啻", "啼", "蒂", "締", "諦", "蹄"] },
		{ "question": "耑", "answers": ["喘", "惴", "揣", "湍", "猯", "瑞", "端"] },
		{ "question": "南", "answers": ["喃", "献", "楠", "遖"] },
		{ "question": "剌", "answers": ["喇", "溂", "蝲"] },
		{ "question": "垔", "answers": ["堙", "湮", "煙", "甄"] },
		{ "question": "保", "answers": ["堡", "葆", "褓", "褒"] },
		{ "question": "眉", "answers": ["媚", "嵋"] },
		{ "question": "叟", "answers": ["嫂", "搜", "溲", "瘦", "艘"] },
		{ "question": "孨", "answers": ["孱", "潺"] },
		{ "question": "封", "answers": ["幇", "幫"] },
		{ "question": "咢", "answers": ["愕", "鄂", "萼", "諤", "鍔", "顎", "鰐", "鶚", "齶"] },
		{ "question": "星", "answers": ["惺", "猩", "腥", "醒"] },
		{ "question": "制", "answers": ["掣", "製"] },
		{ "question": "柬", "answers": ["揀", "煉", "楝", "練", "諫", "闌", "鍊", "蘭", "鶫", "鰊", "瀾", "爛", "欄", "襴"] },
		{ "question": "柔", "answers": ["揉", "糅", "蹂", "鞣"] },
		{ "question": "耶", "answers": ["揶", "爺", "椰"] },
		{ "question": "㡀", "answers": ["敝", "黹", "幣", "弊", "蔽", "瞥", "黻", "斃", "黼", "鼈"] },
		{ "question": "眇", "answers": ["渺", "緲"] },
		{ "question": "面", "answers": ["湎", "靤", "緬", "麺", "靦", "麵", "靨"] },
		{ "question": "馬", "answers": ["馮", "馭", "馴", "馳", "媽", "駅", "駆", "駄", "駁", "瑪", "駐", "駒", "罵", "駕", "駈", "駟", "駛", "駑", "駘", "駝", "碼", "篤", "憑", "駮", "駱", "駭", "駢", "駿", "駻", "騁", "駸", "験", "騒", "騎", "闖", "騅", "騏", "騈", "騨", "騙", "騰", "騫", "驀", "騭", "騷", "驂", "驃", "騾", "驅", "驚", "驒", "驕", "驍", "驎", "驛", "驗", "驟", "羈", "驥", "驢", "驤", "驩", "驪"] },
		{ "question": "戎", "answers": ["絨", "賊"] },
		{ "question": "志", "answers": ["痣", "誌"] },
		{ "question": "臾", "answers": ["萸", "腴", "諛"] },
		{ "question": "㬰", "answers": ["萸", "諛"] },
		{ "question": "舍", "answers": ["舒", "舖", "舘"] },
		{ "question": "夏", "answers": ["厦", "嗄", "廈", "榎"] },
		{ "question": "炏", "answers": ["勞", "塋", "煢", "犖", "榮", "撈", "瑩", "螢", "癆", "營", "蠑", "鶯"] },
		{ "question": "垚", "answers": ["堯", "僥", "嶢", "撓", "澆", "蕘", "橈", "遶", "曉", "燒", "磽", "蟯", "繞", "翹", "鐃", "饒", "驍"] },
		{ "question": "㳄", "answers": ["盜", "羨"] },
		{ "question": "囟", "answers": ["惱", "瑙", "蓖", "腦", "篦"] },
		{ "question": "龱", "answers": ["惱", "瑙", "蓖", "腦", "篦", "竊"] },
		{ "question": "臿", "answers": ["插", "歃"] },
		{ "question": "袁", "answers": ["遠", "園", "猿", "薗", "轅"] },
		{ "question": "亲", "answers": ["新", "親", "薪", "噺", "襯"] },
		{ "question": "動", "answers": ["働", "慟", "勲"] },
		{ "question": "淮", "answers": ["準", "匯"] },
		{ "question": "埶", "answers": ["勢", "熱", "褻", "藝", "囈"] },
		{ "question": "員", "answers": ["損", "隕", "圓", "殞", "賞", "償", "韻"] },
		{ "question": "原", "answers": ["源", "愿", "螈", "願"] },
		{ "question": "真", "answers": ["慎", "填", "嗔", "槙", "瞋", "鎮", "顛"] },
		{ "question": "曽", "answers": ["僧", "増", "層", "憎", "贈"] },
		{ "question": "般", "answers": ["搬", "槃", "盤", "磐", "瘢"] },
		{ "question": "容", "answers": ["溶", "蓉", "熔", "榕", "鎔"] },
		{ "question": "家", "answers": ["嫁", "稼"] },
		{ "question": "既", "answers": ["慨", "概", "厩", "廐"] },
		{ "question": "旣", "answers": ["慨", "厩", "廐", "漑", "曁"] },
		{ "question": "鬲", "answers": ["隔", "膈", "融", "獻", "鬻"] },
		{ "question": "骨", "answers": ["滑", "骭", "猾", "榾", "骰", "骸", "骼", "髀", "髄", "鶻", "髏", "髑", "髓", "體"] },
		{ "question": "崔", "answers": ["催", "摧"] },
		{ "question": "責", "answers": ["債", "勣", "漬", "嘖", "積", "磧", "績", "簀", "蹟", "癪"] },
		{ "question": "竜", "answers": ["滝", "篭"] },
		{ "question": "兼", "answers": ["廉", "嫌", "慊", "蒹", "歉", "謙", "賺", "鎌", "簾", "蠊"] },
		{ "question": "莧", "answers": ["寛", "寬"] },
		{ "question": "桀", "answers": ["傑", "磔"] },
		{ "question": "冓", "answers": ["溝", "媾", "搆", "構", "遘", "篝", "講", "購", "覯"] },
		{ "question": "将", "answers": ["奨", "蒋", "醤"] },
		{ "question": "单", "answers": ["禅", "蝉", "箪"] },
		{ "question": "朔", "answers": ["塑", "溯", "遡", "愬", "槊"] },
		{ "question": "盍", "answers": ["蓋", "溘", "闔"] },
		{ "question": "堇", "answers": ["僅", "勤", "槿", "瑾", "懃", "覲", "謹", "饉"] },
		{ "question": "敖", "answers": ["傲", "嗷", "熬", "遨", "螯", "贅", "鼇"] },
		{ "question": "泉", "answers": ["腺", "楾", "線"] },
		{ "question": "弱", "answers": ["溺", "嫋", "搦", "蒻", "鰯", "鶸"] },
		{ "question": "栗", "answers": ["慄", "篥"] },
		{ "question": "眞", "answers": ["塡", "嗔", "愼", "槇", "瞋", "鎭", "顚", "鷆", "巓", "癲"] },
		{ "question": "益", "answers": ["溢", "隘", "縊", "謚", "鎰", "鷁"] },
		{ "question": "益", "answers": ["溢", "隘", "縊", "謚", "鎰"] },
		{ "question": "華", "answers": ["嘩", "樺", "曄", "譁"] },
		{ "question": "高", "answers": ["塙", "嵩", "蒿", "膏", "敲", "槁", "犒", "稿", "縞", "嚆", "藁", "鎬"] },
		{ "question": "鳥", "answers": ["鳩", "鳰", "鳧", "鳴", "鳶", "蔦", "嶋", "鳳", "鴎", "鴈", "鴇", "鴉", "鴃", "鴆", "鴂", "鴛", "鴨", "鴦", "鴬", "鴫", "鴟", "鴒", "鴕", "鴣", "鴪", "鴥", "鴻", "鵄", "鴿", "鵁", "鴾", "鵆", "鵇", "鵠", "鵜", "鵝", "鵞", "鵑", "鵤", "鵙", "鵥", "鶏", "鵡", "鵬", "鵲", "鶉", "鵺", "鶇", "鵯", "鶍", "鶎", "鶄", "鶚", "鶤", "鶫", "鶩", "鶪", "鶴", "鶯", "鶲", "鷁", "鶻", "鶺", "鷆", "鶸", "鷂", "鷄", "鷗", "鷙", "鷓", "鷲", "鷸", "鷦", "鷯", "鷭", "鷹", "鷺", "鷽", "鸚", "鸛", "鸞"] },
		{ "question": "离", "answers": ["禽", "漓", "璃", "擒", "檎", "離", "魑", "黐", "籬"] },
		{ "question": "㐫", "answers": ["禽", "漓", "璃", "擒", "檎", "離", "魑", "黐", "籬"] },
		{ "question": "禸", "answers": ["禽", "漓", "璃", "擒", "檎", "離", "魑", "竊", "黐", "籬"] },
		{ "question": "晃", "answers": ["幌", "滉"] },
		{ "question": "差", "answers": ["嵯", "嵳", "嗟", "搓", "瑳", "槎", "磋", "縒", "蹉"] },
		{ "question": "衰", "answers": ["蓑", "榱", "簑", "簔"] },
		{ "question": "師", "answers": ["獅", "篩", "鰤"] },
		{ "question": "時", "answers": ["蒔", "塒"] },
		{ "question": "段", "answers": ["椴", "緞", "鍛"] },
		{ "question": "春", "answers": ["椿", "惷", "鰆", "蠢"] },
		{ "question": "唐", "answers": ["塘", "溏", "糖", "螗"] },
		{ "question": "冡", "answers": ["蒙", "濛", "朦", "曚", "檬", "矇", "艨"] },
		{ "question": "庸", "answers": ["傭", "慵"] },
		{ "question": "留", "answers": ["溜", "瑠", "榴", "瘤", "霤", "籀", "餾"] },
		{ "question": "連", "answers": ["蓮", "漣", "縺", "鏈"] },
		{ "question": "蚤", "answers": ["搔", "騷"] },
		{ "question": "㐭", "answers": ["亶", "稟", "禀", "鄙", "圖", "凜", "凛", "壇", "廩", "懍", "擅", "檀", "氈", "羶", "顫"] },
		{ "question": "區", "answers": ["傴", "嘔", "嫗", "嶇", "樞", "歐", "毆", "甌", "軀", "謳", "驅", "鷗"] },
		{ "question": "婁", "answers": ["僂", "屢", "樓", "數", "褸", "瘻", "窶", "螻", "簍", "縷", "藪", "鏤", "籔", "髏"] },
		{ "question": "巢", "answers": ["剿", "勦", "樔"] },
		{ "question": "票", "answers": ["剽", "漂", "嫖", "慓", "標", "瓢", "縹", "飄", "驃", "鰾"] },
		{ "question": "翏", "answers": ["勠", "寥", "廖", "摎", "蓼", "戮", "樛", "膠", "繆", "謬", "醪", "鏐"] },
		{ "question": "耆", "answers": ["嗜", "蓍", "鰭"] },
		{ "question": "冥", "answers": ["幎", "溟", "暝", "瞑", "螟"] },
		{ "question": "䍃", "answers": ["徭", "搖", "瑤", "遙", "謠", "鷂"] },
		{ "question": "室", "answers": ["榁", "腟", "鰘"] },
		{ "question": "辱", "answers": ["溽", "蓐", "褥", "耨", "縟"] },
		{ "question": "舀", "answers": ["滔", "稻", "蹈", "韜"] },
		{ "question": "巫", "answers": ["筮", "誣", "覡", "噬", "靈"] },
		{ "question": "鹿", "answers": ["麁", "塵", "漉", "麈", "麇", "麋", "轆", "麌", "麗", "麓", "麒", "麕", "麑", "鏖", "儷", "麝", "灑", "麟", "驪", "麤"] },
		{ "question": "髟", "answers": ["髢", "髪", "髦", "髣", "髥", "髫", "髯", "髴", "髱", "髮", "髭", "髻", "髷", "鬆", "鬘", "鬚", "鬟", "鬢", "鬣"] },
		{ "question": "妥", "answers": ["綏", "餒"] },
		{ "question": "芻", "answers": ["鄒", "蒭", "皺", "趨", "雛"] },
		{ "question": "麻", "answers": ["痳", "嘛", "麼", "摩", "麾", "磨", "縻", "糜", "麿", "靡", "魔"] },
		{ "question": "歺", "answers": ["粲", "餐", "燦"] },
		{ "question": "秦", "answers": ["蓁", "榛", "臻"] },
		{ "question": "宰", "answers": ["滓", "縡"] },
		{ "question": "毒", "answers": ["瑇", "纛"] },
		{ "question": "魚", "answers": ["魞", "漁", "魯", "魴", "魳", "魸", "魬", "鮎", "鮒", "鮃", "鮓", "鮑", "鮗", "鮖", "薊", "鮇", "鮮", "鮪", "鮭", "鮫", "鮟", "鮨", "鮠", "鮴", "鮱", "鯉", "鯀", "鯊", "鯒", "鯑", "鯏", "鮹", "鯎", "鮸", "鯨", "鯖", "蘇", "鯵", "鯛", "櫓", "鯣", "鯢", "鯤", "鯲", "鯡", "鯔", "鯱", "鯰", "鰙", "鰐", "鰍", "鰓", "鰉", "鰔", "鰕", "鰌", "鰈", "鰆", "鰒", "鰊", "鰄", "鰛", "蘚", "鰚", "鰘", "鰯", "鰭", "鰮", "鰥", "鰤", "鰰", "艪", "鰧", "鱈", "鰺", "鰻", "鱆", "鱇", "鰾", "癬", "鰹", "鱒", "鱚", "鱛", "鱏", "鱓", "鱗", "鱠", "鱧", "鱟", "鱩", "鱶", "鱲", "鱸"] },
		{ "question": "畀", "answers": ["痹", "鼻"] },
		{ "question": "丌", "answers": ["痹", "鼻"] },
		{ "question": "專", "answers": ["傳", "摶", "蓴", "團", "磚", "甎", "轉", "囀"] },
		{ "question": "奚", "answers": ["溪", "蹊", "谿", "鷄"] },
		{ "question": "⺽", "answers": ["與", "興", "盥", "學", "輿", "覺", "攪", "鷽", "鱟", "黌", "釁", "爨"] },
		{ "question": "号", "answers": ["號", "饕"] },
		{ "question": "郞", "answers": ["廊", "榔", "瑯", "螂"] },
		{ "question": "哥", "answers": ["歌", "謌"] },
		{ "question": "祭", "answers": ["察", "際", "蔡", "擦"] },
		{ "question": "寅", "answers": ["演", "螾"] },
		{ "question": "貫", "answers": ["慣", "實"] },
		{ "question": "竟", "answers": ["境", "鏡"] },
		{ "question": "忩", "answers": ["総", "聡"] },
		{ "question": "象", "answers": ["像", "橡", "豫"] },
		{ "question": "能", "answers": ["態", "熊", "罷", "擺", "羆"] },
		{ "question": "啇", "answers": ["適", "摘", "滴", "嫡", "敵", "謫", "鏑"] },
		{ "question": "章", "answers": ["障", "彰", "嶂", "樟", "璋", "瘴", "鱆"] },
		{ "question": "肉", "answers": ["腐", "臠"] },
		{ "question": "曼", "answers": ["漫", "慢", "蔓", "幔", "縵", "謾", "鏝", "饅", "鬘", "鰻"] },
		{ "question": "曹", "answers": ["遭", "漕", "槽", "糟", "艚"] },
		{ "question": "奞", "answers": ["奪", "奮"] },
		{ "question": "黒", "answers": ["墨", "黛"] },
		{ "question": "桼", "answers": ["漆", "膝"] },
		{ "question": "庶", "answers": ["遮", "蔗", "蹠", "鷓"] },
		{ "question": "孰", "answers": ["塾", "熟"] },
		{ "question": "斬", "answers": ["漸", "塹", "嶄", "慚", "暫", "慙", "槧", "鏨"] },
		{ "question": "寍", "answers": ["寧", "嚀", "濘", "獰", "檸"] },
		{ "question": "菐", "answers": ["僕", "撲", "樸", "璞", "蹼"] },
		{ "question": "尞", "answers": ["僚", "寮", "遼", "撩", "潦", "燎", "療", "瞭", "繚", "鐐", "鷯"] },
		{ "question": "昚", "answers": ["僚", "寮", "遼", "撩", "潦", "燎", "療", "瞭", "繚", "鐐", "鷯"] },
		{ "question": "戍", "answers": ["蔑", "襪", "韈"] },
		{ "question": "皃", "answers": ["貌", "藐"] },
		{ "question": "尉", "answers": ["蔚", "慰", "熨"] },
		{ "question": "猒", "answers": ["厭", "壓", "靨", "魘", "黶"] },
		{ "question": "冐", "answers": ["厭", "壓", "靨", "魘", "黶"] },
		{ "question": "郭", "answers": ["廓", "槨"] },
		{ "question": "既", "answers": ["厩", "漑"] },
		{ "question": "虚", "answers": ["嘘", "戯", "墟", "歔"] },
		{ "question": "喬", "answers": ["僑", "蕎", "嬌", "橋", "矯", "轎", "蹻", "驕"] },
		{ "question": "神", "answers": ["榊", "鰰"] },
		{ "question": "神", "answers": ["榊", "鰰"] },
		{ "question": "敞", "answers": ["厰", "廠"] },
		{ "question": "習", "answers": ["摺", "慴", "翫", "褶"] },
		{ "question": "退", "answers": ["腿", "褪"] },
		{ "question": "追", "answers": ["槌", "縋", "鎚"] },
		{ "question": "逢", "answers": ["蓬", "縫", "篷"] },
		{ "question": "國", "answers": ["摑", "幗"] },
		{ "question": "將", "answers": ["蔣", "奬", "漿", "醬", "鏘"] },
		{ "question": "䙴", "answers": ["僊", "遷", "韆"] },
		{ "question": "喜", "answers": ["僖", "嬉", "熹", "禧", "鱚"] },
		{ "question": "堯", "answers": ["僥", "嶢", "撓", "澆", "蕘", "橈", "遶", "曉", "燒", "磽", "蟯", "繞", "翹", "鐃", "饒", "驍"] },
		{ "question": "朁", "answers": ["僭", "潛", "簪", "譖", "蠶"] },
		{ "question": "兓", "answers": ["僭", "潛", "簪", "譖", "蠶"] },
		{ "question": "兂", "answers": ["僭", "潛", "簪", "譖", "蠶"] },
		{ "question": "替", "answers": ["僣", "潜", "譛"] },
		{ "question": "童", "answers": ["僮", "憧", "撞", "幢", "橦", "瞳", "艟", "鐘"] },
		{ "question": "貴", "answers": ["匱", "遺", "潰", "櫃", "簣", "饋"] },
		{ "question": "族", "answers": ["嗾", "蔟", "簇", "鏃"] },
		{ "question": "欶", "answers": ["嗽", "漱"] },
		{ "question": "敕", "answers": ["嫩", "整"] },
		{ "question": "康", "answers": ["慷", "糠", "鱇"] },
		{ "question": "貢", "answers": ["槓", "熕"] },
		{ "question": "羕", "answers": ["漾", "樣"] },
		{ "question": "參", "answers": ["滲", "蔘", "慘", "糝", "驂", "鰺"] },
		{ "question": "鹵", "answers": ["滷", "鹸", "鹹", "鹼", "鹽"] },
		{ "question": "條", "answers": ["滌", "篠"] },
		{ "question": "甾", "answers": ["緇", "輜", "錙", "鯔"] },
		{ "question": "厘", "answers": ["甅", "竰", "糎", "釐"] },
		{ "question": "巸", "answers": ["煕", "熙"] },
		{ "question": "睪", "answers": ["睾", "懌", "澤", "擇", "繹", "譯", "釋", "鐸", "驛"] },
		{ "question": "啚", "answers": ["鄙", "圖"] },
		{ "question": "虐", "answers": ["瘧", "謔"] },
		{ "question": "宿", "answers": ["蓿", "縮"] },
		{ "question": "帶", "answers": ["蔕", "滯"] },
		{ "question": "斯", "answers": ["厮", "嘶", "廝", "撕"] },
		{ "question": "爲", "answers": ["僞", "譌"] },
		{ "question": "丫", "answers": ["齊", "韲"] },
		{ "question": "⺻", "answers": ["盡", "儘", "燼", "贐"] },
		{ "question": "虒", "answers": ["遞", "褫", "篪"] },
		{ "question": "吋", "answers": ["壽", "儔", "濤", "擣", "檮", "禱", "疇", "籌", "躊", "鑄"] },
		{ "question": "㒼", "answers": ["滿", "瞞", "蟎", "懣", "蹣"] },
		{ "question": "曾", "answers": ["僧", "噌", "層", "憎", "增", "甑", "贈", "鱛"] },
		{ "question": "黄", "answers": ["横", "廣", "簧", "黌"] },
		{ "question": "意", "answers": ["億", "憶", "噫", "薏", "臆"] },
		{ "question": "㗊", "answers": ["器", "器", "囂"] },
		{ "question": "巽", "answers": ["選", "撰", "饌"] },
		{ "question": "隺", "answers": ["確", "鶴"] },
		{ "question": "斦", "answers": ["質", "躓"] },
		{ "question": "㳟", "answers": ["暴", "瀑", "爆", "曝"] },
		{ "question": "豦", "answers": ["劇", "據", "遽", "醵"] },
		{ "question": "朝", "answers": ["潮", "嘲", "廟"] },
		{ "question": "景", "answers": ["影", "憬"] },
		{ "question": "義", "answers": ["儀", "嶬", "犠", "礒", "蟻", "艤", "議"] },
		{ "question": "軗", "answers": ["撃", "繋"] },
		{ "question": "登", "answers": ["澄", "嶝", "橙", "燈", "磴", "證", "鐙"] },
		{ "question": "沓", "answers": ["踏", "鞜"] },
		{ "question": "賁", "answers": ["噴", "墳", "憤", "濆"] },
		{ "question": "尊", "answers": ["遵", "噂", "樽", "蹲", "鱒"] },
		{ "question": "番", "answers": ["審", "播", "幡", "蕃", "潘", "膰", "燔", "藩", "翻", "旛", "蟠", "瀋", "繙", "飜", "鷭"] },
		{ "question": "㥑", "answers": ["憂", "優", "擾"] },
		{ "question": "舄", "answers": ["潟", "寫", "瀉"] },
		{ "question": "育", "answers": ["徹", "撤", "轍"] },
		{ "question": "敝", "answers": ["幣", "弊", "蔽", "瞥", "斃", "鼈"] },
		{ "question": "羔", "answers": ["窯", "羹"] },
		{ "question": "復", "answers": ["履", "覆"] },
		{ "question": "執", "answers": ["摯", "蟄", "贄", "鷙"] },
		{ "question": "間", "answers": ["澗", "簡"] },
		{ "question": "規", "answers": ["槻", "窺"] },
		{ "question": "厥", "answers": ["蕨", "獗", "蹶"] },
		{ "question": "歯", "answers": ["噛", "齢"] },
		{ "question": "散", "answers": ["撒", "繖", "霰"] },
		{ "question": "焦", "answers": ["蕉", "憔", "樵", "礁", "鷦"] },
		{ "question": "奠", "answers": ["鄭", "擲", "躑"] },
		{ "question": "尌", "answers": ["廚", "樹"] },
		{ "question": "惢", "answers": ["蕊", "蘂"] },
		{ "question": "歮", "answers": ["蕋", "澁"] },
		{ "question": "然", "answers": ["撚", "燃"] },
		{ "question": "湯", "answers": ["蕩", "盪", "蘯"] },
		{ "question": "無", "answers": ["撫", "蕪", "嘸", "廡", "憮"] },
		{ "question": "辟", "answers": ["僻", "劈", "避", "壁", "嬖", "薜", "擘", "檗", "臂", "癖", "璧", "甓", "襞", "蘗", "躄", "譬", "躃", "闢", "霹"] },
		{ "question": "麥", "answers": ["麪", "麩", "麭", "麴", "麵"] },
		{ "question": "虛", "answers": ["噓", "墟", "歔"] },
		{ "question": "發", "answers": ["潑", "撥", "廢", "癈", "醱"] },
		{ "question": "閒", "answers": ["㵎", "嫺", "燗", "癇", "繝"] },
		{ "question": "䖵", "answers": ["蝱", "蝨", "螽", "蟲", "蠢", "蠡", "蠧", "蠱", "蠹", "蠶"] },
		{ "question": "畺", "answers": ["僵", "彊", "薑", "橿", "疆"] },
		{ "question": "雋", "answers": ["儁", "鐫"] },
		{ "question": "農", "answers": ["儂", "濃", "膿"] },
		{ "question": "幕", "answers": ["冪", "羃"] },
		{ "question": "稟", "answers": ["凜", "廩", "懍"] },
		{ "question": "僉", "answers": ["匳", "劍", "儉", "嶮", "險", "斂", "臉", "歛", "檢", "瞼", "簽", "瀲", "籡", "驗", "鹼"] },
		{ "question": "壹", "answers": ["噎", "殪", "饐", "懿"] },
		{ "question": "單", "answers": ["嬋", "憚", "鄲", "彈", "殫", "戰", "襌", "禪", "簞", "蟬", "闡", "驒", "鱓"] },
		{ "question": "戠", "answers": ["幟", "熾", "職", "織", "識"] },
		{ "question": "堅", "answers": ["慳", "樫", "鏗", "鰹"] },
		{ "question": "從", "answers": ["慫", "樅", "聳", "縱", "蹤"] },
		{ "question": "勞", "answers": ["撈", "癆"] },
		{ "question": "戚", "answers": ["槭", "蹙"] },
		{ "question": "棥", "answers": ["樊", "攀", "礬"] },
		{ "question": "彭", "answers": ["澎", "膨"] },
		{ "question": "覃", "answers": ["潭", "蕈", "簟", "譚", "鐔", "鱏"] },
		{ "question": "尋", "answers": ["潯", "蕁"] },
		{ "question": "展", "answers": ["碾", "輾"] },
		{ "question": "威", "answers": ["縅", "鰄"] },
		{ "question": "鬥", "answers": ["鬧", "鬨", "鬩", "鬪", "鬮"] },
		{ "question": "脊", "answers": ["瘠", "蹐", "鶺"] },
		{ "question": "向", "answers": ["餉", "嚮"] },
		{ "question": "畟", "answers": ["稷", "禝", "謖"] },
		{ "question": "戕", "answers": ["臧", "藏", "贓", "臟"] },
		{ "question": "隋", "answers": ["墮", "橢"] },
		{ "question": "黃", "answers": ["廣", "橫", "壙", "簧", "擴", "曠", "礦", "纊", "鑛", "黌"] },
		{ "question": "買", "answers": ["賣", "瀆", "犢", "牘", "竇", "續", "覿", "贖", "讀", "黷"] },
		{ "question": "黑", "answers": ["墨", "黔", "默", "黜", "黝", "點", "黠", "黥", "壥", "黨", "黯", "纒", "儻", "黴", "黶", "黷"] },
		{ "question": "楽", "answers": ["薬", "檪"] },
		{ "question": "幾", "answers": ["機", "磯", "譏", "饑"] },
		{ "question": "敫", "answers": ["激", "徼", "檄", "邀", "竅", "覈", "繳"] },
		{ "question": "喿", "answers": ["操", "噪", "懆", "澡", "燥", "繰", "藻", "躁", "譟"] },
		{ "question": "蒦", "answers": ["獲", "穫", "蠖", "護"] },
		{ "question": "隻", "answers": ["獲", "穫", "蠖", "護"] },
		{ "question": "新", "answers": ["薪", "噺"] },
		{ "question": "蜀", "answers": ["濁", "獨", "燭", "躅", "觸", "屬", "髑"] },
		{ "question": "雲", "answers": ["曇", "繧", "壜", "罎", "靆", "靉"] },
		{ "question": "溥", "answers": ["薄", "簿"] },
		{ "question": "敏", "answers": ["繁", "繁"] },
		{ "question": "敏", "answers": ["繁", "繁"] },
		{ "question": "粦", "answers": ["隣", "憐", "鄰", "燐", "驎", "鱗", "麟"] },
		{ "question": "疑", "answers": ["凝", "擬", "嶷", "礙", "癡"] },
		{ "question": "貇", "answers": ["墾", "懇"] },
		{ "question": "㐮", "answers": ["嬢", "壌", "穣", "譲", "醸"] },
		{ "question": "亶", "answers": ["壇", "擅", "檀", "氈", "羶", "顫"] },
		{ "question": "雍", "answers": ["擁", "壅", "甕"] },
		{ "question": "睘", "answers": ["還", "圜", "寰", "環", "鐶", "鬟"] },
		{ "question": "感", "answers": ["憾", "撼", "轗"] },
		{ "question": "需", "answers": ["儒", "嬬", "濡", "孺", "懦", "臑", "襦", "蠕", "繻", "糯", "轜", "顬"] },
		{ "question": "善", "answers": ["膳", "繕"] },
		{ "question": "睿", "answers": ["叡", "濬"] },
		{ "question": "矞", "answers": ["橘", "譎", "鷸"] },
		{ "question": "盡", "answers": ["儘", "燼", "贐"] },
		{ "question": "殿", "answers": ["澱", "臀", "癜"] },
		{ "question": "路", "answers": ["蕗", "露", "鷺"] },
		{ "question": "畱", "answers": ["璢", "籒"] },
		{ "question": "丣", "answers": ["璢", "籒"] },
		{ "question": "齊", "answers": ["儕", "劑", "擠", "薺", "濟", "齋", "臍", "纃", "齎", "躋", "霽", "齏"] },
		{ "question": "壽", "answers": ["儔", "濤", "擣", "檮", "禱", "疇", "籌", "躊", "鑄"] },
		{ "question": "異", "answers": ["冀", "翼", "戴", "糞", "驥"] },
		{ "question": "禁", "answers": ["噤", "襟"] },
		{ "question": "肅", "answers": ["嘯", "蕭", "繡", "瀟", "簫"] },
		{ "question": "蒿", "answers": ["嚆", "藁"] },
		{ "question": "與", "answers": ["嶼", "歟", "擧", "譽", "欅", "襷"] },
		{ "question": "解", "answers": ["廨", "懈", "邂", "蟹", "蠏"] },
		{ "question": "奧", "answers": ["懊", "澳", "燠", "襖"] },
		{ "question": "奥", "answers": ["懊", "澳", "燠", "襖"] },
		{ "question": "詹", "answers": ["憺", "澹", "擔", "檐", "膽", "瞻", "蟾", "簷", "譫", "贍"] },
		{ "question": "禽", "answers": ["擒", "檎"] },
		{ "question": "達", "answers": ["撻", "燵", "闥", "韃"] },
		{ "question": "雷", "answers": ["擂", "蕾", "鱩"] },
		{ "question": "敦", "answers": ["暾", "燉", "鐓"] },
		{ "question": "敢", "answers": ["橄", "厳", "瞰", "巌", "嚴", "儼", "巖"] },
		{ "question": "敬", "answers": ["檠", "警", "驚"] },
		{ "question": "蒙", "answers": ["濛", "朦", "曚", "檬", "矇", "艨"] },
		{ "question": "殸", "answers": ["磬", "聲", "謦", "馨"] },
		{ "question": "声", "answers": ["磬", "聲", "謦", "馨"] },
		{ "question": "強", "answers": ["襁", "繈"] },
		{ "question": "强", "answers": ["襁", "繦"] },
		{ "question": "虽", "answers": ["襁", "雖", "繦"] },
		{ "question": "美", "answers": ["躾", "羹"] },
		{ "question": "會", "answers": ["獪", "薈", "檜", "膾", "繪", "鱠"] },
		{ "question": "堂", "answers": ["瞠", "螳"] },
		{ "question": "遂", "answers": ["隧", "燧", "邃"] },
		{ "question": "累", "answers": ["瘰", "螺", "縲", "騾"] },
		{ "question": "舜", "answers": ["蕣", "瞬"] },
		{ "question": "嗇", "answers": ["薔", "墻", "檣", "牆", "穡", "艢"] },
		{ "question": "萬", "answers": ["邁", "勵", "癘", "礪", "蠆", "蠣", "糲"] },
		{ "question": "熏", "answers": ["勳", "薰", "燻", "醺"] },
		{ "question": "厲", "answers": ["勵", "礪", "蠣", "糲"] },
		{ "question": "県", "answers": ["縣", "懸", "纛"] },
		{ "question": "遀", "answers": ["隨", "髓"] },
		{ "question": "厤", "answers": ["曆", "歷", "瀝", "櫪", "癧", "靂"] },
		{ "question": "秝", "answers": ["曆", "歷", "瀝", "櫪", "癧", "靂"] },
		{ "question": "射", "answers": ["謝", "麝"] },
		{ "question": "憂", "answers": ["優", "擾"] },
		{ "question": "翟", "answers": ["濯", "擢", "曜", "戳", "櫂", "燿", "耀", "躍", "糴", "糶"] },
		{ "question": "愛", "answers": ["曖", "靉"] },
		{ "question": "賏", "answers": ["嬰", "嚶", "罌", "瓔", "贔", "櫻", "癭", "纓", "屭", "鸚"] },
		{ "question": "豪", "answers": ["壕", "濠"] },
		{ "question": "署", "answers": ["曙", "薯"] },
		{ "question": "署", "answers": ["曙", "薯"] },
		{ "question": "丱", "answers": ["聯", "關"] },
		{ "question": "黍", "answers": ["黏", "黐"] },
		{ "question": "畾", "answers": ["儡", "壘", "罍", "疊"] },
		{ "question": "寧", "answers": ["嚀", "濘", "獰", "檸"] },
		{ "question": "鼻", "answers": ["嚊", "嬶", "鼾"] },
		{ "question": "賓", "answers": ["嬪", "擯", "濱", "檳", "殯", "繽", "鬢"] },
		{ "question": "賓", "answers": ["嬪", "擯", "濱", "檳", "殯", "繽", "鬢"] },
		{ "question": "臺", "answers": ["擡", "薹"] },
		{ "question": "齒", "answers": ["齔", "嚙", "齣", "齟", "齠", "齡", "齦", "齧", "齬", "齪", "囓", "齷", "齲", "齶"] },
		{ "question": "黹", "answers": ["黻", "黼"] },
		{ "question": "狊", "answers": ["闃", "鶪"] },
		{ "question": "䧹", "answers": ["膺", "應", "鷹", "軈"] },
		{ "question": "爾", "answers": ["濔", "彌", "邇", "璽", "禰", "瀰"] },
		{ "question": "畢", "answers": ["篳", "蹕"] },
		{ "question": "雪", "answers": ["艝", "轌", "鱈"] },
		{ "question": "㬎", "answers": ["隰", "濕", "顯"] },
		{ "question": "耤", "answers": ["藉", "籍"] },
		{ "question": "殹", "answers": ["翳", "醫"] },
		{ "question": "医", "answers": ["翳", "醫"] },
		{ "question": "悤", "answers": ["總", "聰"] },
		{ "question": "惠", "answers": ["穗", "蟪"] },
		{ "question": "厭", "answers": ["壓", "靨", "魘", "黶"] },
		{ "question": "㥯", "answers": ["隱", "穩"] },
		{ "question": "类", "answers": ["類", "類"] },
		{ "question": "監", "answers": ["濫", "藍", "檻", "襤", "艦", "籃", "鑑"] },
		{ "question": "滕", "answers": ["藤", "籐"] },
		{ "question": "丵", "answers": ["叢", "鑿"] },
		{ "question": "數", "answers": ["藪", "籔"] },
		{ "question": "諸", "answers": ["儲", "藷"] },
		{ "question": "諸", "answers": ["儲", "藷"] },
		{ "question": "賣", "answers": ["瀆", "犢", "牘", "竇", "續", "覿", "贖", "讀", "黷"] },
		{ "question": "劉", "answers": ["嚠", "瀏"] },
		{ "question": "廣", "answers": ["壙", "擴", "曠", "礦", "纊", "鑛"] },
		{ "question": "韯", "answers": ["懴", "殱", "籖"] },
		{ "question": "鄭", "answers": ["擲", "躑"] },
		{ "question": "罷", "answers": ["擺", "羆"] },
		{ "question": "樂", "answers": ["擽", "藥", "櫟", "爍", "礫", "轢", "鑠"] },
		{ "question": "賛", "answers": ["攅", "纉", "讃", "鑚"] },
		{ "question": "鼓", "answers": ["鼕", "瞽"] },
		{ "question": "鼠", "answers": ["鼬", "竄", "鼯", "鼴"] },
		{ "question": "養", "answers": ["瀁", "癢", "鱶"] },
		{ "question": "暴", "answers": ["瀑", "爆", "曝"] },
		{ "question": "慮", "answers": ["濾", "鑢"] },
		{ "question": "當", "answers": ["礑", "襠", "蟷", "鐺"] },
		{ "question": "香", "answers": ["馥", "馨"] },
		{ "question": "聑", "answers": ["聶", "囁", "懾", "攝", "躡", "鑷", "顳"] },
		{ "question": "䀠", "answers": ["瞿", "矍", "懼", "攫", "衢", "钁"] },
		{ "question": "蓺", "answers": ["藝", "囈"] },
		{ "question": "巤", "answers": ["獵", "臘", "蠟", "鑞", "鬣", "鱲"] },
		{ "question": "臧", "answers": ["藏", "贓", "臟"] },
		{ "question": "豊", "answers": ["禮", "艶", "醴", "體", "鱧"] },
		{ "question": "雔", "answers": ["雙", "讐"] },
		{ "question": "㡭", "answers": ["斷", "繼"] },
		{ "question": "䩗", "answers": ["覇", "霸"] },
		{ "question": "維", "answers": ["羅", "蘿", "邏", "鑼"] },
		{ "question": "就", "answers": ["蹴", "鷲"] },
		{ "question": "龍", "answers": ["寵", "壟", "隴", "蘢", "龐", "瀧", "朧", "瓏", "襲", "籠", "聾", "龕"] },
		{ "question": "頻", "answers": ["瀕", "蘋", "顰"] },
		{ "question": "頻", "answers": ["瀕", "蘋", "顰"] },
		{ "question": "黽", "answers": ["蠅", "繩", "竈", "鼇", "鼈"] },
		{ "question": "闌", "answers": ["蘭", "瀾", "爛", "欄", "襴"] },
		{ "question": "䦨", "answers": ["蘭", "欄"] },
		{ "question": "廉", "answers": ["簾", "蠊"] },
		{ "question": "魯", "answers": ["櫓", "艪"] },
		{ "question": "燕", "answers": ["嚥", "臙", "讌"] },
		{ "question": "鄉", "answers": ["嚮", "響", "饗"] },
		{ "question": "郷", "answers": ["嚮", "響", "饗"] },
		{ "question": "鄕", "answers": ["嚮", "饗", "響"] },
		{ "question": "曇", "answers": ["壜", "罎"] },
		{ "question": "賴", "answers": ["嬾", "懶", "獺", "藾", "瀨", "癩", "籟"] },
		{ "question": "盧", "answers": ["廬", "蘆", "櫨", "臚", "爐", "艫", "轤", "鑪", "顱", "驢", "鱸"] },
		{ "question": "樊", "answers": ["攀", "礬"] },
		{ "question": "吂", "answers": ["瀛", "羸", "贏"] },
		{ "question": "歷", "answers": ["瀝", "櫪", "癧", "靂"] },
		{ "question": "蔑", "answers": ["襪", "韈"] },
		{ "question": "閵", "answers": ["藺", "躙", "躪"] },
		{ "question": "謁", "answers": ["藹", "靄"] },
		{ "question": "謁", "answers": ["藹", "靄"] },
		{ "question": "雚", "answers": ["勸", "灌", "懽", "權", "歡", "罐", "讙", "觀", "鑵", "顴", "驩", "鸛"] },
		{ "question": "褱", "answers": ["懷", "壞"] },
		{ "question": "眔", "answers": ["懷", "壞", "鰥"] },
		{ "question": "兟", "answers": ["贊", "攢", "纘", "讚", "鑽"] },
		{ "question": "縣", "answers": ["懸", "纛"] },
		{ "question": "嬰", "answers": ["嚶", "瓔", "櫻", "癭", "纓", "鸚"] },
		{ "question": "韱", "answers": ["孅", "懺", "殲", "籤", "纖", "讖"] },
		{ "question": "㦰", "answers": ["孅", "懺", "殲", "籤", "纖", "讖"] },
		{ "question": "毚", "answers": ["巉", "纔", "讒"] },
		{ "question": "㲋", "answers": ["巉", "纔", "讒"] },
		{ "question": "襄", "answers": ["攘", "壤", "孃", "曩", "禳", "穰", "釀", "讓", "驤"] },
		{ "question": "羲", "answers": ["曦", "犧"] },
		{ "question": "頡", "answers": ["襭", "纈"] },
		{ "question": "瞿", "answers": ["矍", "懼", "攫", "衢", "钁"] },
		{ "question": "鮮", "answers": ["蘚", "癬"] },
		{ "question": "墨", "answers": ["壥", "纒"] },
		{ "question": "辥", "answers": ["櫱", "糱"] },
		{ "question": "龜", "answers": ["龝", "鬮"] },
		{ "question": "廛", "answers": ["纏", "躔"] },
		{ "question": "難", "answers": ["儺", "灘", "攤"] },
		{ "question": "難", "answers": ["儺", "灘", "攤"] },
		{ "question": "麗", "answers": ["儷", "灑", "驪"] },
		{ "question": "聶", "answers": ["囁", "懾", "攝", "躡", "鑷", "顳"] },
		{ "question": "雝", "answers": ["廱", "癰"] },
		{ "question": "邕", "answers": ["廱", "癰"] },
		{ "question": "擧", "answers": ["欅", "襷"] },
		{ "question": "霝", "answers": ["櫺", "靈"] },
		{ "question": "遣", "answers": ["譴", "鑓"] },
		{ "question": "嚴", "answers": ["儼", "巖"] },
		{ "question": "顚", "answers": ["巓", "癲"] },
		{ "question": "䜌", "answers": ["巒", "彎", "攣", "欒", "戀", "變", "臠", "蠻", "灣", "鑾", "癴", "鸞"] },
		{ "question": "羅", "answers": ["蘿", "邏", "鑼"] },
		{ "question": "贊", "answers": ["攢", "纘", "讚", "鑽"] },
		{ "question": "矍", "answers": ["攫", "钁"] },
		{ "question": "龠", "answers": ["籥", "鑰"] },
		{ "question": "屬", "answers": ["囑", "矚"] },
		{ "question": "覽", "answers": ["攬", "欖", "纜"] }
	]
}
